Come on! Will you... will
you go? Come on, go, go.
Hey, you cheated on your current wife
with seven different women.
I got digital proof of all of it.
And if you don't stop seeing Krista,
your wife will know everything.
- Done.
- And one more thing.
I'm gonna need something from you.
I don't just hack you,
Krista, I hack everyone.
So I gotta be honest,
I was impressed by you.
I think I can land you
a pretty lucrative gig.
- Who are you?
- That'll come later.
Elliot, listen to me.
I will never leave you.
I will never leave you alone again.
- Who are you talking to?
- Since last month,
- Evil Corp has moved its tapes to five...
- Five backup facilities
and you have a plan to take them all down.
Why are you working with us?
The hack, everything, maybe
we shouldn't execute it.
Why?
The minute our infected server
gets back on the main network,
we're set.
Scott will continue here,
but you, I'm afraid, cannot.
_
- What the hell are you...
- Shh.
I don't know what your grand plan is,
but I need to, and you're going to tell me.
Why did you do it?
What did you hope to
accomplish by doing all of this?
I wanted to save the world.
Hey.
It's so good to see you.
You look great.
- Can I get you a drink?
- Look, Michael, I don't...
Jesus.
I forgot.
It's not even your real name.
It's, uh... Lenny.
Lenny.
So tell me what's going on.
How advanced is it?
I already emailed my
friend at Sloan Kettering.
If it's as serious as you say...
- Krista. Krista.
- Then she wants to...
Look.
I'm not dying.
You're a sick motherfucker!
Look, hold on. It's the only way
- I could get you to meet up.
- Don't you ever call me again,
- even when you are dying.
- One of your patients hacked me.
Some kid.
His name's Elliot Alderson.
I went to the police already.
Please sit back down.
We need to talk about this.
Here. The police had
their cyber crime division
look into it.
They've been trying to track
him down for the past six weeks.
- What is this?
- That proves it was him.
He took my dog to the vet.
Look. See, she was microchipped,
and I gave her chip number
to all the vets in the city.
This sick fucker not only
hacked me and ruined my life,
he stole my dog on top of it.
This guy's certifiable.
I mean, he's seeing you,
so technically he is.
- What did he do to you exactly?
- He made me...
you know...
say all those things to you.
This kid should not be
allowed to do what he did.
He hacked into my private life.
And then that Ashley
Madison leak happened.
My wife found out about
everything anyway.
After the whole thing, she left me.
I can't even see my little girl.
- The divorce is... is a nightmare.
- I don't give a shit about your divorce.
Look, if he's doing this to me,
then he must be doing this to other people.
Think about it.
If he knew enough
about me to hack me,
then that means he must
have hacked you, too.
He did, didn't he?
- I can't talk about this with you.
- Hey! You have to help me catch him.
The dog thing alone isn't enough.
My buddy says this
Computer Abuse and Fraud Act
is tough to prosecute.
You need a lot of evidence.
This kid is good, Krista.
He was routing through something
called proxies or something
out in Estonia.
He's untraceable.
Short of that whole
country falling apart,
we're never gonna get our
hands on any real evidence.
- Just what exactly do you think I can do?
- Maybe he said something.
You know, in your sessions.
Oh, come on, don't give me that
privileged information bullshit.
This guy's committing
a crime, a serious one.
He deserves to go to jail.
If you know something,
if he said anything,
you have to tell me.
Look, I'm not the enemy here.
He is.
We were a good thing.
Remember?
I mean, don't you remember this place?
We had some good times here.
Come on.
Don't stay mad at me.
I really loved you.
He never told me anything.
I can't help you.
The asshole stole my dog!
The response to the Japanese
and Chinese stock markets
has provoked panic, setting
off the downward trends
of the European stock exchange.
But what's even more worrisome
is that the IMF has no leverage
against these defaults.
Already, 17 governments
are said to be
in large-scale crises with
some on the verge of collapse.
Among the countries are Lithuania,
Croatia, Ukraine, Romania,
the Czech Republic, and Estonia.
This faction has deemed
the hack inflicted
upon the world's largest conglomerate
as an opportunity for reform
and a chance to start anew,
building more egalitarian
economies with lessons learned
from decades of economic disparity.
A spokesperson for a group...
- Synced and corrected by skoad -
www.addic7ed.com
- Where am I?
- Excuse me?
- I mean, where am I?
- You've been parked
in the lot for the past two days.
That's as much as you paid me
before the credit card systems went down.
I'm gonna need some cash, man.
This is Tyrell's.
Why were we in there?
Oh, don't tell me you don't have any cash.
Ha, you're shit out of
luck for a while, buddy.
I don't understand.
How long have you been asleep?
Seriously, what do you remember?
Wait, I don't even trust you.
Hey.
Hey, where you going?
What about your car?
Hey, we're gonna tow your car tonight!
- What took you so long?
- I just had to shower and change.
You're still new here. I wouldn't push it.
Jesus Christ, finally you're here.
- Where have you been?
- Yeah, man.
I mean, not cool, not cool at all.
I thought we were
gonna execute together.
I mean, what is going on here?
He's just saying that we
had planned on something
- a little more ceremonial.
- Ceremonial? Man,
we been wiping drives,
wrangling cables, pulling
fiber taps and the...
Okay, everyone, lay off!
I'm sure he had his reasons.
Besides, whatever. The
point is, it worked.
- Jesus, what did I do?
- We need to clean up
and get the hell out of here.
Were you there? Did you see it?
- What did I do?
- Elliot, what's going on?
You disappear on me at the apartment
and come here to execute
without even telling me.
Execute. It executed, but how?
- I... what happened to Tyrell?
- Then you were gone
for another three days.
- Where have you been?
- Are you saying... it went through?
Like gangbusters.
People are loving it.
They actually want to join fsociety.
Elliot, they're organizing
protests all across the city.
_
Elliot! What's going on?
- Are you still seeing him?
- No, but I need to.
Dude, you can't just leave.
We're in wipe-down mode here
- and we need your help.
- I told you we shouldn't have done this.
So, okay, your burn rate,
that's rent and utilities
alone, is 50,000 a month.
Your lease isn't up for
another three months,
so we have to eat those
costs no matter what.
So that leaves us with
staffing, operations,
outstanding loans, equipment rentals.
I'm just gonna call it, Gideon.
You have to shut down Allsafe.
Maybe I can just buy some time.
We could bounce back from this.
Gideon, your number one client
is in the middle of a major crisis.
You can't escape the
fallout from this.
As your part-time CFO and your friend,
I have to be honest and tell you,
this is beyond bleak.
- When is it not?
- I'm sorry?
Ever since I started this company,
it's felt like we've just been
rearranging chairs on
the goddamn "Titanic."
When was the last time you and I
- have not had a depressing conversation?
- Gideon, I handle the money.
It's always gonna be a
depressing conversation.
Best thing you can do for them
is to let them know soon
so they can find other jobs.
And...
What?
All their 401(k)s were
tied up in the market...
Which is expected to
plummet once the bell rings.
Well, that's only rumors at this point.
What?
Seems to be a little more than rumors.
Every bank is essentially affected.
I know I couldn't use any of my
credit cards over the weekend.
Could you?
Well, I don't know.
There might be a silver lining to all this.
If what they're saying
about these fsociety hackers
is actually true, you'll now have no debt.
Why did Tyrell let this happen?
He was with me. I told
him the whole plan.
He was gonna stop it.
A simple program, a worm that
can make data unreadable,
malware that took Darlene
maybe two hours to code.
Is that really all it
takes to kill the world?
Shouldn't I be enjoying this?
- _
- Why am I even looking for Tyrell?
Isn't this what we wanted?
So this is what a
revolution looks like,
people in expensive
clothing running around.
Not how I pictured it.
I wonder what stage they're at.
Denial? Muttering to themselves?
No, this can be fixed.
Maybe bargaining, forcing
their techs to work overtime
to try to decrypt our data.
Or have they come to
the realization yet
that Darlene encrypted everything
with 256-bit AES and it would take
an incomprehensible
amount of time to crack?
That all of their data is
actually gone for good?
No, I have to find him.
I have to know what happened.
_
- Can I help you with something?
- Yes, I'm looking for Tyrell Wellick.
He's not here.
He doesn't work here anymore.
Why are you here? What do
you need to see him for?
And, yes, confirmation coming in.
This is fsociety
claiming responsibility
for the hack.
We are cutting live to
the video right now.
Evil Corp, we have delivered
on our promise as expected.
The people of the world who
have been enslaved by you
have been freed.
Your financial data
has been destroyed.
Any attempts to salvage it
will be utterly futile.
Face it, you have been owned.
We at fsociety will smile
as we watch you and
your dark soul die.
That means any money
you owe these pigs
has been forgiven by us,
your friends at fsociety.
The market's opening
bell this morning
will be the final death
knell of Evil Corp.
We hope, as a new society
rises from the ashes,
that you will forge a better world,
a world that values a free people,
a world where greed
is not encouraged,
a world that belongs to us again,
a world changed forever!
And while you do that,
remember to repeat these words.
We are fsociety.
- We are finally free.
- _
We are finally awake!
Authorities have been trying
to locate the whereabouts
of the mysterious masked man
as well as other members
of the fsociety collective.
The investigation is still underway.
The FBI Cybercrime
Division is working with...
Where's my bag?
I need my bag. It... it has all my papers.
I put all of your talking
points on these index cards
- so that you wouldn't have to...
- God damn it!
Will you please just give
me my bag, for Christ's sake?
I asked you to keep it close by.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean anything by it.
- I was just trying to...
- Never mind what you meant.
Just do as I say.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to snap at you.
It's been a long day,
and... and I'm not used to
all the new faces around here.
No problem.
Four minutes, people!
Let's get last looks. Let's go.
So anyways, this should
fry anything and everything
to a crisp.
You're in luck. My boss is at the bank.
Seems like everybody's
lining up this morning.
So you got some time.
Jesus,
- are we really doing this right now?
- Hey, I don't need no judgment.
Not like I want to be here either.
Sorry, dude, I got no sympathy.
You don't want to put cute
puppies out of their misery,
you don't have to.
That's just sick.
That ain't on me. I gotta pay the bills.
That's the only reason why I'm here.
You know, I've run all the scenarios
of our little revolution here, but, uh...
using a dead puppy oven was not on my list.
Can I help you?
Yeah.
Looking for Tyrell Wellick.
- Is he here?
- No.
He's not.
Do you know where he is?
- Who are you?
- Good question.
We work together.
He'll be home soon.
Just called me from
the car ten minutes ago.
He's stuck in some traffic.
You're welcome to wait
inside if you want.
Whoo! Oh, shit!
- Come on, get up!
- Fsociety, bitch!
- Yeah, that's how it is, baby!
- Whoo!
What did you say your name was?
Uh... I'm Ollie.
And what were you working
on with my husband?
You've gotta help
me get out of this.
There's something about her.
I feel like she can hear us.
He wanted my advice,
you know, about the hack
that's going on right now.
When was the last time you saw him?
She's lying to me. He isn't coming.
She's fishing for something.
I'm not sure.
It was last week, I think.
Really?
You know, between you and me,
I'm a little concerned for Tyrell.
Was he acting strange when you saw him?
No.
That's funny,
'cause he was acting very strange
last I saw him.
Three days ago.
Didn't she say he just called?
And then he just vanished.
Excuse me?
I don't understand what you're saying.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah. I think it's just the stress
from the past few days getting to me.
Anyway, I shouldn't take
up any more of your time.
Thank you... Ollie.
And, Sarah, we've had meetings all weekend
handling the situation.
I'm being told by our network storage team
that they are in fact
getting to the bottom of this.
Mr. Plouffe, have you seen
the latest stock price?
It's hitting an all-time low of $18,
and it's still dropping.
How are people reacting
to this on the inside?
Almost $400 billion of
wealth was lost today.
That's pretty astounding.
Are you concerned?
That's an interesting question.
But right now we're focused on tackling
the technical issues at hand.
We have loyal customers who are suffering,
and our number one priority
is to address their needs.
We had one of our experts
in here earlier today.
They're saying that if, in fact,
fsociety's claims are true...
Your data is inaccessible
and could prove nearly
impossible to recover.
And given that there does seem
to be some legitimacy to this...
The White House is with us on this.
They're gonna protect everyone's money.
The bottom line is
the public does not
need to worry about this.
Mr. Plouffe, this
was a massive attack.
All of your servers, including
your data center in China
as well as your offline
backups have been destroyed.
I'm not really sure you can
ask the public not to worry.
- You want me to be honest?
- Of course.
You're right. Absolutely right.
The public should be worried.
I mean, personally, my life is over.
What's happening?
My pension, savings, everything...
has been in this company
since I started here,
and that's all gone now.
Truth is...
I've been with the
engineering team all weekend.
This has to stop. That's enough.
No one knows how to fix it.
In fact, about the only
thing we do know for certain
is that...
this will be impossible to fix.
You need to take care of this.
Calm down, everyone.
That's all we need from
Ms. Moss, Mr. Price.
- Good. Thank you.
- Sir.
Thanks.
I heard you were leaving for the day.
Mr. Price...
- did you need me to stay?
- No, no, no, no. Sit, sit.
I know I'm the CEO of the company,
but what you went
through, it was traumatic.
I just felt I needed to
make myself available.
You are absolutely free to... to go home
and... and recover, of course.
All right?
Oh.
You're Terry's reference, right?
I rarely see him impressed
with anyone, but you... you?
Well... we're glad you're on the team.
And I look forward to
you impressing me as well.
You know, I'm... I'm
holding a press conference
this afternoon.
Since you're new to the PR department,
I think you should attend.
You might pick up some invaluable lessons.
Um...
no.
No, I'm not sure that I can.
Well, the invitation is open
if you should change your mind.
Um...
You need some new shoes.
Those won't do anymore.
Tyrell Wellick's gone.
I wake up in his SUV and the
world's about to fall apart.
I know. I know this looks bad,
but I'm sure there's an explanation.
Don't think that. We'll find him.
We'll find him. He's
gotta be somewhere.
My dad, Mr. Robot,
whatever the hell he is,
if he's not gonna show
up, maybe he got sloppy,
left behind a clue.
_
All right, come out!
Come out now!
Come on!
I need to know what happened!
Come on out!
I'm here!
I'm waiting for you!
Come on, man.
Come out!
Okay, we have to go analog for this.
We need to get these fliers out now
since we can't be sure anyone's
Internet access will work.
What? I'm thinking ahead.
First banking, then infrastructure.
We've been through this.
Now, take these fliers, pass them out.
It's the last step and then we're clear.
You guys are acting like we're
walking towards doomsday here.
Well, it does say here
it's an end of the world party.
Figure of speech.
You wonder why we're
not in high spirits?
Maybe it's because our fearless leader goes
and shoots up the world
and then disappears,
yet again, while we're
here cleaning up after him.
_
He knows the password,
which means I know the password.
_
What's he trying to say?
I'm on the hook for everything?
He won't come out to play if I ask.
So maybe I gotta force his hand.
I need to use a landline.
I need to get myself arrested.
- 911. What's your emergency?
- I have a confession to make.
All right, you got me.
I'm afraid to ask.
Now, wait a minute, you said you work...
Was this from the guy?
The one they're talking about on the news?
Um... yes.
You mean to tell me you
witnessed this thing...
and you're here to buy new shoes?
Wow.
That's pretty...
It's just pretty cold.
How can you work there?
That guy said it himself,
they're just liars.
I know. They are.
But I'm not sure
that he knew what he was saying.
Oh, you sound just like them.
Have some moral fiber
and leave their asses.
Their practices are well-documented
and it's all despicable.
Listen, this isn't my business,
but don't drink their Kool-Aid.
Look, I just needed a job.
What kind of an excuse is that?
- You don't understand.
- You should hear yourself.
I don't know who you
think you're talking to,
but I'll try the Pradas next.
Calm down.
Get your caramel latte. It's on me.
- Where is he?
- You know how this looks, right?
Very weird.
I don't give a shit.
- Where's Tyrell?
- We made a deal that helped us both.
Tell me where he is!
You're starting to attract some attention.
I recommend you get one of
those Bluetooth headsets.
That way people just think
you're the local douche.
Tyrell disappeared.
No one knows where he is.
But you know.
So do you.
You forget, kiddo, I am you.
- No, you're not.
- Is that a fact?
Hey, man, I gotta tell you I had
sex with your mom this morning,
and it was fantastic.
Don't have time for you, little man.
Your mom was real nice. Smell.
God! What did you do to him?
What did I do?
Well, did you just see what he did?
- No, I don't know, man.
- Yeah, he flicked my nose.
You're losing it, kiddo.
I'm only supposed to be your prophet.
You're supposed to be my god.
Come on!
The dramatic repercussions of
the recent financial meltdown
are not relegated to
developing nations.
The United States has also
witnessed a disruption
of order and peace.
While businesses determine how
or whether they will function
through the uncertainty,
individuals have taken
to the streets, giving the
major cities a tenor...
Ooh.
Very nice.
I'm glad you reconsidered.
What? What is it?
Come on.
You have questions.
I'm a person with a lot of answers,
especially right now.
Okay.
It's just that...
well, I can't help but wonder,
why do you seem so confident?
Everyone else is worried, but you?
You're sure that you're
gonna get through this.
- Why?
- Hmm.
- People did this. Right?
- _
I mean, aliens didn't
invade our planet.
Zeus didn't come out of
the heavens to destroy us.
Zombies haven't risen from the dead.
No.
Whoever's behind this,
they're just people...
like you and me.
Except, of course, I have the full weight
of the biggest conglomerate
in the world behind me.
You'll come to realize
that when you have that,
matters like this, they tend to crack...
under that weight.
Can I ask another question?
All right, go.
Why me?
Why am I really here?
I know you know who I am.
Why are you letting me be here?
Why are you even talking to me right now?
None of this makes any sense.
Well, be that as it may, I...
I find you refreshing.
You're young, bold,
exactly what we need right now.
- Come on.
- What?
There has to be more to it than that.
Angela, just a word of advice.
Don't talk your way out of a compliment.
Excuse me. They'll be ready.
Shall we?
Oh, you're still thinking
about this morning.
I don't think I'll ever get
that image out of my head.
Between you and me, I was
glad he killed himself.
He was not a very good person.
He had a gambling problem.
He drank too much.
Most notably, he was weak.
His instincts left a lot to be desired.
Oh, I despise people like that.
In fact, I felt...
the world was a little better off
knowing he wasn't in it anymore.
Oh, I believe even his
family will benefit from this
in the long run.
Before we even begin,
let's have a moment of silence
for our dear, brave friend,
James Plouffe.
Well, this place is a petri dish now.
Yeah, I'd say we got enough
fingerprints everywhere.
So that's it then, right?
That's it?
How about, "That's amazing"?
How about we party
and thank ourselves for
all the hard work we did?
Yeah, I don't think Trenton
was talking about tonight.
- Well, what then?
- Well, you know,
I think she's saying after tonight, right?
Then what? I mean, what do we all do now?
Guys, this isn't about
what we'll do tomorrow!
This is about what we did.
I mean, look at all these people.
They're free because of us,
because of what we did in this room.
We're finally awake!
We are finally alive.
- Our streets!
- Whose streets?
Our streets!
- Our streets!
- Whose streets?
- I know you killed him.
- Our streets!
I know you did it. I know you did it.
Just tell me what happened to Tyrell.
- Our streets!
- Shut up!
I have played nice for far too long.
I'm so sick of your whining.
It's not gonna change anything anyway.
Please, you have to do something.
You have to help me.
- Say something. Make him tell me.
- Stop talking to them!
They can't help us.
We have to do this together, just us.
He's right, you know.
You're hurting the
whole family, Elliot.
No, no, this isn't my family.
None of them are real.
Neither is whoever you're talking to.
Then you're not real.
You're not real.
What? You are?
Is any of it real?
I mean, look at this. Look at it!
A world built on fantasy!
Synthetic emotions in the form of pills,
psychological warfare in
the form of advertising,
mind-altering chemicals
in the form of food,
brainwashing seminars in the form of media,
controlled isolated bubbles
in the form of social networks.
Real? You want to talk about reality?
We haven't lived in
anything remotely close to it
since the turn of the century.
We turned it off, took out the batteries,
snacked on a bag of GMOs
while we tossed the remnants
in the ever-expanding dumpster
of the human condition.
We live in branded houses
trademarked by corporations
built on bipolar numbers
jumping up and down on digital displays,
hypnotizing us into the biggest
slumber mankind has ever seen.
You have to dig pretty deep, kiddo,
before you can find anything real.
We live in a kingdom of bullshit,
a kingdom you've lived in for far too long.
So don't tell me about not being real.
I'm no less real than
the fucking beef patty
in your...
As far as you're concerned, Elliot,
I am very real.
We are all together now,
whether you like it or not.
No! No!
No!
I want to be alone.
I need to be alone.
No, you don't want that, remember?
Remember how you felt
when you were alone?
You were in pain.
You were miserable.
That's why we're here.
Those lonely nights
when you sat and cried
in your apartment, you
begged us to help you.
You asked us to come.
You needed us to come.
No!
I want you to leave!
Leave!
We're deep down inside you, Elliot.
You can't leave us,
and we can't leave you.
Ever.
It's true, Son.
I don't know what I'm supposed to do.
I'll tell you exactly
what you're gonna do.
You're gonna start listening to us.
The world is a better place
because of what we did, Elliot,
and you're gonna realize
that one way or another.
Now, here's what I
need you to do now.
You're going to walk to the subway.
You're going to get on your train.
You're going to get
off at your stop.
Woohoo-hoo-hoo!
You're going to go home.
You're gonna sit at your computer,
watch and enjoy the
beautiful carnage
that we've all created together.
We hope a new society
rises from the ashes,
that you will forge a better world.
- Well, enjoy the evening.
- Thank you.
- How are you?
- Good evening.
- Good to see you.
- Thank you.
Go ahead. What's on your mind?
I know you're not without your troubles,
but we still haven't
discussed the coltan mines.
You're really bringing
that up at a time like this?
You asked, I answered, succinctly.
Well, perhaps I was too hasty.
I'd like, for the moment,
to take in the music.
Besides... plenty of
other items on our agenda.
The fucking Congo can wait.
Oh, your troubles are
weighing heavily on you.
I'm not entirely sure why.
I was told that you know
the person responsible.
Yes. Yes.
Of course we do.
And we will handle that person
as we usually do.
- You seem a little preoccupied yourself.
- I don't believe in preoccupation.
It's more of an observation.
- Which is?
- The infamous Emperor Nero
played an instrument very similar
to the one she's playing, the lyre.
Legend has it that he played it merrily
as he watched...
- As he watched?
- As he watched Rome burn.
- Synced and corrected by skoad -
www.addic7ed.com