Hello, friend.
"Hello, friend."
That's lame.
Maybe I should give you a name,
but that's a slippery slope.
You're only in my head.
We have to remember that.
Shit.
It's actually happened,
I'm talking to
an imaginary person.
What I'm about to tell you
is top secret,
a conspiracy
bigger than all of us.
There's a powerful group
of people out there
that are secretly running
the world.
I'm talking about the guys
no one knows about,
the guys that are invisible.
The top 1% of the top 1%,
the guys that play God
without permission.
And now I think
they're following me.
This is about last night.
I should've gone
to Angela's birthday party.
Instead, I went to--
Hey, Ron.
There you go.
You're Ron.
But your real name
is Rohit Mehta.
You changed it to Ron
when you bought
your first Ron's Coffee Shop
six years ago.
Now you got 17 of 'em
with 8 more coming next quarter.
May I help you
with something?
I like coming here
'cause your Wi-Fi was fast.
I mean, you're one
of the few spots
that has a fiber connection
with gigabit speed.
It's good.
So good, it scratched
that part of my mind, part
that doesn't allow good to exist
without condition,
so I started intercepting
all the traffic
on your network.
That's when I noticed
something strange.
It's when I decided
to hack you.
- Hack--
- I know you run a website
- called Plato's Boys.
- Pardon me?
You're using Tor networking
to keep the servers anonymous.
You made it really hard
for anyone to see it,
but I saw it.
The onion routing protocol,
it's not as anonymous
as you think it is.
Whoever's in control
of the exit nodes
is also in control
of the traffic,
which makes me...
the one in control.
I must ask you to kindly leave.
I own everything.
All your emails.
All your files.
All your...pics.
Get out of here right now,
or I'll call the--
Police? You want them
to find out
about the 100 terabytes
of child pornography
you serve to
your 400,000 users?
Personally, man, I was
hoping it was just gonna be
some BDSM stuff.
You realize how much simpler
that would have been?
I did not hurt anyone.
I never did.
That's my...
personal life.
I understand what it's like
to be different.
I'm very different too.
I mean, I don't jerk off
to little kids, but...
I don't know how
to talk to people.
My dad was the only one
I could talk to.
But he died.
I'm sorry to hear that.
How did he pass,
may I ask?
Leukemia.
He definitely got it
from radiation
at the company
he worked at,
though I couldn't
prove it.
Now he's dead.
Company's fine, though.
Oh...hey.
It's okay, Rohit.
You don't have to
worry anymore.
I don't understand.
Are you blackmailing me?
So that's what
this is about...
money.
That's all you care
about, huh?
No.
If I pay you now,
you'll want more and more.
No matter how much
I give.
You will inform
the police anyway.
I won't pay you, sir.
Remember,
you also broke the law.
Actually, you're right.
Partly.
See, I usually do
this kind of thing
from my computer,
but this time I wanted
to do it AFK.
In person.
Trying to work on
my social anxiety.
But there's always
the threat of you fleeing
after I call you out.
You'd tell your sys admin
to take your servers down,
wipe all the data.
So I made sure to include
the current time
and--and location
on my anonymous tip.
Wait. Hold on.
I'll give you the money.
I'll pay you.
How much do you want?
That's the part you were
wrong about, Rohit.
I don't give a shit
about money.
Now I'm being followed.
The higher ups don't like
someone with my powers.
In three short minutes,
I destroyed a man's business,
life, existence.
- I deleted him.
- Hey!
Hey, you.
Hey, kiddo.
What's happening?
Exciting time
in the world right now.
Exciting time.
But I'm only a vigilante
hacker by night.
By day, just a regular
cyber security engineer,
employee number ER28-0652.
Elliot!
In here.
- What's up?
- El.
Yeah, I can totally--
I can totally handle it.
They were hacked again.
Last night.
Gideon...
That's my childhood friend Angela.
She can be a bit
high strung sometimes,
but trust me--
she's one of the good ones.
What am I looking at?
Is this the log file?
This was a RUDY attack.
This is awesome.
- Gideon, will you answer me?
- Awesome?
You think this is awesome?
This is killing us, Elliot.
- Gideon, I'm not--
- Angela!
Let's just see how
this meeting goes today.
Their networks are getting
attacked every week.
Who knows if they'll still
even be a client.
They're coming in?
Hey, what did we say
about the dress code?
All right, now,
look over those logs.
And be ready this afternoon
in case they have any questions.
Okay?
Okay.
- Start smoking again?
- Did you not get
my texts last night?
I sent you exactly
13 of them.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I couldn't make it.
You promised me that you were
gonna try this time.
Stop thinking about something else
when I'm talking to you.
I hate when you do that.
Sorry. I was thinking
about work.
Maybe that's why Gideon
loves you so much.
He thanks me all the time
for bringing you in.
But for some reason,
I think you secretly
hate it here.
She was right.
I liked most of the people,
but our business,
a cyber security firm
that protects corporations--
I can't think of anything
I hate more.
No, I love it here.
I'm sorry.
I'm just in a bad mood.
I'm late on my last
two student loan payments,
and I can't get Gideon
to give me a raise.
- Hey...
- Hi.
Yo, buddy.
Missed you last night.
Where were you?
Gotta go.
Big meeting today.
Did you find out
what happened?
Yeah. He said
he was working.
Oh, come on.
You gotta talk to him.
We're gonna be late
for the staff meeting.
He can't stand me.
And you know why.
Angela, I can't have
that kind of negativity
in my life.
That's exactly
what I'm talking about.
What are you thinking about?
Nothing.
You want to know
what I'm thinking about?
First time
you came to me.
I didn't exactly
come to Krista.
I was forced here.
But I do like her.
Hacking her was simple.
Her password: Dylan 2791.
Favorite artist and the year in
which she was born, backwards.
Though she's a psychologist,
she's really bad
at reading people.
But I'm good at reading people.
My secret: I look for
the worst in them.
I know she went through
a divorce four years ago.
I know she was
devastated by it
and has been dating losers
on eHarmony ever since.
Her most recent foray--
Michael Hansen.
I searched for him online,
but nothing came up.
No LinkedIn, no Facebook,
nothing.
Something about him bugs me,
scratching that part
of my mind again.
But I'll hack him soon enough.
I always do.
I know you're not
yelling like before,
which is good.
But I can tell you're
still holding on to it.
And we need to work on
your anger issues, Elliot.
You're angry at everyone,
at society...
Fuck society.
I know you have a lot
to be angry about,
but keeping it to yourself
and staying quiet
like you're doing--
it's not going to
help you.
There's pain underneath.
That's where our work
needs to go.
What is it about society
that disappoints you so much?
Oh, I don't know.
Is it that we collectively
thought Steve Jobs
was a great man,
even when we knew
he made billions off the backs
of children?
Or maybe it's that it feels
like all our heroes
are counterfeit.
The world itself's
just one big hoax.
Spamming each other
with our running commentary
of bullshit
masquerading as insight,
our social media
faking as intimacy.
Or is it that we voted
for this?
Not with our rigged
elections,
but with our things,
our property, our money.
I'm not saying
anything new.
We all know why
we do this,
not because Hunger Games
books makes us happy
but because
we wanna be sedated.
Because it's painful
not to pretend,
because we're cowards.
Fuck society.
Elliot.
You're not saying
anything.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Don't be frustrated.
Why shouldn't I be?
You're different
than most.
You at least try.
You at least
understand.
Understand what?
What it's like
to feel alone.
You understand the pain.
You want to protect
people from it.
You want to protect me
from it.
I respect that
about you.
Why do you think
I know
what it's like
to feel alone?
Shit! From her emails!
Elliot?
I don't know.
Let's talk about
last night.
Did you go to Angela's
birthday party?
Yeah. It was nice.
Did you try to talk
to anyone?
Sure.
I got a girl's number.
- You did?
- [chuckles]
She's cute.
She likes
The Hunger Games.
You're hiding again,
Elliot.
When you hide,
your delusions come back.
It's a slippery slope.
Let's talk about the men
in black you've been seeing.
Are they still there?
No, I...
told you they're gone.
The meds you gave me
are working.
Yo, man.
Do you wanna, uh...
you wanna do lunch
today?
Uh, yeah...
- I got other plans.
- Other plans. Right.
That's...what you said the last
three times I asked you.
Look, bud, you...
and Angela
have been close
for a long time,
and that's even more reason
why I want us to be
on good terms.
I-I just--I feel like
things have been
awkward between us.
Don't you?
I'm okay with it
being awkward between us.
Um, yeah.
I-I'm--I'm not
okay with that.
Um...look, man,
I love Angela,
and I want us to--
to get along for her sake.
I mean, that's what I'm--
that's what I'm here for.
I just, I...
I don't normally do stuff...
Am I crazy not to like this guy?
Among some of
his Facebook likes
are George W. Bush's
Decision Points,
Transformers 2:
Revenge of the Fallen,
and the music of Josh Groban.
Must I really justify myself
any further?
I'm working on
that shit, you know?
His was the easiest to hack.
Password was 123456Seven.
I witnessed his first
"I love you" with Angela
over Gchat,
then I witnessed the first
of many infidelities
with Stella B.
I've never done
anything like this before...
I've thought about
telling Angela,
but she has shitty taste
in men,
and I'm not quite ready
to see what comes after this
just yet.
You like music.
I like music.
Maroon 5.
Plus I can manage Ollie
easier than the others.
for now, anyway.
And that's all I mean.
[sighs]
I just want you
to know that.
I like you, bro,
and...
I want you
to like me too.
I understand.
I'll try harder.
That's cool, man.
Hey, whenever you're
ready, I'd love to just...
chill.
Oh--forgot about your...
no touching thing.
Truth is, I shouldn't hate
Ollie; he's not that bad a guy.
He's too dumb to be bad.
In fact, when I think about
the really bad people...
E Corp, the largest
conglomerate in the world...
they're so big,
they're literally everywhere.
A perfect monster
of modern society.
The E might as well
stand for Evil.
And all of life's necessities...
In fact, after a thorough,
intensive self-reprogramming,
that's all my mind hears,
sees, or reads
when they pop up
in my world.
That was have to offer.
Together, we can change the world,
with E... Evil Corp.
Krista would have a shit fit
if she knew I did that.
But that's what they are--
a conglomerate of evil.
And now I have to help them.
There are six on-site engineers
on your account.
- Plus a few off-site...
- There he is, Terry Colby,
the CTO.
Even though he's the head
technology guy
at one of the biggest
companies in the world,
he owns a Blackberry.
So this is it
right here.
But also looks like he doesn't
see a terminal very often
He's not a techie.
He's a moron.
An arrogant moron.
The worst kind.
Oh, hi.
Tyrell Wellick.
I'm Senior Vice President,
Technology.
Elliot. Just a tech.
Don't be so humble.
You know, I started out
exactly where you are,
and...to be honest,
you know,
my heart is still
there.
So I see you're
running Gnome.
You know, I'm actually
on KDE myself.
I know this desktop
environment
is supposed to be better
but...
you know what
they say.
Old habits--
they die hard.
An executive running Linux
with--
Yeah, I know what
you're thinking.
I'm an executive.
I mean...
why am I even running
Linux?
Again--old habits.
It's gonna be fun
working with you.
I should join
the rest of the group.
Bon soir, Elliot.
Sometimes I dream
of saving the world.
Saving everyone
from the invisible hand,
one that brands us
with an employee badge.
The one that forces us
to work for them...
The one that controls us
every day without us knowing it.
But I can't stop it.
I'm not that special.
I'm just anonymous.
I'm just alone.
If it weren't for Qwerty,
I'd be completely empty.
I hate when I can't hold in
my loneliness.
This crying has been
happening too often,
every other week now.
What do normal people do
when they get this sad?
They reach out
to friends or family, I think.
That's not an option.
I do morphine.
The key to doing morphine
without turning into a junkie
is to limit yourself
to 30 milligrams a day.
Anything more
just builds up your tolerance.
I check every pill I get
for purity.
I have 8 milligram Suboxone
for maintenance
in case I go through
withdrawals.
Shit!
I'm out again.
How much?
On the house.
No, Shayla.
Not doing that.
Okay? This is just
a regular drug deal
- like it always is.
- Fine.
So what are you
you to tonight?
'Cause I tried to post
something on your Facebook
and couldn't find you.
I'm not on Facebook.
What? Why not?
'Cause I hate Facebook.
That's crazy.
Well...you want to
do these together then?
Pure Molly...
Don't ever make decisions
when you're on morphine.
Instagram check-in
for Krista at Pierre Loti.
Okay, Michael Hansen.
Time to find out
who you really are.
- Thank you. Bye.
- Bye.
Taxi!
Uh, hi--I just left
my keys in one of your cabs.
56Y2.
Sure.
What about you two?
Huh?
You guys got any
spare change?
Help me out?
New York's expensive, guys.
Come on.
306 Hawthorne.
Thank you.
Come on, asshole
Piss already.
- Come on!
Come on!
Will you--will you go?
- Come on, go, go!
- Hey!
Go, will ya?
Hey.
May I borrow your phone?
Mine's dead.
I need to call my mom.
Thank you.
No answer.
Thanks anyway.
Angela,
is everything okay?
I need you to come
to AllSafe.
You're there?
It's 3:00 in the morning.
They attacked Evil Corp
servers again,
but it's bad this time.
It's a DDoS attack.
Did you call Lloyd?
He's on call.
Yeah, he's here.
Is he talking to
their tech department?
He's online with them,
but so far nothing.
I don't think that
Lloyd can handle this.
Look, Gideon just put me
on this account.
I can't screw up
in my first week.
I need you.
Please.
I'll be right there.
Finally!
Calm down--it's only
been an hour.
Yeah, well, an hour
in Evil Corp time
is like $13 million
in revenue, approximately.
Actually,
I calculated that.
That's exactly
how much they lost.
Don't worry.
I got you.
Lloyd, what's up?
- Lloyd!
Elliot. This is bad.
Worst DDoS attack
I've ever seen.
- Did you reconfigure the DNS?
- Yes!
- Stop the services.
- I already stopped
the services,
tries to reboot the servers
but they're not
coming back up.
Dude, someone is straight up
fingerblasting
their entire network
right now.
They just started
reporting on the outage.
Shit. This is worse
than I thought.
They're in the network?
What's the status update?
I thought we set up
security protocols
so that this doesn't happen.
Where's the attack coming from?
Everywhere, obviously.
The USA, Finland,
Thailand, Kuwait--
Start restarting the services,
load sharing,
redirect the traffic.
Call Prolexic for help.
What?
I don't think this
is just a DDoS attack.
I think they got a rootkit
sitting inside the servers.
What's a rootkit?
It's like a crazy serial
rapist with a very big dick.
- Jesus, Lloyd.
- Sorry. It's malicious code
that completely
takes over their system.
It can delete system files
and stop programs.
- Viruses, worms--
- How do we stop it?
That's the thing.
It's fundamentally
invisible--you can't stop it.
All of their servers
are timing out.
None of them
are coming back up.
That's because
every time we restart the server
the virus replicates itself
during boot up
and crashes the host.
How are we supposed to
bring up the network
if we can't
restart the servers?
We can't.
Which is what they wanted.
By defending ourselves,
we ended up spreading
the virus everywhere.
Only thing we can do
is we've gotta take
the whole system offline,
wipe the infected servers
clean,
then bring them back up.
You're coming with me.
- Yeah.
- Lloyd.
Tell everybody to start
taking everything offline.
- On it.
- Uh, the server farm in Dulles.
We're gonna need the jet.
They're booting
the network back up.
Now, you're downloading
the logs, right--
- Stop. Tell him to stop.
- What?
Don't start the boot sequence.
You guys missed one.
There's an infected server
up and running.
What's the ETA
before it hits this server?
The backup server
up and running?
It's ready, but it's not
configured for auto switch.
We need to redirect
the traffic,
need to switch DNS.
You got this, you got this,
you got this.
This is impossible.
You got this,
you got this, you got this.
It's almost at the back server!
We still up?
We're okay.
Yeah.
Hank.
I'm gonna take a look
at the infected server, okay?
Give me a minute.
Yeah. Uh...I'll meet you
at the elevators.
They must have left
a mark or something.
Every hacker loves attention.
They don't just do DDoS
attacks for no reason.
This is it.
Fsociety.
Is that supposed to be
a joke?
This was way too easy.
They didn't hide it well at all.
This note is for me.
They're telling me
to leave it here.
But why?
Doesn't matter.
Time to shut them down.
Why can't I delete it?
I don't want to delete it.
I want it to stay.
What's wrong with me?
I'll reconfigure the access
to the root directory
so only I can use it.
And no one will know.
For you, sir.
Did you know
that I'm gay?
Uh...
No.
Hmm.
Consider this me coming out
to you then, okay?
It's hard because I don't like
to talk about my sex life.
But my partner,
he gets very paranoid.
He thinks I'm ashamed of--
He wants me to be
more public about it, so,
Anyway, I'm gay.
Thanks.
Yeah.
Hey, man,
don't worry about it.
Hackers have a short
attention span.
They'll get bored,
harass someone else.
Evil Corp is thinking
about leaving us.
And I don't know
if I can blame them.
They could have called
their other security teams.
- Mm.
- They called you.
Well, somebody over there
likes us,
but Terry Colby,
he's getting the pressure.
and he calls the shots.
Evil Corp is 80%
of our business.
If we lose them,
it's gonna be it for us.
It's gonna be it...
For me.
I feel like
I can talk to you.
I mean, more than
the others, anyway.
I'm sure,
in a weird way,
you'll be happy
if we went under.
Oh, come on.
Come on.
I know you hate
wearing those stupid shirts.
Gideon?
I promise I'll find them.
Evil Corp service should be
back up soon enough.
I'll take a look
at the dat file.
I'll ask my IRC contacts
about fsociety when I get home.
I've never seen their name
on the boards though.
They've gotta be new,
but they're good.
Rough night?
I'm getting off here.
I think you should
come with me.
But only if
you didn't delete it.
You deleted it,
we got nothing to talk about.
Are you talking to me?
Stand clear of
the closing doors, please.
Who are you?
We gotta wait for the Q.
Then what?
Then we're going
to Brooklyn.
Out by Coney Island.
Why?
What's there?
Obviously you're gonna ask
a lot of questions.
It's weird what you're doing
right now, I get it.
I-I can't tell you
anything
until we get there.
Can't smoke in here.
You've been
following me.
Why?
What do you want
from me?
My dad was a petty thief.
Never could hold down
a job.
So, he just robbed,
convenience stores,
shops,
small-time stuff.
One time,
he sat me down,
he told me something
I never forgot.
He said, "Everyone steals."
"That's how it works."
"You think people out there
are getting exactly
what they deserve?
No.
They're getting paid
over or under,
but someone in the chain
always gets bamboozled."
"I steal, Son,
but I don't get caught."
"That's my contract
with society."
"Now if you can catch me
stealing, I'll go to jail."
"But if you can't,
then I've earned the money."
I respected that, man.
I thought that shit
was cool
as a little kid.
A few years after that,
they finally caught him.
Sent him to jail.
Dies five years later.
My respect goes with him.
I thought he was free
doing what he did,
but he wasn't.
He was in prison.
Just like you are now,
Elliot.
But I'm gonna
break you out.
Why would you guys
actually meet IRL?
You remember that
hacker group O-Megz?
They got outed
by their own leader to the FBI,
and six hackers
went to prison for it?
You know how
they got 'em?
They went on
the dude's computer,
tracked 'em all down
through emails,
VPN sessions,
chat messages, texts.
One guy, and the whole thing
comes down.
- It's what's called--
- A central point of failure.
Right.
Because they refused
to meet in person,
they compromised each other
every time
they sent so much
as a smiley face.
The rule here is,
it's done here,
and only here.
It ends when you walk out
that door,
and begins when
you walk in.
Our encryption
is the real world.
How do you talk
to each other then?
We don't.
We come and go,
work on the project when we can.
How do you trust them?
I give them an exercise.
If they pass, they join us.
If they fail--
The DDoS attack last night,
you were testing me.
You said there was
a project.
What's the project?
That'll come later.
I just wanted you
to see the place.
There's not much you can
do without a CPU.
I'm crazy.
I have to be crazy because
that didn't just happen, right?
This is a delusion.
Is this a delusion?
Shit, I'm a schizo.
Have I really lost it
this time?
No, no. Last night happened.
It was real.
Angela called me.
I was at AllSafe.
Evil Corp's servers
were compromised.
Those are facts,
not delusions.
I know. I know, I know
I realize I'm saying all of this
to an imaginary person,
but I created you.
I didn't create this.
Oh, thank God you're here.
I was just about to go
wait in the Starbucks.
You live in a bad neighborhood.
Do you know that?
I do know that.
Do you want to
get high and
watch your favorite movie?
Oh, you saved our asses
last night.
I thought Gideon was
definitely gonna fire me.
Where have you been?
I thought you'd
be sleeping.
I--yeah, I fell asleep
on the train.
That sounds like such a lie,
but, whatever.
I don't want
to get into that right now.
So you want to
do this?
I miss Qwerty.
I hope she still loves me.
Shit.
She wasn't supposed
to be here, okay?
Give me a minute
and I'll get rid of her.
That's okay.
Um...
This is great.
Elliot, I'm happy
for you.
No, it's not like that.
Well, maybe it should be,
you know?
It's good that you're...
dating.
Well, I'll see you
on Monday.
We can do movie night
next time.
I promise, okay?
Yeah.
Have fun.
Mm, Elliot?
Oh, shit.
Is it Wednesday?
- Shayla.
- I have to move my car.
Shayla, leave.
Now.
No mention of Mr. Robot
anywhere.
No mention of fsociety.
Not on any of
the hacker boards.
Not on IRC, forums, blogs,
no one's heard of them.
Property was owned by
Fun Society Amusement, LLC
for 13 years.
Owner was shot a killed
a year and a half ago.
No owner since.
And the ownership history
before that
is sparse to nonexistent.
This guy is good.
Very good.
Doesn't matter.
Their arcade network's IP
is in the dat file.
That'll be enough
to turn them in.
What's your ask, Mr. Robot?
Hey, man,
where's your boss?
Okay, cut the bullshit.
When are you going to give us
access to the root directory?
What?
Dude, come on.
I wrote that rootkit.
I still have to put
Colby's IP in the dat file.
Dickhead.
Elliot!
Good news.
I scored the last bag
of Twinkies from Gristedes.
You want one?
She just called me
a dickhead.
Yeah, that's Darlene.
Hey, you like
Ferris wheels?
Ah, it's beautiful.
Gets better the higher up
you go, you know?
Oh, I love it up here.
You like it?
I'm here to tell you
I'm turning you in.
I'm giving them
all the information.
Let me tell you why
you're really here.
You're here because you sense
something wrong with the world.
Something
you can't explain.
But you know it controls you
and everyone you care about.
What are you talking about?
Money.
Money hasn't been real since we
got off the gold standard.
It's become virtual.
Software.
The operating system
of our world.
And, Elliot,
we are on the verge
of taking down
this virtual reality.
Think about it.
What if you could take down
one conglomerate?
A conglomerate
so deeply entrenched
in the world's economy,
that too big to fail
doesn't even come close
to describing it.
You want to create
another financial meltdown
like the one we just had,
but way worse.
Yeah, why would
I want that?
Everyone would lose
their money.
What if I told you
that this conglomerate
just so happens to own
70% of the global
consumer credit industry?
Huh?
If we hit their data center
just right,
we could systematically format
all the servers,
- including backup.
- That would erase all--
All the debt we owe them.
Every record of every
credit card, loan, and mortgage
would be wiped clean.
It would be impossible
to reinforce
outdated paper records.
It would all be gone.
The single biggest incident
of wealth redistribution
in history.
Evil Corp.
The conglomerate.
That's why you
picked me.
Because I work
at AllSafe.
Tomorrow, AllSafe is going to
get a visit
from the FBI
and the U.S. Cyber Command.
You are going to modify
the dat file
and put Colby's
terminal IP address in there.
Terry Colby?
You're gonna frame him?
No one's gonna believe that.
I met him, he's a moron.
So are the FBI.
Even if they don't believe
he did it,
they'll believe
he gave someone access to it.
Yeah, he'll just go to jail.
What good will that do?
You don't take down
a conglomerate
by shooting them
in the heart.
That's the thing
about conglomerates,
they don't have hearts.
You take them down
limb by limb.
And as they unravel,
their illusion
of control unravels.
Who are you?
That'll come later.
Right now, you have a lot
to think about.
You have to change
the dat file
and put Colby's IP
in there.
You do that,
you have set in motion
the largest revolution
the world will ever see.
¶ If you go away ¶
¶ On this summer day ¶
¶ Then you might as well
take the sun away ¶
¶ All the birds that flew ¶
¶ In a summer sky ¶
¶ When our love was new ¶
¶ And our hearts were high ¶
¶ When the day was young ¶
¶ And the night was long ¶
¶ And the moon stood still ¶
¶ For the night birds song ¶
¶ If you go away ¶
¶ But if you stay ¶
¶ I'll make you a day ¶
¶ Like no day's been ¶
¶ Or will be again ¶
¶ We'll sail on the sun ¶
¶ We'll ride on the rain ¶
¶ We'll talk to the trees ¶
¶ And worship the wind ¶
¶ Then if you go ¶
¶ I'll understand ¶
¶ Leave me just enough love ¶
¶ To fill up my hand ¶
¶ If you go away ¶
¶ As I know you must ¶
¶ There'll be nothing left ¶
¶ In the world to trust ¶
¶ Just an empty room ¶
¶ Full of empty space ¶
¶ Like the empty look ¶
¶ I see on your face ¶
¶ Can I tell you now ¶
¶ As you turn to go ¶
¶ I'll be dying slowly ¶
¶ Till your next hello ¶
¶ If you go away ¶
So, what do we got?
So, if you'll take a look
at the first page
of your agenda--
You're the one
who stopped the hack.
You know, the gals in analysis
said this was a tough one.
All things being equal,
it should have shut us down
for days, so...
you did good.
Okay.
We should start with
our account executive, Angela.
Okay, we first noticed
the breach
at 2:07 A.M. Eastern Standard
on Friday night.
You mean, Saturday?
Sorry, yes,
technically, Saturday morning.
Yeah, okay, Angela,
that's what we're here for.
The technicals.
Right.
Yes.
Anyway, he arrived at the office
at 2:35 and I instru--
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
So that's almost a half hour
after the initial breach.
Why didn't anyone pipe in
from their laptops?
- It's not protocol--
- It wouldn't have been secure
if someone terminaled in
on this.
It was the smarter move
to have someone come in
so they can log in
on a secure line.
Exactly.
Then Lloyd was able to--
Just--just actually,
just one second.
- Yeah.
You know, I, uh,
I always loved
this view.
Now that that's taken care of,
let's pick it up
where we left off.
What happened to Angela?
She knows more
about what happened.
She's not going to work out
for us, not on this level.
We need to stick
to the more tech savvy here.
Now, let's get to the heart
of this thing
because I can't sit here
and look through a packet
for the next 20 minutes.
All right, just who did this?
Is it that hard?
Who did this?
I found the configuration file
of the rootkit
with a pattern
of IP addresses.
Once you decrypt it, you'll know
where the hack came from.
19 days.
No news, no arrests,
no revolution.
No FBI, Colby, Evil Corp.
No Mr. Robot.
No fsociety.
I need to take
my mind off things.
Hello.
Hi, this is Sam from Bank of E
security fraud department.
Unfortunately
I have to inform you
that your account's
been compromised.
What? What happened?
First before I can
answer any questions,
I need to verify
some information.
Are you still at
306 Hawthorne Avenue?
Yes. Apartment 2C.
Great.
And your security question,
favorite baseball team?
Um, Yankees.
I don't remember this
being a security question.
And lastly, your pet's name?
Um, Flipper.
Who am I speaking to?
Can I get your name and number?
With those details plus
a dictionary brute-force attack,
it'll take my program maybe two
minutes to crack his password.
What I wouldn't give
to be normal.
To live in that bubble,
the reality of the naive.
That's how I justify this.
To keep their optimism intact.
To protect them.
How? He's too old
to have a complicated password.
It had to have been
a combination of these things.
I'm missing something,
I'm missing something.
Michael Hansen
isn't his real name.
Come on.
Get over here.
Lenny Shannon?
Michael Hansen?
Which one are you
playing tonight?
You're going to stop
seeing Krista.
What the fuck
You're going to break up
with her.
You're never going
to see her again.
You're the guy
that used my phone.
You cheated on your current wife
with seven different women.
I got digital proof
of all of it.
Ashley Madison, online escorts,
fake Facebook pages.
I own it all.
And if you don't stop
seeing her,
your wife will know everything
along with the police.
The police?
Yeah, one of the escorts
was 15.
That 15 part I made up,
but he did have a proclivity
for young escorts
that helped the lie.
But I'm not gonna do
any of that
as long as you break up
with Krista.
Tonight.
Done.
You're also gonna
tell her the truth.
That you're married,
cheat on your wife,
you hire hookers.
That you never had any intention
of being serious with her.
Why?
That would destroy her.
She thinks that...
We're in love.
Exactly. Krista needs to avoid
dickheads like you
in the future.
Her radar needs fixing.
I'll know if you
skip any detail.
So don't.
And one more thing...
I'm gonna need
something from you.
Come on.
Hmm.
I like you, Flipper.
You're cool.
I never want to be right
about my hacks,
but people always find a way
to disappoint.
Michael Hansen now gets
filed away among the others.
Forever buried
in my digital cemetery.
The look of disillusionment.
He told her.
She cried all night.
Now comes the sadness.
I don't like
seeing her sad.
- You okay?
- Sorry.
Sorry.
Go on.
I think Angela blames me
for what happened
at the Evil Corp meeting.
What do I do?
I need to talk to her.
I think you just answered
your own question.
Talk to her.
She won't respond
to any of my texts or emails.
Then go to her
in person.
Tell her you need
to talk.
Communication is key,
Elliot.
Real human interaction.
That's what's important
for you right now.
Hey.
Do you--
- Do you think we can talk?
- What?
You won't talk to me.
You haven't talked to me
since the meeting.
I don't want to talk to you
because I feel embarrassed
every time I think
about what happened.
Okay?
It's fine.
I'll get over it.
- It's been three weeks.
- I have to get back to work.
You're just going to
ignore me?
You didn't have to
stick up for me in there.
I know that you were
just trying to help,
just don't do it again.
Even if I'm losing.
Let me lose, okay?
Don't look confused.
Just say it.
"Okay."
Okay.
Elliott.
FBI agents claim that Colby
either used hacking groups
or worked in conjunction
with them
to pressure Evil Corp during
his contract negotiations.
After a long and exhaustive
investigation,
sources close to the FBI
have confirmed the hacks were
in part tied
to Colby's terminal.
It's happening, it's happening,
it's happening, it's happening.
Sir, step inside
the car.
Sir.
Step inside
the vehicle now.
Go ahead.
Sir, go on in.
Bon soir, Elliot.
Please tell me
you're seeing this, too.