I will be the youngest executive
this company has ever seen.
All right, you know, I'll take
it if you leave us alone.
All right? Thank you.
Check track two out.
- I will, track two.
- All right, man.
Why didn't you tell me
about the DAT file?
Worked at Evil Corp
his whole life.
Then out of the blue, he got fired.
No one knew why.
He had leukemia. Made me
swear to never tell anyone.
Finally, I got so worried,
told my mom.
And when he found out,
he got pissed.
You ever
think you deserved it?
I was eight years old.
You didn't commit to the
sacred pact you had formed.
My approach
within our business units,
is to first invest in new
technologies and develop prototypes
in order to understand
the technology potential.
Because despite the recent success
of our cybersecurity team,
our company currently still has
seventy-two potential
hacker vulnerabilities
in our primary and second...
No, wait a second...
You stupid piece of shit.
Again.
Our company currently still has
73 potential hacker vulnerabilities
in our primary
and secondary data centers.
Now is not the time
to be encumbered
by the company's tragic and
shameful loss of our chief tech...
Too formal, God damn it!
Warm it up,
don't be a cold robot.
Again!
Now is not the time
to be encumbered by the company's
tragic and shameful loss
of our Chief Technology Officer.
We have to be swift
in naming a replacement CTO.
And, sir, I would like
to suggest it be me.
For the sake of our company
that we make our decision today.
My promotion...
My internal promotion shows not
only our confidence as a company,
but strength in our boldness
to the public.
Thank you for your time.
You will be the next CTO
of this company.
You will be the
next CTO of this company.
You will be
the next CTO of this company.
You sure you don't want
anything? Pellegrino? Tea?
Sir, thank you again
for seeing me.
Tyrell, I'm gonna have
to reschedule this.
- Anwar, set up another time.
- Sir, it's just that I think that...
I get it, I get it. We'll get another
meeting on the books right away.
We've got a really good
CTO candidate
the board is very excited about.
They're not ready
to discuss it yet.
We'll loop you in.
Just give us a couple
of weeks. Hmm?
Uh, put Wellick back
on the books. Two weeks.
Oh, nice tie.
Let me guess. Brioni?
Great taste, as always.
Be well.
I'll email
your assistant the details.
If you could,
just email it to me directly.
This is too important
for me to miss.
Ripped By mstoll
Happy New Year 2016 - New Year, New Color ;-)
Mr. Wellick, we're here.
Do you think I could have
300 this time?
Spoken like a true capitalist.
Bad day at the office?
No kicking...
Argh. Please.
Enough. No more.
Most coders think debugging
software is about fixing a mistake,
but that's bullshit.
Debugging's actually all about
finding the bug.
About understanding why the
bug was there to begin with.
About knowing that its
existence was no accident.
It came to you
to deliver a message,
like an unconscious bubble
floating to the surface,
popping with a revelation you've
secretly known all along.
I don't know
why I'm saying all of this.
Maybe it's because I'm pumped up on
whatever smack legal drug dealers
like Eli Lilly make
money off nowadays.
But usually it's because
there's a sense it's coming.
A bug buzzing its way towards me
to gum up the works until it
forces me to make a call.
"Kill me or embrace me."
Or maybe I'm just freaking out
because I never thought I'd wake up
to find these two women
staring back at me.
Are you awake?
I don't know.
What are you doing here?
We talked, maybe a few hours
ago when I first got here.
You don't remember?
They said I was your
emergency contact.
Um, all right. Um...
You told them to call
your psychiatrist.
You can't leave until
you talk to one.
So I'm gonna wait outside.
Hey.
Do you remember requesting me
from the staff?
You requested me because
the police said that...
I got jumped by a bunch of kids.
It's not the end of the world.
They wanted to do a full
drug panel and you refused.
May I ask why?
Elliot, if we can't have
a conversation about this...
I've been taking morphine.
Why?
I don't have a good enough
reason to give you.
I Wish I did, but I don't.
Maybe we should consider rehab.
I'm not a junkie.
Then you'll need
to prove it to me.
Submit to a bimonthly
drug test. Voluntarily.
That's the only way that
I'll recommend your release.
Hospitals, a heavily
networked one like this
are almost too easy to hack.
This is William Highsmith.
He's not only the head
of the IT department here,
he is the IT department.
He's also an idiot.
Not that I blame him because the
people that hire him are also idiots.
The poor guy only gets a budget
of about 7,000 bucks a year.
And he's supposed to protect their
network from people like me?
He never stood a chance.
He uses useless virus scans, dated
servers, and security software
that runs on Windows 98.
It's one of the reasons why I made
this place my primary care facility.
I can make my health records look like
every other obedient zombie out there.
Okay. You don't
have to worry.
I'm not going to do
morphine again.
That's a nice breakfast.
Sorry, credit card system
is down.
Like I said, the most
difficult thing about debugging
isn't fixing the bug,
it's all about finding the bug.
For Evil Corp, Mr. Robot
found that bug in me.
I was the mistake
that led to all of this.
I have to ask
you one thing.
Did you have something to do
with Vera getting busted?
Shit, Elliot.
You said you weren't
gonna do anything.
He's on murder charges,
do you know that?
His whole crew bounced.
I mean, I...
I don't know what I'm
gonna do for money now.
Just tell me, Elliot.
And don't lie.
Did you do something?
No.
Hmm.
Hey.
Are you okay?
- I mean with everything that
happened to... - I'm fine.
What happened to your door?
You're not supposed to be here.
Okay, I changed the locks
for a reason.
Mmm.
Interesting toy,
but you may want to spend a little more
scratch if you actually want it to,
you know, work.
Check it,
Jessica Alba says she wants
to join fsociety.
Jesus, what happened
to your face?
What's going on?
Well, I'm not
the princess of social graces,
but typically it goes
something like,
"Hi, this is Darlene..."
Stop.
You need to leave.
Babe, seriously, we have a lot of shit
to discuss, so if you wouldn't mind...
Get out.
I suggest you get a grip.
I mean, what was
she talking about?
I gotta get to work.
Work? Are you serious?
You can't go to work.
You have to call in sick.
I have to go.
A bug is never
just a mistake.
It represents something bigger.
An error of thinking...
Sir!
...that makes you who you are.
Sir! Sir!
Sir, you
dropped your wallet!
Thanks.
Sure.
Stop! Stop!
He stole my purse!
That was your wallet?
Yes, that was my wallet
you just gave him.
Stop!
He got
into my system.
And he wants me to put the CD on
one of the computers at work.
Why does he wanna do that?
I don't know, Stella,
he didn't give me
a full explanation.
So, he's got naked pics of me?
Is that the only thing you're seriously
taking away from this conversation?
Hey, babe.
Hey.
How was your run?
Strange.
Someone dropped their wallet.
And I picked it up to give
it to them, but then this...
Nothing strange about that, just
shows how good of a person you are.
Always have been. Almost to a fault.
What does that mean?
Just that you...
You're too good for the world.
That's probably why I love you.
I'm gonna hop in the shower.
I told you I can't talk.
You have 100 hours precisely.
After that,
everything we own
will be released.
And it's not enough just to
focus your attention on the logs.
We should also monitor social-media
traffic, as well as IRC, Pastebin.
And set up scripts
to keep going 24/7.
We might get lucky,
we might get sloppy, make a
mistake, you know, catch some...
This is the world
we live in,
people relying on
each other's mistakes
to manipulate one another,
use one another,
even relate to one another.
The warm, messy circle
of humanity.
Elliot?
I'm inviting you guys,
uh, to dinner tonight.
Morton's notwithstanding,
I cook a mean steak.
What? Can't a boss invite his
favorite employees to dinner?
No, that's cool,
but I got plans.
Can you guys give us a minute?
Yeah.
You wanna tell me
what's going on?
Not really.
Well...
You're missing work,
you come in looking like that,
and you expect me
not to ask questions?
Look, I don't know how much you want
me asking about your personal life.
But...
Not at all, actually.
I mean, I don't mean
to be rude, just...
I'm just being honest.
Mr. Robot may have
found Evil Corp's bug,
but he didn't find mine.
That's the only way
to protect myself,
never show them my source code.
Close myself off.
Create my cold, perfect maze
where no one can ever find me.
Elliot! I cannot believe you work here.
This place is a shithole!
Look, I thought I'd
swing by, take you to lunch.
Oh, that's nice.
I think she likes you, bud.
All right, fine, I'll take her.
But let the record show, I was
trying to be a good wing man.
Oh, calm down! Shit.
I'm not that into
redheads anyway.
The whole nation of Ireland
makes my dick soft.
Leave.
Darlene said we need to talk.
Leave, now.
You're right,
probably shouldn't talk here.
Let's go to that bar next door.
I'm not going anywhere with you.
I'm not going anywhere
until you do.
So, I can hang out here
and create a scene,
or you can give me five
minutes in the bar next door.
Either way, I'm gonna have fun.
Dealer's choice.
Mmm.
What? It's an appletini.
I should kick your ass.
Mmm. If that'll make us
square, you have my blessing.
Nah, man, I want nothing to do with you.
You're a maniac.
What can I get for you?
Uh, nothing.
Uh, you should probably order something.
I'd recommend this.
Fine.
I'll, I'll have a...
Appletini.
You should it as a compliment, guy,
these things are goddamn delicious.
I get it, compliments
make me uncomfortable, too.
You know, I find that hard to believe.
Yeah, who am I kidding?
I love compliments.
$12.
I really don't think you enjoyed that.
I suggest sipping it...
Last chance.
What do you want?
I'm sorry for what I did.
I don't buy it.
More importantly,
I don't give a shit.
Hey, I never wanted to hurt you.
People who get violent, get that way
because they can't communicate.
Your dad...
I bet he felt shitty
for doing what he did.
I'm sure he wanted
to apologize, too.
Sometimes pushing your kid
away is just easier.
Don't stay mad
at him too long, kiddo.
You're leaving?
That's what you want, isn't it?
What about your plan?
Plan?
You're the key
to the whole thing.
Without you, there is no plan.
That's it?
It's over?
You expect me to believe that?
See you in another life.
Did you hear that?
I can't believe it.
Is that really happening?
Fsociety's finally over.
The recent glitch in the otherwise
neat reality I created over the years,
I'll never slip
up like that again.
I'm gonna be more normal now.
Maybe Shayla could
even be my girlfriend.
I'll go see those stupid
Marvel movies with her.
I'll join a gym.
I'll heart things on Instagram.
I'll drink vanilla lattes.
I'm gonna lead
a bug-free life from now on.
Anything to protect
my perfect maze.
Hey, Gideon.
Is that dinner
still on for tonight?
Um, yeah, sure.
Uh, uh, you want...
You want to come?
Yeah.
Great.
Can I bring my girlfriend?
You have a girlfriend?
Well, I haven't
asked her yet, but I will.
Hopefully she'll say "yes."
Uh, yeah, sure.
Perfect.
Thanks.
Was he drinking Starbucks?
Are you still trying
to rip that CD?
Yeah, it's all scratched up.
Let's get outta here.
My boss invited me to a dinner
party at his place tonight.
Thought you could come
as my girlfriend.
What?
Are you actually asking me to
be your girlfriend right now?
Yeah.
Anyway, I need you. I'm not good
in social situations like that.
There is something
seriously wrong with you.
I'm... I'm not
gonna be used anymore.
Why don't you ask the girl
from this morning, okay?
She seems like she might wanna go to
some stupid, stuffy dinner party.
You don't actually know me.
All you know is that I'm...
Of course I know Shayla.
I hacked her email as soon
as she moved in next door.
With a simple phishing scam, I
owned her password pretty easily.
I'm not talking about
the stuff you can find online.
I'm talking about the real me.
Tell me then.
No. Forget it.
I wanna know.
What is this?
It's beautiful.
I've never seen
this before, she must...
...never posted online. Um,
I mean, a lot of 'ems not...
They're not done.
She's got
her own private maze, too.
Took a lot of different pieces,
um, from different things.
From my photographs
or drawings. And...
Like, there's this one.
Um, it's really fucking corny.
But it's like... Has everything.
The kids and the...
Shayla 's bug was
always elusive to me.
Maybe this was it,
wanting normalcy, but stuck
in the outer fringes.
Not knowing how to participate.
Just like me.
Can I kiss you?
Next time, don't ask.
It's lame.
Bugs usually get
a bad rep.
But sometimes...
Don't let me down, okay?
When a bug finally
makes itself known,
it can be exhilarating.
Like you just
unlocked something.
A grand opportunity waiting
to be taken advantage of.
Mr. Wellick?
Hey.
What was your name again?
Anwar.
I didn't know you came
to places like this.
I don't.
What do you mean?
You're here now.
I'm here because you are.
What? I'm sorry,
I don't get it.
I think you're beautiful.
I wanna take you home.
Wait, I thought
you were married.
Because, after all,
a bug's only purpose,
its only reason for existence,
is to be a mistake
that needs fixing.
To help you right a wrong.
And what feels better than that?
So, Elliot,
do you think you
should introduce us?
Oh, um, Shayla,
Angela and Ollie.
You, uh... You look
lovely this evening.
What up guys?
You just get here?
Nice suit.
Thanks, dude.
What is up with you?
You've been fidgeting all night.
Maybe we should try
the doorbell again.
Hey guys!
How have you been
standing out here?
The doorbell is broken.
I should have warned you.
Come in!
I'm Harry, by the way.
Angela. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Hey.
Always nice to put a face
with an employee badge number.
Right?
Ollie, how long have
you guys been together?
Uh, two and a half years.
Two years.
Okay.
Elliot, how long have
you and Shayla been together?
Well, uh...
Um, just... Just today.
Okay, enough grilling
of the guests.
Let's check on
the real grill, shall we?
Elliot, I could use your help.
So, I have a confession.
I had the sys admins of the data center
in Dulles check that server again.
Gideon, what did you do?
Of course, there was nothing.
I have no idea what there was
to even be suspicious about.
I mean, what possible motivation
would you have to do anything?
Gideon has to let this go.
If he comes
near this hornet's nest,
I'm not sure
I can save him from it.
I have to kill
any suspicion left.
You've been nothing,
but a hard worker for Allsafe.
So,
I apologize.
After the conversation
on the plane,
I knew what was at stake.
The whole company.
I was worried that the DAT file
I found wasn't the right one,
and I just didn't want to get your
hopes up in case I was wrong.
That's why I didn't tell you
before the meeting.
Shit, I'm gonna have
to let him hug me, aren't I?
You're such
a brilliant engineer, Elliot.
You should never doubt
your skills,
no matter how much
pressure I put on you.
And you certainly don't have
to keep anything from me.
I care about you.
From the Mixed-Up Files
of Basil E. Frankweiler.
That's where I got
the idea, remember?
I wanted to be
Claudia Kincaid so bad.
Even her name was cool.
Remember, we thought we were
going to the Met,
somehow we ended up at the
Queens Museum instead.
No Google Maps back then.
I loved running away with you.
Somehow, when you're eight,
running away can be fun.
The normal life.
Smiles,
dinner parties,
childhood stories.
I could get used to this,
maybe even like it.
What's wrong?
Evil
Corp's hacking scandal continues
with the release
of these latest emails.
Information stemming from
the latest dump reveals
that Terry Colby was one of three
high-level executives involved
in the cover-up
of the widely publicized
Washington Township
Toxic Waste Scandal.
If these reports are true, Colby
may be facing more indictments.
In the ensuing 24 months after the
alleged toxic waste leak in 1993,
26 employees died from
similar types of leukemia.
Evil Corp, however, managed to
get the class action lawsuit
filed against it by the
surviving victims dismissed,
claiming there was no direct evidence
linking their factories to the diagnoses.
Now, these emails indicate
that Colby was in fact aware
of the dangerous
levels of toxicity
and kept it a secret, as it quote,
"Would not be cost-effective
"to retool the current systems in place,
even if there are potential lawsuits."
End quote.
Mr. Colby was unavailable for
comment, but his lawyers...
My perfect maze
crumbling before my eyes.
...data dump are
further proof Colby was set up.
But they didn't
indicate by whom.
There's nothing
to hide behind.
I didn't think it existed,
but there it was, is.
Mr. Robot
finally found my bug.
...linking the waste levels in
Washington Township to the victim's illnesses.
Legal analysts support the claim that
there is not enough evidence to...
What's going on?
That's how my mom,
um, and Elliot's dad...
I have to go.
Well, wait... Wait,
let me come with you.
No, I'd rather you didn't.
Evidence in the
Washington Township scandal.
Terry Colby remains
under investigation
for his alleged involvement
with the Evil Corp executives
because there was no evidence
linking the waste dump to leukemia.
Evil Corp is dangerous...
Don't look so sad.
He did this to himself.
He gave in. He was a coward.
He was weak and pathetic,
and, in the end, that's
what killed your father.
Why are you crying?
Don't ask so many questions.
I miss him.
There's no point to that.
But I do.
Then you're just as weak as him.
You're not sad?
Why should I be?
It's a beautiful night.
The weather is nice.
And I'm enjoying my cigarette.
The bug forces
the software to adapt,
evolving something new
because of it.
Work around it or work through it...
No matter what, it changes,
it becomes something new,
the next version,
the inevitable upgrade.
You're a strange creature.
I'm just a businessman.
And that's about as clean
as I'm gonna get it.
You have to do the rest
in the shower.
I don't mind
being a little dirty.
I do.
You should join me!
Yeah, I'll be there in a minute.
Hey.
I'm sorry
that I ran off like that.
Did you talk to him?
Nope. He wasn't home.
Well, I'm here.
I want to talk to you about
everything, just not tonight, okay?
So, you'd talk to him,
but not your own boyfriend?
It's different, Ollie.
Both of our parents
died because...
That's how we know each other.
I really don't wanna talk
about this right now.
Well, what if I do?
What if you do what?
Wanna talk!
About...
Something.
What the hell
are you talking about?
I have to tell you something.
I don't know why you're...
You're putting yourself through this,
you don't have to keep
looking at it.
All right? It meant nothing.
Okay, I know I sound like a
broken record, but I love you,
and I wanna be with you.
Stop speaking.
Just tell me what you need
in order for me to fix this,
and I'll do it.
We need to break up.
Angela, come on.
What choice
did you give me, Ollie?
Look, I know I have a problem,
I'm not denying that.
Well maybe my problem is...
I can't be
with a guy with your problem.
Where's the CD?
It's in my...
In my bag. Why?
He has my bank account, Ollie.
And my dad's bank account.
How did they...
Our accounts are linked
because of my student loans. I
used your laptop to access it.
He has my dad's social security,
his credit card numbers,
everything.
Okay.
Okay, that is bad, but I'm... But I'm
sure the cops will figure out a way...
If we don't do what this guy
says and we go to the oops,
then he's just gonna sell our
information to the highest bidder,
and me and my dad
are completely screwed.
Do you have any idea
how difficult it is
to come back from massive
identity theft like this?
What are you saying?
Angela? Are you crazy?
No. We cannot just infect Allsafe's
network because of this.
I'll lose my job!
And there it is.
You'll lose your job too,
if that matters.
Besides, even if we put
the CD in,
who says this guy won't
just do all of this anyway?
Hey. Hey, hey.
Come here.
Look at me.
We are going to figure this out.
Okay?
You're right.
I'm sorry.
I'm just scared.
I don't wanna break up
with you. I'm sorry that I said that.
I love you so much.
This is Edmond Dulles.
Yeah, hi. This, um, Gideon
Goddard at Allsafe Security.
I need to talk to Sean Skyler
about server CS30 again.
Hold please.
I'll transfer you.
Mmm-hmm.
Here's the plan.