- There's a reason we met.
There's something between us.
I can see it.
- You're only seeing
what's in front of you.
You're not seeing
what's above you.
[thunder rumbling]
- This is going to be
affecting our economy
in ways that are
extraordinarily significant.
The FBI announced today
that Tyrell Wellick
and fsociety
engaged in this attack.
- Blackouts.
Why?
So they can take away
your power.
- The public is hoarding cash.
The housing market
is grinding to a halt.
- Dark Army.
They got no code.
They hack for anyone.
- Tell me about your father.
- We were close.
Worked at Evil Corp
his whole life.
One of the best
computer engineers they had.
One day, he told me
he had leukemia.
- They are going to try
and get rid of me again,
and I need you
to not let them.
- He is a part of you
that makes you you.
- Who are you talking to?
- 26 employees died
in the widely-publicized
Washington Township
toxic waste scandal.
- If I told you
that your mother
and Elliot's father
died for a reason,
would it make a difference?
That they were sacrificed
for the greater good,
that they gave their lives
to take humanity
to the next level?
- Tyrell, are you there?
They told me
you would be calling.
This is a secure line.
- You sure you still don't
want to talk to me?
- We got to show her
we're smarter.
They're going to try
and flip her.
Let me do it alone.
I know her.
- You've got to be
fucking kidding me.
- This gets
his phone mic live.
I'm going to ask him
about Stage 2.
- The Dark Army set this up?
- They're our partners.
- It's Elliot.
He's the one with the plan.
- When is Stage 2?
Femtocell the backdoor.
You planned all of that
with him?
You're not hacking anything.
This will level that building
and kill people.
I'm going to get rid of
the backdoor.
- We're supposed to be gods
together,
and yet you want to
destroy our destiny?
- Step away from the computer!
- You touch that keyboard,
and I will shoot you.
- No, you won't.
You can't.
It doesn't exist.
- This control
you think you have...
[tense music]
It's an illusion.
- I'm the only one
that exists.
It's time to finally
take back control.
Real control.
- "So much depends
on a red wheelbarrow."
[gunshot]
"Glazed with rainwater
beside the white chickens."
- You know,
once you gave me this,
you said to stop anyone
who gets in the way of
our plan.
- Sorry, kiddo.
[like static] I couldn't let
anyone stop this.
Including us.
-  Love you've gone
from me
And left behind
So many memories
[hole punch clicks]
- Looks like you're going to
get a free milkshake,
you lucky dog.
- I'll take chocolate,
please.
- Oh, sorry, sir.
That offer is only valid
on your next visit.
- I don't understand.
I got my punches.
Didn't you just say
I could have a free milkshake?
- Yes, and you can redeem it
on your next visit.
- What's the difference?
I'm here now.
- I'm sorry, sir.
That's not the way it works.
- Okay, should I just
get out of line
and then get back in?
- No, sir.
You would have to redeem it
on your next visit here.
- Okay.
What qualifies as a visit?
Do I have to leave the premises
and come back?
Do I have to go home?
Is it time-based?
You see the faulty logic here,
don't you?
- Sir, those are the rules.
You can speak to the manager,
or I'd be happy to
add a milkshake to your order
for $12.95.
- It's not about the money.
[cell phone rings]
It's about the principle.
- Sir,
there's nothing I can do.
[phone rings]
- Uh-huh.
Calm down.
No...
Screaming isn't going to help
this situation, is it?
Uh-huh.
Yeah, well,
I agree.
It's not good.
Is he dead?
Uh-huh.
All right.
Be there in 15 minutes.
When we lose our principles,
we invite chaos.
[elevator clanks]
- [breathing raggedly]
Thank God you're here.
I...
I don't know how
it got to this.
[breathes]
Please,
tell me you can help him.
He--he can't...
I can't...
- Well, he's kinda still alive.
Uh, this wasn't what I meant
by "safekeeping."
- Please, just tell me,
I need to know.
Is he going to live?
- [noncommittal grunt]
The doctors are on route.
And they're about
two minutes out.
Camera...
Uh...
You know,
pushing on his stomach
like that--
that's, uh,
that's not helping things.
You might want to stop that.
[camera shutter beeps, clicks]
Uh-huh.
Well,
our people are working on him
as we speak.
Uh-huh.
[door creaks]
Just went in to surgery.
Uh-huh.
Well...
[car turns over]
What do you want me to do
about the Swede?
Uh-huh.
And as far as the kid goes?
Ready when you are.
[tense music]
Okeydoke.
- I love a great mystery.
And I'm fascinated
by the greatest
unsolved mystery.
Do we see reality as it is?
If I close my eyes
and imagine...
That, ladies and gentlemen,
is why it's always smart
to have backup generators
at a nuclear power plant.
[laughter]
And as I was saying,
if I close my eyes,
I can imagine
that everything we experience,
everything we see,
think, and do,
is unfolding simultaneously
in a parallel universe.
And if so,
how many copies of our cells
exist?
And might our mental states
be conjoined?
For better or worse.
- He really is
a crazy little goose, isn't he?
- No, no, no.
Remember what we said.
Practice makes perfect.
- [accented] Sir,
I think they are both
incredibly unstable people.
Let me run Stage 2 for you.
I am more than capable.
[tablet cover snaps shut]
- Have I ever told you
that Mr. Alderson's father
used to work for us
on this project?
Unbeknownst to him,
of course.
In fact, it was his
great engineering work
that led to some of our
early successes.
What an extraordinary
coincidence.
And now his son works for us
after so many years.
- But you don't believe
in coincidence.
- Yes, I don't,
which is why you misunderstand
Mr. Alderson's value.
It was his
impassioned plea
to destroy E Corp
that presented us
with the opportunity
to set our plan in motion,
and it has taken
his relentless determination
since
to continue it.
We may possess
the necessary tools,
but what we do not have
is his unadulterated focused...
rage.
Time presented us Mr. Alderson
when we needed him.
Therefore,
his will must be our guide.
And after Mr. Alderson
completes the great work
that we need from him,
then he can die for us.
Just like his father.
[Julie Andrews singing
"Whistling Away the Dark"]
-  Often I see
This sad old world
Is whistling in the dark
Just like a child
Who late from school
Walks bravely home
through the park
To keep their spirit
soaring
[high-pitched buzzing]
[music fades out]
[foreboding music]
- Are you still there?
Am I?
What did we miss?
Did you see anything?
I blacked out.
If I'm alive,
I must have been right.
None of it was real.
I'm the one in control.
The one with the power.
But why doesn't it
feel that way?
- You're awake.
[distant sirens]
The electricity's still out.
It's been out a week now.
- What am I doing here?
[metronomic music]
- They brought you here
yesterday.
You don't remember.
- What are you talking about?
Who brought me here?
- The people
that you're working with.
They called me.
They told me
that you were hurt.
- What people?
- I don't know who they are.
I only recognized one of them.
- Who?
- Tyrell Wellick.
- Shit.
It was real.
It actually happened.
The gun.
- Slow down.
You've been shot.
- And like that,
my power is gone too.
- I just did
what they told me to do.
I was scared.
- Angela...
you have to tell me
how I got here.
- I was on my way
to turn myself in to the FBI,
and I was stopped
by the Dark Army.
They sent a man
to my apartment.
Elliot, you can't get up.
- I have to warn the police.
- You can't do that.
[line trilling]
If you tell the police
anything,
they're going to kill me.
- 911 center is experiencing
high call volume.
For power outage updates,
use 511.
- They made that very clear.
[line trilling]
- 911.
What's your emergency?
Hello?
- [breathing raggedly]
Then I have to go there.
- Go where?
- I need to find him.
- Who?
- Tyrell.
- Are you crazy?
He shot you.
- They're trying to blow up
Evil Corp's recovery facility.
- Hold on.
- I have to stop them.
- How can you be so sure
that that's what they're doing?
You've been unconscious
for the past six days.
Maybe you're wrong.
- What if I'm not?
Do you have something
I can wear?
[distant police siren chirping]
They did a full wipe-down.
Where is Tyrell?
And something else is off.
That ever-looming presence
that is Mr. Robot.
I don't feel it.
Is it possible
that the bullet killed him,
and not me?
[thunder rumbling]
- The mark of the beast
is the mark of the elite.
One world government
is a myth.
Fear the one world
corporation.
The beast has many titles.
Prince of darkness,
Lord of Lies,
Ruler of Hell.
[continues preaching distantly]
- Oh, Elliot.
Hey.
Let your visitor know
I got plenty of
vacant apartments.
We got to get
some of these things rented,
or else we're all
going to get screwed.
That's why I upgraded
the facade.
You know. It used to be
this ugly red.
Now it's this chrome.
I think it's very inviting.
- What visitor?
- Whoever's in your apartment.
Just tell him
we're running a special.
Utilities included.
[laughs]
[keys jingling]
[dramatic music]
- Where the fuck
have you been?
- You shouldn't be here.
- Why are you walking
like that?
You can't just disappear on me
for days and not say anything.
[radio static]
- [quietly]
Shut the fuck up.
There are men outside.
They might be listening.
We have to go.
- I need to talk to you
about something.
- It's not safe for you here.
- Cisco's dead.
[distant sirens]
Dark Army turned on us.
They killed him,
and I think I'm next.
- What happened?
- We were having dinner,
and all of a sudden,
gunshots went off.
The slowest three seconds
of my life.
The FBI even questioned me.
So yeah, it's not safe
for me anywhere.
In fact, everywhere for me
is pretty much fucked.
- What did you tell them?
The FBI?
- God.
You're a shitty brother,
you know that?
I could've been dead, Elliot.
- Sorry.
- What is this about,
anyway?
Stage 2?
The phone we hacked
before you did
your vanishing act.
The hot mic picked it all up.
Stage 2 is your plan,
isn't it?
Elliot?
What is Stage 2?
[tense music]
- The femtocell
you had Angela install.
- Yeah, so?
That was for a hack
on the FBI.
- That wasn't
the only reason.
It created a backdoor
inside Evil Corp.
It was to get access
to the UPSs inside
one of their buildings.
- What building?
- The building
that's housing
their recovery program.
All their backup paper records,
titles,
deeds, loan documents...
- Jesus.
Oh, you were--you were just
going to blow it up?
This is what you meant
by "finishing off Evil Corp."
They'd have no chance
at rebuilding their database.
You were planning this
with them
all along behind my back.
- No, no, it wasn't like that.
- Because you didn't think
I'd go along with it?
Killing all of those people?
- It wasn't me!
Wasn't me.
[whispering]
I can stop it.
I can stop this.
- You're not going to get
online here.
Internet's been down for days.
- If I can close the backdoor,
I can stop it.
Darlene...
please help me.
- I know a space
that has access.
But you're not going to
get in there
wearing that shirt.
[suspenseful music]
- You got to be
kidding me, man.
- No, that's the cost.
- Come on.
- How are you going to pay?
[electronic dance music
playing]
[indistinct chatter]
- Looks a little busy.
- The only hacker space
with a dedicated
fiber connection.
Stay here, I'll find us
a way to get on.
- A CTF tournament.
Capture the flag.
It's like the hacker Olympics.
Teams around the world
compete to solve challenges.
Reverse-engineering
protocol exploitation,
forensics.
The entire city's
suffering an energy crisis
while they're here, exercising
their inner anarchy.
It's times like these
I really wish
I had a mute button for life.
- Whoo! Whoo!
[world becomes silent]
Isn't that better?
- We're fucked.
All the machines are taken.
They're in the middle
of the final round
of the qualifier
for a CTF.
It's them versus
nine other countries,
and from the scoreboard,
the Koreans are ride or die.
It's going to take forever
before this is over.
- Or I could just
win it for them.
[cheering]
They let you save
and load your game,
restoring all the mines
you found
and all the shells you cleared.
That's the weakness.
The game trusts
whatever data you give it
to recreate the board.
Poison the data.
You can make it run
whatever code you want.
- Yeah.
We already thought about that.
It won't work.
There's a server-side key
used to verify the game saves.
- And without it,
you just get a checksum error,
which is why you play the game
until you find the mines first.
Once you know the full board,
you can derive the key.
And you already spotted
the code injection vuln
in the save handler function,
right?
- Shit.
I never thought of that.
- Dude, just let him on.
- No way, man.
Need I remind you,
I was a CyberPatriot finalist.
- Yeah, in middle school.
If we don't make the top three,
we're not going to Vegas.
And he knows this shit
better than you.
- Fuck it, I've been at this
for four fucking hours.
I gotta deuce it out anyway.
This Soylent ain't
for the faint-hearted.
[eerie music]
- [panting]
- I see them.
Stay calm.
It's Dark Army.
It's me they want, not you.
You having an attack?
- It's okay.
Don't stop, okay?
I'll be fine.
[cries]
[hyperventilating]
Fuck!
[cries]
You need to help me.
There's Dark Army everywhere.
I saw them.
They have guns.
Please.
[knocking on door]
Shit.
[people cheering]
- Dude!
Dude, I can't believe
it only took you
two minutes to win
the final round.
- Can you please
take your hand off me
and leave me alone?
- Yeah.
Dude, I--I was just--
- Thank you.
[keys clacking]
The backdoor had
a hard-coded C2 domain
pointing to a listener
on Tyrell's machine.
All I have to do
is hack the registrar
and change
the name server configs.
Once I hijack the domain,
I can shut down their access
before the Dark Army notices.
- Elliot.
- I'm almost done.
I shut the backdoor.
I just have to uninstall--
[computer cuts out]
[crowd still cheering]
- Stand up and walk with us.
Do it.
[dance music plays distantly]
[indistinct chatter]
- Go down Cortlandt Alley.
- What are you doing?
This is them.
- It's them I want to see.
[engine turns over]
- [whistles]
Get in.
- We're good, man.
- No, you're not.
That car she's eyeballing
is FBI.
They're following you.
Been following you
since you left the apartment.
You're gonna want to get in.
[motor revs]
Hey, miss, grab my laptop.
Should be on the floor
right below you there.
Pull up the motor vehicle
lookup tool, would you?
Sorry...
about the mess.
Been a while
since I had time to clean it.
But hey, gas prices
what they are right now,
taxis are a premium,
so, you know,
you're welcome
for the free cab ride.
Uh, now, Elliot,
do me a favor, would you?
Read her the license plate
of the car
that's been tailing us.
- UVM 7482.
[passing traffic honking]
[tense music]
- All right, good.
Uh, now, miss.
Input that plate number.
Grab the VIN number.
Put it on a...
sticky note.
I got 'em
in the side door there,
along with a pen.
[cell rings]
- OnStar center.
This is Debbie.
How may I help you?
- Yeah, I need to report
an emergency.
This is Detective
Robert Abernathy,
badge number 8301,
out of the 19 precinct.
[aside]
Get that number?
Yeah, I got a stolen vehicle.
Driving erratically,
and almost hitting pedestrians
during the outage here.
Yeah, I'm gonna pursue
for about ten minutes.
Yeah, I have line of sight
of the vehicle.
I need to initiate a slowdown.
Okay. VIN number,
here we go:
1, H, G, C,
M, 8, 2, 6,
3, 3, A,
0, 0,
4, 3,
F as in Franklin,
2.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Uh, okay.
I see the lights blinking.
Thank you, guys.
All right.
Who wants barbecue?
[thunder rumbling]
[generator humming]
[neon sign buzzing]
- Red Wheelbarrow.
Did they get that from me?
Or did I get it from them?
However it happened,
it's clearly
a Dark Army front now.
This must be the guy
that sent me
that fucking menu.
- Do me a favor, miss.
Go get us a couple
of number fours.
On me.
Oh.
And make sure
they punch my card.
- I'm not going anywhere.
[light music playing]
- Well, I got business
with your brother, here.
Now, the faster
we get that rolling,
the faster you two can leave.
- It's okay.
[thunder rumbling]
- I'll go stand over there,
but I'm not getting you
a fucking number four.
- What about my punch card?
- And don't call me "miss."
- Well, she's full of life,
huh?
- Let's get to what
this is about.
- Well...
[sighs]
We hear you've been
running around town.
The doc says
you should be resting.
- I had shit to do.
- Well, you want to
catch me up
on where we're at?
- I shut the backdoor.
- Now, why would you
go do a thing like that?
- I'm calling
this operation off.
- You sure you want to do that?
We've gone to great lengths--
- It's not negotiable.
And if there's a problem
with my request,
you can deal with me.
And only me.
[thunder rumbling]
- Ah, I suppose our employer
will be disappointed.
- I don't have an employer.
- Uh-huh.
Well...
She believes that a plan
lives or dies
by its creator, so...
if you want it dead,
so be it.
- Where are you going?
- Oh, I want to go home.
And they canceled
the Mets game,
so I'll probably end up
working on my book a little.
- So that's it?
- That's it.
- I want confirmation.
From her.
[thunder rumbling]
- You know that bullet
we took out of you?
We can easily
put it right back in.
You won.
Go home.
Before you end up
losing again.
- What happened?
- It's over.
They're calling off Stage 2.
- Just like that?
- Just like that.
- I don't buy it.
- We'd both be dead
if they wanted to stop us.
That tends to be their response
when they disagree with you.
- And who are "they," exactly?
Is this just Dark Army, or
is Tyrell Wellick
involved in all of this, too?
I know a lot more
than you think, Elliot.
Answer the question.
Is Tyrell Wellick involved?
Has he been a part
of this whole thing
from the beginning?
- No.
Look, even if they were lying,
I closed their only access.
- You want to bury your head
in the sand,
be my guest.
But my eyes are staying
wide fucking open.
- The only thing that matters
is that we survive this thing.
We got out alive,
which happens to be
a luxury right now.
We don't know where Trenton
and Mobley are,
but they're probably dead.
And we know what happened
to Cisco.
- Go fuck yourself.
[door opens, closes]
[distant siren wailing]
- Darlene's right.
I can't trust them.
This was too easy.
But at least I stopped them
for now.
I can go home knowing that.
But was she right about me?
Am I sticking my head
in the sand?
Did my revolution
just bury our minds,
instead of freeing them?
[dark music]
Encrypting Evil Corp's data
was meant to empower us.
Instead, it left us powerless,
scaring us into
even more submission.
I am not going to get rid of
the invisible hand.
Turned it into a fist
that punched us in the dick.
And like a botnet,
the fear I created
is spreading so fast,
it's practically airborne.
It's swallowed us whole,
digested us,
and now we're stuck
in its asshole,
waiting to be dumped out.
And while we're here,
they're having their way
with us.
They packaged a fight
into product.
Turned our dissent
into intellectual property.
Televising our revolution
with commercial breaks.
[NBC chime]
They backdoored
into our minds
and robbed our truth,
refurbished the facts,
then marked up the price.
This is what they do.
It's what they're good at.
This is their greatest trick.
- To try and bring the truth.
They're trying to
take that away.
And now they're moving
to the next step.
Yeah, next step.
You know what the next step is?
- Lobotomizing us
into their
virtual reality horror show.
- Why? So they can
take away your power,
and I am not talking
about your electricity.
- And this all started
because I tried to
hide from society.
Remember?
Fuck society.
Yeah, well, I fucked society,
all right.
I reset it to zero,
and if I don't do anything
about it,
it will continue to grow
in this malignant way.
And that's what I'm afraid of
the most.
This dark future
that I set into motion.
Who knows
what could come from this?
- Thank you,
thank you very much.
- What if instead of
fighting back, we caved,
gave away our privacy
for security,
exchanged dignity for safety,
and traded revolution
for repression?
What if we choose weakness
over strength?
- These are not the people
that made our country great.
These are the people
that are destroying
our country.
- They'll even have us
build our own prison.
This is what they wanted
all along.
For us to buy in
on our worst selves.
[crowds jeering]
And I just made it easier
for them.
I didn't start a revolution.
I just made us docile enough
for their slaughtering.
And I can stand here
and blame Evil Corp
and every other conglomerate
out there
for taking advantage of us,
blame the FBI, NSA, CIA,
for letting them
get away with this,
blame all the world's leaders
for aiding and abetting them,
blame Adam Smith
for inventing modern-day
capitalism
in the first fucking place.
Blame money for dividing us,
blame us for letting it.
But none of that's true.
The truth is...
I'm the one to blame.
[thunder rumbling]
I'm the problem.
This was my fault.
All of it.
I did this.
[thunderclap]
Fuck me.
- Sir?
We're closing up.
I'm going to have to
ask you to leave.
[thunder rumbling]
[thunder, torrential rain]
- I need a job at Evil Corp.
- What?
- I need to find a way
to fix what I did.
You need to give me
a job there.
- I don't know
that I can just do that.
- With everything
they've been through,
they must need people
to work on
their recovery program.
I need you to try.
This is important.
- Okay.
I'll try.
- One more thing.
[tense music]
I need you
to keep an eye on me.
I need you to tell me
if I'm ever him.
If anyone can tell...
It's you.
- Why do you think
I can tell?
- You know me
better than anyone.
Right now...
You're the only person
I can trust.
- [gasps]
[mutters]
- Sorry.
- What happened before,
when we kissed,
that was a mistake.
[distant thunder]
- If you're wondering
if this hurts...
Yeah.
It hurts a lot, but...
I get it.
I've known Angela
since I was eight.
This is what she does.
She doesn't love the people
who love her.
She loves the people
who don't.
This is her power-saver mode.
[solemn music]
What's wrong?
- I have to
tell you something.
- What?
- What if I told you
we could make it
like none of this
ever happened?
- You mean 5/9?
- No, not just that.
I mean, everything.
Including what happened
to our parents.
If we could take it all back,
from the beginning...
what would you be willing
to sacrifice for that?
- Angela,
what are you talking about?
That's not possible.
- What if I told you it is?
- How?
- Never mind.
I'm just tired.
I think I should go to bed.
Can you stay here tonight?
It's been a rough
couple of months.
Just make me feel safe.
- Yeah.
- [gasps]
Elliot?
- It's me.
[dark music]
- Come closer.
I need to get dressed.
And then we'll go.
- Did you convince him
Stage 2 is over?
- That's been taken care of.
- We need to pick up Darlene.
She should be a part of this.
- No.
In fact, you need to
stay away from her.
We can't trust her.
She helped Elliot
close the backdoor.
- Come again?
She did what?
The backdoor is closed?
- Yes.
- [scoffs]
Why are you so calm about this?
- We're going to find a way
to get back on the network.
- Is that all?
- We'll be fine.
- This isn't about
the backdoor.
It's about him.
Anything we do,
he will try to slow us down.
As long as he exists,
he will stop us.
- Then we'll find a way
to redirect his energy.
[cell phone buzzes]
Come on.
They're expecting us.
- What's that for?
- In case Elliot comes back.
- How can you tell?
That it's me?
How do you know
that you're not talking to him
right now?
- Your eyes.
You're never trying
to look away.
[distant sirens]
- Are you all right?
When I saw him
earlier tonight,
he was all hell-bent
on not doing this.
How'd you change his mind?
- You have to remember,
he woke up
with a gunshot wound
in his stomach.
He's still getting
his bearings,
but he's fine now.
- Uh-huh.
Something's rotten
about all this.
When we spoke earlier,
he was looking at me
like we'd never met.
- You brought me in
to manage him.
And that's exactly
what I've done.
Nothing else matters,
does it?
Thank you
for getting me the time
before checking in with her.
- Don't thank me too quickly.
We're behind schedule now,
and we both know how she feels
about punctuality.
- One more thing.
I'm going to get him
a job at Evil Corp.
Doesn't hurt to have him
on the inside,
given our situation.
- Are you sure
he's good to go?
- Yes.
- You have to understand, I...
thought you were
dismantling our project.
You were ruining
our whole mission
that we sacrificed
and worked hard to build.
- It's okay.
You did what I asked of you.
Still...could've had
better aim, though.
It takes a lot
to miss every vital organ.
That's some pretty
piss-poor marksmanship.
What?
I'm messing with you.
Just trying to
break the ice a little.
Come on.
Still have plenty of work
to do.
[Daft Punk's "Touch"]
-  Touch
I remember touch
Pictures came with touch
A painter in my mind
Tell me what you see
A tourist in a dream
A visitor it seems
A half-forgotten song
Where do I belong
Tell me what you see
I need something more
[muffled, faraway voice]
- We reestablish access
that tunnels us right back in
Evil Corp's internal network.
[on radio]
-  Suddenly alive
Happiness arrive
Hunger like a storm
How do I begin
Tell me what you see
- I got to ask,
what is in this for you?
Why are you doing this?
- Like I told you before,
I'm not going to talk to you
like I talk to Elliot.
You and I,
we are not friends.
- It's precisely
that you're besties with him
that I'm trying to understand
how you can lie to him
so blatantly.
- How could I be lying to him?
I'm literally looking
right at him.
- That's certainly
a creative way
to get out of this.
But let's be real.
You are taking advantage
of Elliot's...
let's call it
"unique" condition.
- He started this,
didn't he?
I'm just helping him
finish it.
I'm pushing him along.
Isn't that what you do?
- That is what I do.
If you want me
to keep on doing
what it is that I do,
we're going to have to
trust each other.
Right now, Angela,
I do not trust you.
So I'm going to ask you
one more time.
Why, exactly,
are you doing all of this?
- Evil Corp killed my mom.
And my whole life...
I've always wanted justice
for her death.
But how do you bring justice
to a conglomerate
as untouchable as Evil Corp?
I thought I would never win.
Even after I found out
about your crazy plan,
I still didn't believe
it was possible.
Not until I met Whiterose.
It wasn't until
she opened my eyes
that I could see how
all of the damage
that they've caused...
Could finally be...undone.
When we succeed...
A whole new world
will be born.
[lights hum]
Looks like the power's back on.
-  Touch
Sweet touch
You've given me
too much to feel
Sweet touch
You've almost convinced me
I'm real
I need something more
I need something
More