_
- Stay right there!
- Don't you fucking move!
Why'd he surrender?
- Who is your leader?
- Fsociety.
A honeypot? For what?
A specific server, involved
in the last fsociety attack.
CS30.
You should know that
nothing's gonna come from this.
It's nice to finally meet you.
Are you sure he is good to go?
When we spoke earlier,
he was looking at me
like we'd never met.
Make sure this doesn't happen again.
Fucking weirdo.
I texted you the address.
- Is that where Tyrell is?
- Yes.
We gotta act before Wellick disappears
for another five months.
You said you'd bring my family to me.
It's gonna work out
the way we discussed.
Angela, whatever White
Rose told you is a lie.
These consequences were necessary...
- People are going to die!
- No, they're going to be fine!
Listen to me. You have
to stop the attack.
There's one last thing I
need in order to execute:
the full force of the Dark Army.
A reported 71 buildings
owned by E Corp exploded or caught fire.
When you see White Rose,
make sure you say I did you good.
We're gonna stay with
my buddy in Arizona.
If what I discovered is real,
do you know what that means?
We can potentially
undo this whole thing.
Excuse me, do you have the time?
Reports are still coming in
from across the country...
But based on the number of targets,
we are now in the midst of
the worst attack on U.S. soil
in the history of our nation.
In a series of seemingly
orchestrated strikes
across the country,
a reported 71 buildings owned by E Corp
exploded or caught fire.
There has been no official confirmation,
or even speculation, as to what caused
the explosions and fires to occur.
Officials with knowledge of the attacks
have stated that the death toll...
I know it may seem petty
in light of today, but...
I just can't stop thinking about it.
Keep turning it over in my mind.
"Frasier."
Now, my homie said it's iconic and shit.
Even won a record 37
Primetime Emmys, or whatever.
So I started watching.
And I'm cool with suspending
my disbelief a little,
but this?
Am I really supposed to believe
a baldin' white dude from Seattle
gets to smash that much?
And it's not like he was
slaying hood rats, neither.
This nigga get more butt than ash trays.
Turned me off from the fucking
situation comedies altogether.
Had to cleanse the palate.
And I know it only got
one Emmy nomination,
but I'll tell you,
you wanna see a believable protagonist
doing extraordinary shit?
Don't sleep on "Knight Rider," yo.
As of now, no one has
claimed responsibility
for this nightmarish attack.
You don't have to kill us.
You know, we can... we...
We can work with you.
Haven't... haven't enough
people died already today?
My man. My man...
Relax.
Calm down.
If I was here to take you out,
would've done it already.
Your roomie here serves
as a prime example to that.
Then what is it? Why are you here?
Oh, just to babysit,
to keep you guys safe and sound.
Will be tested in the coming days
as we learn more, as we
find those responsible..
You know, it's kinda sad, actually,
the general lack of respect
afforded to "Knight Rider."
They throw fucking gold
statues at the Crane brothers,
but Michael Knight and KITT,
their relationship predicted
the current societal
dependence on technology,
and that was 30 years ago.
Plus, anytime Mike
spits game on a chick,
I swear, I believe every goddamn word.
If nothing else,
"Knight Rider" should've
won a fucking statue
for his dope ass theme song.
I mean, the shit just stays with you.
Stuck in my head right now, in fact.
A National Terrorism Advisory System
has issued an imminent alert bulletin,
after a reported 71 E Corp buildings
were targeted in a coordinated attack
unlike any the world has seen.
At this time, many
looming questions remain:
the cause of the explosions
that brought so much destruction,
or worse, if any additional
attacks are to follow.
Unfortunately, what we do know
is that...
Elliot, it's okay.
Just calm down and keep breathing.
- Okay.
- And you can tell me
what it is that you think you did, okay?
Just breathe,
and whenever you're ready, we can talk.
Okay.
Um...
Uh...
I, um...
I think we...
I'm... I'm sorry.
I don't know if I can say it.
I don't know if I can say it,
what... I'm sorry, Krista.
What... what he...
Or I...
What... what...
What we both may have done,
I don't know if I can say it.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I don't know if I can say it.
I don't know if I can say it.
I'm sorry.
Nice to see you again, beautiful.
Hello, Mr. Robot.
Of course he comes
running to you after today.
So predictable.
Elliot said he wanted
to speak to me, but...
conscious or not,
I suspect that he thought
it was more important
that I speak to you.
Why do you have to keep
going through a middleman?
Why can't he just speak to me himself?
I'm not sure he wants to,
but I wanna help you figure out why.
Elliot told me he's worried
that you may have
done something harmful.
Do you know what he
might be referencing?
Everything that happened today
is because he was ignoring
our responsibilities.
What happened exactly?
The point is...
It's not me he has to worry about.
It's the others, the
real string pullers.
Who would that be?
You wanna know what's really going on?
Look around, sweetheart.
I'm not the only one under their thumb.
They're manipulating everything, always,
just to line their own
pockets, to have total control.
But that's the conspiracy, man.
So you and Elliot...
You want to challenge
these manipulators?
Me and Elliot wanted to
take the control away,
give it back to the ones
who were getting shit on.
We got halfway there, until
someone swiped my ideas
and warped them to suit
whatever bullshit agenda
served their self-interest.
That's what Five/Nine was about,
our revolution.
So you are a supporter of Five/Nine?
Supporter?
I was no supporter.
I was the architect!
How about telling me why you think
Elliot might be upset with you?
I don't have time for this shit.
I gotta find the pricks who screwed me.
Turn on the news, lady.
All these buildings fucking blowing up.
I think they're trying
to pin that shit on me.
I know it. It ain't happening.
So, the attacks today were a part of
the revolution you created?
Is that what you're saying?
We were only supposed
to take out one location,
once all the paper
records were centralized.
That was it.
Yeah, I've gotta be
honest with you, Mr. Robot,
this sounds like delusions of grandeur.
How else do you explain what
the authorities are saying?
They claim to have the man responsible.
Wellick?
No, he was working for me,
but you and the rest of the world
are never gonna know that,
because you keep happily
lapping up those
sugar-coated pearls of semen
they keep pouring down your throats.
You're buying the narrative
that they've been pushing for months.
Pigs at a trough!
You still don't believe me.
You're indulging me right now,
like I'm one of your nutso patients.
Do the math.
Elliot worked at Allsafe,
ground zero for Five/Nine.
He was also arrested for hacking.
He even hacked you, didn't he?
And he's completely out of his mind.
You add all that up...
You still want to doubt me?
Good people of Earth,
there is more up our sleeves.
71 buildings is a parlor trick.
Our true act of sorcery will astound
within the next 24 hours.
To all fat cats, gluttons, and honchos,
as you lazily don
your ribbons of remembrance
for this tragic day,
do not forget, the clock is ticking.
I think the public may
lose faith in the Bureau,
once they learn that you squandered
the chance to prevent another attack.
I'm not gonna be strong-armed,
not by you, not after today.
Then I suggest you start taking
- my client's words seriously.
- This is unreal.
The country's under attack,
and you're protecting him?
Wellick was targeted,
because of his access
and credentials at E Corp.
These terrorists
threatened his wife and son
if he didn't comply.
For five straight months,
my client was held
captive in a basement.
You can't expect us to buy this.
We have confirmation.
Wellick gave an unauthorized order
to put server CS30 back on the network,
the same night the hack was initiated,
all while being investigated for murder.
Yeah, a charge for
which he's been cleared.
That doesn't change the facts.
Wellick got passed over for CTO,
got fired, two days later, disappears,
and now, hours before the
largest terror attack ever
on U.S. soil, Wellick resurfaces,
claiming he was kidnapped.
So, what, are you charging my client
with coincidental resurfacing?
We don't call that
coincidence around here.
- We call it bullshit.
- Dom...
- We have motive.
- With no hard evidence.
But here's what you do have.
You have a guy that'll point you
to the terrorists who held him hostage,
the actual people behind the attacks,
the same ones planning more destruction.
Mr. Wellick can ID them,
and tell you their likely location,
in exchange for protection and immunity.
- We're not gonna cut a deal.
- We're gonna charge him
and just add obstruction
of justice on top of it.
You saw the video.
Time is not a luxury that you have,
not with another attack
on the horizon, so...
do you really wanna sit here
and continue to quibble
about Mr. Wellick?
Let's just round them all up,
Darlene, Elliot, Angela Moss.
Let's just haul 'em all
in here and go at 'em hard.
Wellick's lawyer is right.
Time is not our friend here.
And if Tyrell can get
us two workable leads...
We're being played!
How do you not see this?
I still think the Dark Army's involved,
and bringing in the
others might expose that.
I have to brief Comey,
and he has to brief the President.
I won't go to them with
half-assed theories again,
not when this much is on the line.
Why do you keep ignoring
our credible sources?
The most credible one
being in that room.
Tyrell Wellick's name alone
is going to play better
with them than the others.
Play better?
Are you already wondering
how this is gonna look?
You wanna cover this
up to the FBI Director
and the President of the United States?
Spare me the conspiracy theories.
I need to bring them something concrete.
And if Wellick's lying?
Then this deal is off,
and we have our guy.
It's a win-win for us, either way.
Why are you fighting with me on this?
Because something's not adding up.
What's that supposed to mean?
I don't know if this is
because you're overworked
or stressed out or
just under some delusion
that you're a fucking
super-cop, but it stops now.
You report to me.
Start remembering that.
As to what caused the
explosions and fires to...
...Tyrell Wellick and took
him into custody...
...Warned of another attack
within the next 24 hours.
...Of our company's paper rec...
Officials with knowledge of the attacks
have stated that the death toll
is expected to be well...
Right now, the estimate's around 3,000.
What estimate?
The dead.
But it's still climbing.
Okay, maybe you should just
chill with the TV for a second.
They're gonna be okay, right?
Who's that?
All those people who died.
Do you think that they're gonna be okay?
I'm gonna go grab my shit and come back.
It won't be long.
Just don't go anywhere, okay?
Can we just take a break?
I, um... I need a minute.
Unfortunately, that's not possible.
As you know, this is time-sensitive.
Okay.
But after this, I get
to see my family, yes?
It's very important that
I see my wife and child.
I'll be sure to relay your
request to my superior.
For now, though, need
your eyes on that book.
You shouldn't have told anyone, Mom.
I could get in trouble for telling you.
Well, you can't be
afraid to leave the house.
You still have two treatments left.
Don't listen to that video.
It's just a scare tactic.
We caught the guy.
Fine, fi... ... fine.
I'll call Dr. Zeigler,
and ask if it can wait.
I love you too.
The operation took place at
Red Wheelbarrow Barbecue,
it's a popular fast food restaurant
in Manhattan's Flatiron District.
Wellick ID'd the two suspects,
both corroborated by Sasan Nouri,
our fsociety video perp.
You call it in?
We're about to release a BOLO.
Nice work, Stanchek.
I'll see you down in the squad room.
Okay.
- And, uh, sir?
- What?
It's Wellick.
He keeps asking about his family.
He wants to see 'em.
It's just us now.
We can speak freely.
You need to get anything off your chest?
Well...
there's some information
that's about to be
declassified for public release,
and before you hear it from your lawyer
or somebody else,
I wanted to personally come
here and deliver it to you.
Rumor has it you're
asking about your family?
Yes, I've been told
that if I cooperate...
Your wife's dead.
Almost two weeks now.
What?
- No, you must be mistaken.
- Lovers' quarrel
with a dude she was banging.
He shot her in the head at close range.
It's nasty stuff.
Lies. You're lying.
Which means that your son
is currently being raised at
Peaceful Acres Foster Care.
Now, last I checked, it was
only a one in five abuse rate.
Decent odds.
No.
This can't be true.
I know you're lying.
I want to see my wife. I demand it.
If you're thinking about
telling anyone here about me,
if you veer from the plan at all,
I promise, you won't live
to place a flower at your wife's grave.
And your son......
I'll make it my personal mission
to ensure he becomes a statistic.
Just another forgotten child,
lost to the system, forever.
I know what this is. You
sent that email to the FBI.
I knew the Dark Army would find out.
I'm not stupid. I never sent the email.
How do you explain
this? Why are we here?
Kay, maybe he's not gonna
kill us, but someone sure is.
If anything does happen to us,
if I don't make it back to my computer,
I sent the email to go out automatically
to someone I trust.
I'm supposed to be on
a J-Date with Juanita
at Ruby Tuesdays, as we speak.
She's probably worried about me.
Hey. Hey, maybe... Maybe
she'll call the cops,
- report me missing.
- Doubt it.
Besides, what are you
even doing on J-Date?
You're not even Jewish.
And doesn't sound like she is, either.
I told you, my 23andMe
said I'm 6% Ashkenazi,
and for your information,
her full name is Juanita Rosenberg.
Look, do you think I wanna
be stuck in the backseat
of a psychopath's Cadillac with you?
I should be at home with my family.
My brother is probably
flipping out right now.
You think your brother's flipping out?
That guy...
slit my friend's throat,
and now he's digging
what could be a mass grave over there.
Yeah. If your brother's flipping out,
I'm like a Sam Kinison stand-up bit,
okay, Shelley Duvall
at the Overlook Hotel.
I'm at "hot mic'd Christian Bale"
levels of intensity and hysteria,
so please, don't talk
to me about flipping out.
Yes. Yes.
What... hang on, what are you doing?
- You gotta get us out of here.
- I can't...
- I don't know how to drive.
- You have a genius level IQ,
and you can't work an
automatic transmission?
I grew up in the city.
I never had to learn.
Oh, yeah, well, you do now, kay?
Get up there, put pedal to the metal.
Yeah, okay, okay. Okay.
Floor it. Floor it.
- Okay.
- Floor it!
Floor it!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Easy! Easy!
Damn.
That's no way to treat a Caddie.
I can't just do nothing.
I almost went straight
to the authorities.
Oh, well, let's thank our lucky stars
you opted to call me first.
I told you what he said.
How can I not report this?
As your counsel and your friend,
I should remind you, you are bound
by doctor-patient privilege,
so unless he's stated intent
to do something in the future,
you can't turn him in.
Per HIPPA, you'll lose
your license and practice.
No, there's something
about this. I can feel it.
I know him.
I actually think he
might've been involved.
You know how many crazies are out there
claiming responsibility for the attacks?
The... the FBI and the police
are inundated by phone calls
from people just like your client.
Fuck.
Any updates?
They think the total will be over 4,000.
But the number doesn't
really matter now...
Even if there's more.
What do you mean "even if there's more"?
No matter what happens now,
everything will be fine.
Angela, if there are more attacks,
you have to tell me.
I don't know anything about them.
What are you doing?
Here, let me show you.
Okay. Watch.
See?
They all came back.
They're all fine.
Here, I'll show you again.
Told you.
Everyone's okay again.
Everyone's gonna be okay.
Our FBI reporters say that
there was evidence found
at Red Wheelbarrow that...
Tyrell Wellick had been hiding out
in the restaurant's basement.
The FBI's investigating the possibility
that the same fsociety
members behind Five/Nine...
were operating out of
the barbecue eatery.
Interestingly enough,
the basement itself
does not appear on any
plans or blueprints
reported with the city, so it is possible
that Tyrell Wellick and
fsociety were operating
unbeknownst to the Red
Wheelbarrow Barbecue.
While unsuspecting employees
are not a risk to unwitting
customers, justified the
notorious hacker claim.
Hey.
Hey!
Stage 2 was my operation.
You assholes went rogue...
As everyone in this room knows well
nothing creates profit
quite like global conflict.
Bullshit.
Ah, Phillip.
Always a pleasure,
though I am surprised to see you
with all you have on your plate.
You know damn well I'm marooned here.
Well, then a little bit of good news
on an otherwise trying day.
My government did finally
get around to signing that accord.
Ecoin is poised to
become the world standard.
After your latest outburst,
nothing could save my company.
My actions were never
meant to harm E Corp.
On the contrary,
good old-fashioned American sympathy
will go a long way in boosting
an already surging Ecoin.
E Corp is the very definition
of too big to fail.
Trust me, it will survive.
But I won't.
So...
is that... is that what
all this has been then?
No.
When... when you surprised
me with Five/Nine,
I understood your move.
A false flag operation,
a temporary global crisis
to help me pressure the administration
into giving you your damn Congo.
All went according to plan,
which leaves me struggling
to find the upside to this.
Why come after me?
Think back on that fateful night.
We sat,
listening to a young woman
playing a lyre.
A lawsuit was brewing against my plant.
You told me you would...
Handle that person
as we usually do.
And yet,
your pet project, Angela Moss,
was allowed to continue
with her lawsuit...
Which put my plans in jeopardy.
Your job was simple:
manipulate her,
control her.
You couldn't,
so I had to.
You little piece of shit.
Do not forget,
I installed you as CEO
only to protect my plant.
You were meant to do what
your predecessor couldn't,
and look at what happened to him.
And now, you will follow
every order that I give you,
including hiring your own replacement.
- Fuck you.
- In the interim,
uh, I trust that there
will be no interference,
with my plant being
relocated to the Congo.
This... this is funny.
That's... that's... That's all this is.
This is... this is, uh... This is a joke
with a bad punchline.
You will also be called upon
to handle all logistical issues:
proper access for my staff,
shipment of all materials...
No! You give me the real
reason, motherfucker.
Coming at me now.
What in God's name do you hope to gain?
The opportunity to teach a lesson.
A lesson? You sadistic fuck.
You got your U.N. vote,
you got your plant,
you got everything you wanted!
No. You don't get off that easy,
not until you explain it to me.
You had to destroy so much.
Why?
Because, Phillip...
I had to ask you twice.
What if we're being recruited?
Recruited into digging our own grave?
Look at the dimensions.
This hole's only big
enough for your friend.
What if we're being
recruited into the Dark Army?
They could've... They
could've just asked.
They're probably planning
a follow-up attack,
and they need to use us for our skills.
You know I can hear you, right?
Even from way back here.
Every word.
Come on, man.
At least tell us what the
Dark Army wants from us.
Tell us what's going
on, or we stop digging!
We're serious.
I kinda like you two.
You guys are funny, in a
George-Elaine kinda way.
Still wouldn't try me, though.
I got a job to do, and...
you don't wanna know
where this knife been.
You feel me?
Get out of the car.
Hurry up. I'm running out of time here.
See that up there?
What is this?
You know why those people are
enjoying themselves so much,
even though thousands died today
in the biggest attack in U.S. history?
That wasn't my fault. That
wasn't supposed to happen.
I wanna know who made that call.
Was it Tyrell? What
about this other attack?
That was never a part of my plan.
See, kid, that's been your
mistake the entire time,
thinking this whole thing's
about your silly little plan.
No, your revolution
was only allowed to happen
'cause it was bought and paid for
by people like them.
Face it,
no matter how hard you try...
That's always the end result.
What the hell?
You're going in?
Uh, mistress of a senator
we got on the payroll.
Powdered her nose with some bad shit,
died a couple hours ago.
I'm just here to make it scandal-free.
You see what I mean?
Literally nothing can
stop these shindigs,
not thousands dead across the country,
not a lifeless mistress
in the guest bathroom.
Hm.
I guess they got here
sooner than I thought.
Worm-catching motherfuckers, you know?
What's going on?
Who are these people?
This is where we say our good-byes.
- What?
- You're leaving us with them?
As you know, I'm... I'm
only a chaperone here.
Well, what happens now to us?
Well, that will be up to him.
And I got my fingers crossed
he treats you guys all right.
Mr. Markesh...
Ms. Biswas...
please follow me into the garage.
_
What is this?
Take a seat.
Please.
Now...
tell me what you see.
Location confirmed. We're in position.
Repeat: location confirmed.
We're in position.
Be safe out there, boys.
Keep your head on a swivel.
Alpha team approaching
the door. Taking position.
Stand by for breach.
Assault force is on the white side,
ready for primary breach.
A threat analysis
for the FAA's next-gen IP based system.
Targeting IPs in Chicago,
Atlanta,
L.A.
Bravo team set. Holding perimeter.
This is malware
that targets air-traffic control systems
at major airports.
They're planning another attack,
probably like today, except...
this time, they're crashing planes.
Copy, Bravo. Got Alpha and
Bravo teams in position.
But the exploit's already written.
What do you need us for?
- Execute, execute, execute!
- Go. Let's go.
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Alpha team is in. Repeat Alpha team is in.
In the Dark Army,
we understand what it's
like to believe in something.
We're willing to die for our cause,
without thinking twice,
because we know
we are all soldiers
of something much larger.
Please don't kill us.
Please don't do this.
Room's clear.
Bravo team, stand by.
Something else we all believe in:
self-sacrifice,
because when you serve a higher power,
no act is more honorable than suicide.
There is no greater gift
one can offer the cause...
Than everything.
Secure garage, Alpha One.
We can do whatever you want.
Please. Maybe you can use us.
Everything in this room,
from the plans to crash the airplanes
to your very presence,
is only here to tell a story.
Sadly, we have no use for your skills,
but you both do serve
a very important purpose.
- No. Oh, no, no, no...
- No...
No, no, no, don't give me
the gun! No, please don't!
- No! Stop!
- No, please don't!
No! Stop! No!
- Please don't!
- No!
You don't have to do
this. You don't have to...
We got a camera, a few terminals...
We got a body.
- We have a body here.
- Body?
Oh, my God.
Two bodies.
Hold on.
Got a thermal. Find a light source?
One male civilian DOA on
the ground with a handgun.
One female civilian DOA
with a second handgun.
Room is clear.
TOC, be advised, both jackpots are down.
Send in medics.
Alpha team to TOC, area's secure.
We think it might be Iranian.
Alert case squad and ERT.
Got an Iranian flag.
Fsociety masks.
Paraphernalia.
Camcorder.
Like a makeshift studio.
It's over, DiPierro.
I know we would've preferred
to have gotten them alive,
but at least we
prevented another attack.
You're actually gonna
get away with this.