You brought me in to manage him,
and that's exactly what I've done.
- I'm gonna get him a job at Evil Corp.
- _
Doesn't hurt to have him on the inside.
I'm sending shipping requests
to the actual facilities,
but in the manifest,
I'm making it look like
all the paper is still
arriving in New York.
How do you bring
justice to a conglomerate
as untouchable as Evil Corp?
When I met Whiterose,
she opened my eyes,
and I could see how all of the damage
that they've caused
could finally be undone.
- No!
- [MUFFLED GUNSHOT]
Don't you see it yet?
We are gods.
What's that for?
In case Elliot comes back.
He sometimes can become
a different person.
Answer me!
Stay away from me, you fucking psycho.
I like what you did with the place.
Still like mine better though.
You ever think about not
doing this shit anymore?
Can't we just be a normal
couple that complains
about the water bill,
looks up vacation packages to Budapest?
- Hello, E Corp.
- Guys back at CART
are zeroing in on the guy in the video.
We might have a good lead soon.
Your job is to get intel from Elliot
on Tyrell Wellick.
That is the only reason
you're not in jail right now.
- Good job.
- You get anything from Elliot's computer?
Last night he sent an
encrypted email with a link.
[CLANG]
Is that coming from downstairs?
Is Darlene home?
[EERIE, AMBIENT MUSIC]
♪ ♪
♪ Everything means nothing to me ♪
[SUBWAY CAR SCREECHING]
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Hey.
I said "hey."
What's your deal?
Come on, dude, I don't have all day.
What do you want?
Come on, look around you.
The entire train is either
asleep or drop-dead exhausted.
Meanwhile, you're over
here river dancing,
trying way too hard to
pretend like you're in a hurry
to get somewhere we both
know you don't have to be.
Honestly, I don't know
what you're saying.
You have my wallet.
You're batshit.
And you're a terrible pickpocket.
Take out my wallet.
♪ ♪
Take it out, now.
Open it.
♪ ♪
There should be a Polaroid inside.
- Take it out.
- Look, I didn't take anything.
- Just take it back.
- Take out the Polaroid.
♪ ♪
Was that so hard?
Thank you.
Wait, what is this?
Don't you want your wallet back?
It's yours.
Why?
You stole from me, but
I stole from you first.
♪ ♪
That old lady knitting,
that frat dude over there,
I stole from them too.
Everyone.
This whole economic
fuckshow is my fault,
and everything that's happened
to you and everybody else
since Five/Nine, that's my bad too.
♪ ♪
That's not even the cherry on top.
I killed a woman.
♪ ♪
Got her right in the
heart with a stun gun.
♪ ♪
This is me.
[BEEP]
[METALLIC TINKLING]
Wait!
[SOFT PERCUSSION]
♪ ♪
Mr Robot
Metadata.
♪ ♪
The story behind the data.
Getting information is one thing,
but how it was created...
Where and by whom...
Can often be illuminating.
♪ ♪
Who the fuck is that?
- Is Darlene home?
- No, she's out.
♪ ♪
This email wasn't for Tyrell.
It was for us.
Fuck me sideways, how do he know?
He must've phished us
when you went to that URL.
Shit, shit, shit.
Should we bring him in?
What if Darlene gets back?
Like most pics people post
on Instagram or Facebook,
they don't realize they just gifted
whatever social media
site their camera type,
phone model, name, and location,
all hidden inside the
photograph's metadata.
Come on, Darlene, pick
up the goddamn phone.
[PHONE VIBRATING]
[LINE TRILLING]
Oh, Jesus H.
She left her phone downstairs.
[PERCUSSION CONTINUES]
How long ago did she leave?
Doesn't matter. She's back.
It's over.
Our lead asset is about to get burned.
Let's bring him in.
This guy's time is past due anyway.
I never trusted his bug eyes.
If we do that, it'll burn
Elliot's bridge to Tyrell.
It's about to be burned anyway.
♪ ♪
Where are you going?
Don't look at me. Act normal.
Elliot phished us.
He's in your apartment.
Stay cool, don't blow your cover.
♪ ♪
[DOOR CLOSES]
[MUSIC STOPS]
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
♪ ♪
You said you were leaving town.
What are you doing here?
♪ ♪
Since when do you have an apartment?
How can you afford this place?
None of your fucking business.
Leave.
[RADIO CHATTER]
I told you to walk away from this.
And I told you to leave.
We clearly have communication issues.
Let's go. You're coming with me.
- We have to talk.
- Not gonna happen.
I am not going anywhere with you.
♪ ♪
Last night, I noticed
some extra hardware
wired to my monitor's display controller
along with a small cellular
modem taking screen shots
every ten seconds and
sending them out somewhere,
and now I'm standing
here, and I wanna know
why the fuck are you hacking me?
Take another step, and
I will fucking scream.
You're not gonna hurt me again.
♪ ♪
And if it is him that
I'm talking to right now,
then yeah, I hacked you.
I don't trust you, so back the fuck off.
Darlene...
♪ ♪
It's me.
Yeah, well, that's a
pretty complicated statement
coming from you.
♪ ♪
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Dom, get back here now.
Audio's useless.
He's using a goddamn voice protector.
♪ ♪
You should've listened to me.
He is still here, and you
can't keep ignoring it.
♪ ♪
Doesn't mean you hack me, we
don't do that to each other.
You wouldn't talk to me.
What else was I supposed to do?
♪ ♪
He's working with them, isn't he?
I need to show you something.
Mm.
I know, I know, ribs for breakfast,
but I can't pass 'em up when I'm here.
You know, the key is in the moisture.
Here, look.
See that pink in there?
Red Wheelbarrow understands.
Mop sauce... That's their secret.
Layman's version...
Two tablespoons dry rub
to one cup apple cider vinegar,
maybe beer, depends.
Then use a brush to mop the ribs
during the cooking process. Delicious.
You said we needed to talk.
[WANG CHUNG "DANCE HALL DAYS" PLAYING]
Anyone tail you on the way here?
SDRs are now second nature to me.
Did three cover stops, nothing.
Oh, good.
Well, this is just a
little Monday morning
staff meeting update kind of thing.
Today's Friday.
It was a figure of speech.
Point is I received official word...
We go on September
29th, ten days from now.
Now, you know how the boss
feels about timetables.
You said you can manage
those two knuckleheads,
and she put a lot of faith in you.
I'm assuming you can make this happen.
What about the shipping delays?
Well, good thing we have
our guy on the inside, huh?
Help speed things up.
Of course.
We'll make it happen.
Good.
♪ ♪
I wanna be sure too.
We've prepared for an
emergency evacuation
so no one will be in
the building when we go?
♪ ♪
I'm asking.
We have.
Keep us on schedule, all will be good.
♪ ♪
I have to ask...
Did Whiterose ever show you?
♪ ♪
Yes.
And you believe in it?
♪ ♪
Take a look at technology nowadays.
It's mind-boggling.
Hell, these ribs.
You think it was even possible
to cook 'em as deliciously
as this a hundred years ago?
I mean, who knows if
this is even real meat?
As tasty as they are,
I wouldn't be surprised
if they grew 'em in a lab.
I'm not talking about ribs.
My point is, I think
anything is possible.
♪ ♪
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
Did he do this, or...
No, it was me.
I had to do a deep search,
make sure no one was listening.
You were right.
Stage 2 was never called off.
Is Tyrell involved?
Has to be.
They're still trying to blow
up the recovery building.
I've been monitoring traffic at E Corp,
and that led me to an
unpatched web server.
- Talk to me.
- I'm trying to show you.
It's all right here in my research.
Why are you monitoring them?
You could've taken all of this,
sent it in as an anonymous tip,
- and walked away.
- It's not that simple.
Yes, it is.
You don't want to turn them in.
Why?
♪ ♪
Tell me what's going on.
I want to be the one that finds them.
I need to see where this leads.
What does that mean?
♪ ♪
Elliot, listen to me.
This is not who you are.
You don't blow up buildings.
You don't hurt people.
I know.
What is this, then?
♪ ♪
There's something inside
me that can't let go
of what we started.
What we started is over.
♪ ♪
Before, when I was
here, you said you wanted
to stop this.
I need you to go back to that place.
Tell me right now... Can you do that?
♪ ♪
Yes.
Good.
So with that in mind
and with what you have,
how do we find them and just
end this once and for all?
♪ ♪
The best lead we've got is me.
She gave me her keys when we were...
♪ ♪
Landlord never changed the locks,
and it's been vacant.
♪ ♪
So what? You just come in here and hang?
[DOOR CLOSES]
♪ ♪
I get it.
I haven't lost time during the day,
but at night...
That's when you want me to
stay awake and keep watch
on the off chance you turn into Mr. Hyde
and follow you to
Tyrell and the Dark Army.
Hey.
You're my brother.
I'm always here for you.
Besides, if you really
think this is the best way
to find Tyrell...
It's weird, but I guess we passed weird
a long fucking time ago.
I'm in.
[PHONE VIBRATES]
♪ ♪
Shit, I have to get to work.
Whatever he does,
it's not me.
♪ ♪
I know.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
♪ ♪
[ON TV] MAN: Come in.
The last thing anyone wants is some...
- sleazy politician...
- [PHONE RINGS]
WOMAN: Oh, please, come.
It'll be great.
[PHONE RINGS]
MAN: How far is this place?
WOMAN: Just around the corner.
MAN: Oh, right, well,
I just wanted to say...
[PHONE RINGS]
Thank you for the Christmas card.
WOMAN: You're welcome.
Look, I'm so sorry about that day.
[PHONE RINGS]
I came into the room, and
he slinked towards me,
and there was a fire,
and he's the President
of the United States,
and nothing happened...
- I promise.
- [PHONE RINGS]
And I just felt like
such a fool because...
[CRASH]
- FBI, FBI!
- FBI!
- On your fucking knees!
- Hands behind your head!
[PHONE RINGS]
Don't you fucking move!
[RADIO TRANSMISSION]
Don't move.
Don't you fucking move.
[PHONE RINGS]
I sometimes wonder if I'd
died when Tyrell shot me,
would my revolution have died with me?
At first, I thought the
Dark Army saved my life.
They didn't though.
They saved him, Mr. Robot.
And now he's trying to
wage a terrorist attack,
and that excites me.
Why?
Darlene's right.
I could've tipped off the FBI,
given them all this evidence
and let them handle it.
I could just go back to my new TV
and IKEA furniture.
What's wrong with me?
What's that?
Nothing, boring.
It's a scan, encrypt, archive.
It's the new consolidation.
Meeting's next week, I think.
That was a terrible lie.
There's no way she believes me.
Okay.
You're still coming to
the party tonight, right?
I forgot that part of
being a corporate drone
is going to mandated office functions.
Yeah, definitely.
I wouldn't miss it.
Great.
[AMBIENT MUSIC]
♪ ♪
One of these days, you
gotta pound that ass, dude.
Like, I've been out here
splashing everything in sight,
but it's starting to feel
a little lonely in p-town.
Don't let her slip away, all right?
I need you on this.
We know you posted the fsociety video.
With a court order, we got
the Vimeo connection logs
for the account you used,
which led us to your IP address
and then your home address.
That's why you're sitting here.
What my partner's trying to say is
you're on a path to a hell,
and we're not talking
the thousand virgins kind.
We're talking sharing a prison shower
with a few Allah-hating
Nazis on the daily.
You're young.
Don't waste these years behind bars.
All you gotta do is tell
us who's behind this.
♪ ♪
Do you know Darlene Alderson?
Elliot Alderson, do you know him?
♪ ♪
Have you ever worked with him?
Tyrell Wellick, is he your leader?
The tough, quiet kind.
Boys in Gitmo find your
type especially cute.
Whiterose.
♪ ♪
Is Whiterose your leader?
Mr. Nouri, when I get
bored, I get very teed off,
and this silent treatment of yours
is a straight-up sedative.
So this is the last
time I'm gonna ask you,
and, I urge you this
time, do not bore me.
Who is your leader?
♪ ♪
Fsociety.
Just me.
Could have fooled me.
What's with the Armani Exchange getup?
I came from a work party.
Copy that.
You good for the night?
You sure you can stay up?
Just did an eight ball, so I'm golden.
Maybe we should have some sort of signal
when I'm coming and going
so you know it's me.
How about you just tell me?
That's a good signal.
Good night. Wait, are
you going to sleep?
I was gonna walk Flipper first.
Cool, I'll come with.
Okay, so, just thinking out loud,
but, if I do follow him and find Tyrell
and the Dark Army and shit goes down,
like, bad shit, you'd
get vengeance, right?
Like, if I die or something,
you'll kill whoever did it,
and, obviously, I'll
do the same for you.
Like, like a vengeance pact.
Is that even a thing?
It can be our thing.
You in?
Fuck yeah, I'm in.
Cool.
Darlene...
I'm sorry.
I treated you like shit for weeks.
I shouldn't have been pushing you away.
You're my fucking sister.
♪ ♪
I should've believed you.
We've got the fsociety video traced
right to that asshole's apartment.
We got more than half
the FBI across the country
chasing Tyrell Wellick,
and you're asking that yahoo
about the mythical
Whiterose from the land
of Dark Web Fairy Tales?
Come on, Dom, Whiterose
is a boogie man story
for the Dark Army.
Groups like these don't have leaders.
The Dark Army isn't
like any other group.
And I'm tired of being
the only one that questions
their involvement in this.
No doubt they're involved,
but this video is fsociety
to the bone, and ever
since we picked up our guy,
fsociety chatter is off the charts.
Makes sense if they're planning
to make good on their threat,
and we just snagged
one of their operatives.
This guy practically
handed us his location.
I don't like it.
Okay, but isn't every Dark Army member
trained to pull a trigger on themselves
in lieu of getting caught?
Why'd he surrender?
♪ ♪
[SIREN BLARING IN DISTANCE]
[CLICKING]
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[DOOR SHUTS]
[DISTANT CAR ALARM BLARING]
♪ ♪
[MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
[SIREN WAILS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[SUBWAY CARS CLATTERING]
[TIRES SQUEALING]
♪ ♪
I checked with the other facilities.
Elliot's been rerouting the shipments
all over the country.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
[CLATTERING]
[PANTING]
Why am I even surprised?
I told you this would happen.
You know him.
You know he can't be trusted.
He's behind the shipping delays.
This explains everything.
This manifest was a fucking mirage.
[CRASHING]
♪ ♪
And on top of that, you've agreed
to a new timeline?
That was before I
knew about all of this.
I came here to talk about our options.
Options? We have no fucking options!
What happened to your perfect plan?
You placed him at E Corp to
speed up the consolidation,
not to stop it.
We're worse off than where we started.
Why did you even let him
work there in the first place?
It was the best way to manage him.
This doesn't change anything.
This can still be salvaged.
This is all your fault.
No, it's all his fault.
The Dark Army needs
to know what he's done.
You know that you can't tell them.
You understand the consequences.
And not just for Elliot, for all of us.
Well, maybe I can reason with them.
Never appeal to a man's better nature.
He may not have one.
This isn't impossible.
We arrange to have
the western-most states
ship their records by plane.
Our trucks will handle the East Coast.
We just need to stay focused.
Everyone will notice the trucks.
It will draw too much attention.
If we move the paper over the weekend,
we can operate under the radar.
In the meantime, I'll have
Elliot's access revoked
to make sure that he
doesn't interfere again.
What?
You can promise this motherfucker
won't stop us again when
he wakes up in the morning?
You can talk to me.
♪ ♪
Okay.
Face it, Elliot, if that's who
I'm even talking to.
We work nights together for
over six weeks to prepare
this project, but you spend your days
ruining all we've accomplished.
You, as a person, make no sense.
You're a liability.
Our goal hasn't changed.
I can't follow this
back-and-forth anymore.
You had one simple directive...
To maintain control until
the plan was executed.
It doesn't work that way.
There's no on/off switch.
Then tell me, how does it work?
'Cause I don't even know which Elliot
I'm talking to right now.
How it works is I am here now.
Don't forget whose operation this is.
♪ ♪
I once thought you to be a god.
I loved you.
But now I see how foolish I
was and how inferior you are.
Like a fucking cockroach.
You messed up for the last time.
I'm taking over. So, no.
This is no longer your operation.
This is mine. [GRUNTING]
Listen to me, you Swedish scumfuck.
This is my revolution.
I am the architect. Do you understand?
The only reason you are here
is because I allowed you to be.
Don't forget I could've
pulled that trigger twice.
♪ ♪
He is fucking crazy.
I want him out, out!
He's unfit to run this op.
You okay?
♪ ♪
Hey.
Look me in the eyes and
tell me that you're okay.
♪ ♪
Shit.
What's happening?
♪ ♪
He's here.
Angela?
♪ ♪
Why is he here?
Hey, it's okay.
- What are you doing?
- Calm down.
Where am I?
Calm down. Everything's gonna be...
♪ ♪
Please tell me you know what's happening.
It's okay.
Please, tell me you know what's happening.
[GASPS]
Tell me you know what's happening.
[DOOR RATTLES]
♪ ♪
Tell me you have something.
Buy me a drink.
I've been covering
your ass the last week.
You disappeared.
All I've gotten is one text saying
you might have a development,
and now you want me
to buy you a drink?
You almost got me busted
by my own brother, remember?
Yeah, I'm still butthurt about that,
in case you were wondering.
And you never told us
what you two talked about
when he came to the safe house.
Yeah, well, maybe I'm just
tired of being a traitor.
Maybe I just wanna be a normal person
for one fucking minute, okay?
So how about you buy me...
a drink?
[CHVRCHES "UNDER THE TIDE" PLAYING]
You know I could get in trouble
for meeting up with you
like this, one-on-one?
You're supposed to be at the safe house.
Yeah, well, we tried it your way,
and Elliot ended up almost making us.
Okay, now we're trying it my way.
What'll you have?
Bourbon, Eagle Rare, neat.
On her tab.
♪ ♪
Okay, you got your drink.
Now tell me what else you got.
You said you're from Jersey. What part?
I don't have time for Q and As.
My way, remember?
I need to know what you have.
Well, I'll tell you what I don't have.
I nel have no friends.
I have no social contact.
I have no life because of you.
Now, you said you're from Jersey.
You don't fucking say.
What part?
♪ ♪
The world-renown town of Teaneck.
- Siblings?
- Two brothers.
Relationship status?
How many of these do
I have to go through?
Relationship status?
Okay...
♪ ♪
On again/off again with someone,
but they're not really the
one or anything like that.
Ah, the old pronoun game.
I experimented with that for a bit.
It's all good with me.
Thanks for your approval.
It's 2015 now. Why the coded dialogue?
FBI doesn't approve of muff-divers?
♪ ♪
Let's just say it keeps things simple.
Whatever diddles your skittle.
What about you?
Well, my last relationship
didn't end very well.
You were there, remember?
♪ ♪
Shit.
This is why I don't do the social thing.
♪ ♪
Darlene, I get this is tough for you.
We've got a lot of
intel that says something
is happening and soon.
From the looks of it, it could be big.
We need to get Tyrell
before it's too late,
which means you need to tell
me if you know something.
♪ ♪
I think I have a lead, but
I need to go at it alone
- without a wire.
- That's not gonna happen.
Well, tough titties, it's the only way
I'm doing this,
because, when I do this,
and you're all popping
Cristal after you land Tyrell,
understand something...
It's game over for me.
I may have immunity, but
I'm gonna lose my brother.
♪ ♪
No can do, Kathmandu.
This needs to happen by Monday.
But I can't work with him anymore.
Elliot is dead to me.
Our partnership is over.
Uh-huh, and...
Shipping paper records from 71 buildings
across the country to New
York over this weekend?
It would draw too much attention.
That sounds like a YP, not an MP.
I don't know what to tell you.
Whiterose is strict about her schedule.
Be reasonable.
I'm back at the beginning.
Give me more time.
As I said, has to happen on Monday.
Why the change in deadline?
You knew there were delays.
This mad rush isn't worth the risk.
You keep squawking as
if I'm gonna give you
a different answer.
Look, you get this done,
we all take a nice vacation.
I've been looking for some time
- to finish my book.
- You don't understand.
I lost my partner.
We were supposed to be gods
together, but it's over.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Tyrell, I get that you
and Elliot are having
interpersonal issues.
Sometimes coworkers find
that they aren't the right
fit, but they still gotta finish
the job, you know?
Besides, you and I both
know this has nothing
to do with Elliot being a god.
If he is no longer with you,
if he cannot finish the job,
well, that proves one thing.
You are the god, not him.
And I am damn confident
that you will find a solution
to our timing issue.
You were destined for this, Tyrell.
This is your moment.
This is the moment you were born for.
You cannot turn away now.
[AMBIENT MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Yes.
There is a way.
First, the baby monitor.
I haven't been able to connect in weeks.
They must've set up a new system.
Regardless, I want to see
them in person instead.
My wife, my son, and I
will go to the Ukraine, together,
on Monday after the plan is complete.
They don't extradite to the U.S.
I want your word.
I'll get into that.
♪ ♪
Okay.
Do me a favor and check on Joanna.
I've been reading online, and it seems
she's been maintaining a low profile.
Make sure she's okay and
inform her of the plan.
Of course.
And Irving?
There's one last thing I
need in order to execute.
What's that?
♪ ♪
The full force of the Dark Army.
Your message said this was urgent.
I'm coming to you because
I don't have just cause
for this request,
but I need it to happen quickly.
Go on.
I need you to fire Elliot Alderson.
Ban him from any and all
E Corp branches and subsidiaries.
And why do you want me to fire him?
I have my reasons.
Explaining them won't help,
but my discretion on them
is important to me.
And you're comfortable
making this decision?
Mr. Price, I know this random employee
doesn't matter to you.
He's just a number.
You can continue to
question me because you seek
my true reasons, or
you can deny my request
because I'm overreaching.
But I'll return the favor.
You know I'm good for it.
If you want my reasons,
I'll have to restate
what I said.
They are mine, and my discretion on them
is important.
And this is your request?
It is.
♪ ♪
Consider it done.
Thank you.
♪ ♪
You still there?
Yes, it's me.
♪ ♪
[CHUCKLES] Relax, I said it's me.
How are you feeling?
Are you gonna tell me what happened?
We've been over this.
Elliot saw everything.
I had to knock him
out, and now we're here.
I was asking about your phone call.
We're good to go.
Price said yes, but you're
staying here this weekend.
Can't have any more accidents.
He's gonna wake up again.
He saw you and Tyrell.
He only saw us for a few seconds.
Maybe he won't remember.
And, if he does, I'll handle it.
You just do what you do best.
Fight him off.
I told you this would happen.
I told you that he would
find a way to stop us.
Stage 2 has been completely derailed.
♪ ♪
What is it?
Irving.
He says we'll be ready to go on Monday.
[ELLIOTT SMITH "EVERYTHING
MEANS NOTHING TO ME"]
♪ Someone found the future
as a statue in a fountain ♪
♪ At attention, looking
backward in a pool of water ♪
♪ Wishes with a blue
songbird on his shoulder ♪
♪ Who keeps singing over everything ♪
♪ Everything means nothing to me ♪
[KNOCKING]
- DARLENE: Open up.
- [DOG BARKS]
Any day, dude, it's me.
[CLICKING]
♪ In the water showed
an iron man still... ♪
Elliot?
♪ Trying to salute ♪
♪ People from a time ♪
♪ When he was everything ♪
♪ He's supposed to be ♪
♪ Everything means nothing to me ♪