- Hello?
- Bonsoir, Elliot.
- _
- They're planning something.
17 of 71 facilities
around the country so far.
This is where the
paper records are going.
Elliot, what is Stage 2?
The femtocell was to get
access to their UPS's.
They're trying to blow up
Evil Corp's recovery building.
I don't play fair. I play what I want.
_
- I invoke my Fifth Amendment...
- You're an enemy combatant.
You don't have any rights.
One of your patients hacked me.
He stole my dog on top of it.
_
The phone call... make me understand.
I wanted you to feel what I felt.
- You pussy.
- You...
This fucker thinks he can hurt my girl!
If you're serious about
- punishing him...
- I am.
- Just tell me what to do.
- The E Corp party.
When you saw Scott, he was disheveled.
- Yeah, but Joanna...
- Tell the cops your story.
Scott Knowles intimidated
you. This is how we punish him.
That ever-looming presence
that is Mr. Robot, I don't feel it.
Is it possible that
the bullet killed him...
And not me?
I need to find a way to fix what I did.
I need a job at Evil Corp.
You know when you fuck something up
and you wish you had
the power to hit "undo"?
Like when you say the dumbest thing
in front of your biggest crush.
Or when you talk shit
about your boss in an email,
then hit "reply all"
to everyone at work.
Or when you crash the
entire world economy
and kick-start the inevitable downfall
of human civilization?
We all have those days.
But today is not gonna be one of them.
Because today
I found a way to hit "undo".
Today is the day I start
working at Evil Corp.
Hello. I'm Linda,
Chief Human Resources
Officer here at Evil Corp.
Evil Corp is, well, evil.
That much I thought, but
what I didn't realize was
maybe they're a necessary evil
that just needs to be kept in check.
In fact, maybe calling them evil
was just my dorm room
philosophizing run amuck.
I'd like to say welcome
to the Evil Corp family.
We're happy to have you here.
But this doesn't mean I'm selling out.
I'm just growing up.
Signing up for a 401K,
choosing an HMO plan
with a good deductible.
Sign up for Trunk Club.
Pop a few Zoloft.
Join in on the live-action cartoon
of 2D emotions that everyone else is in.
I finally see the fatal
exception error of my ways,
and I know what to do now.
I'm gonna fix the world I broke,
and put it back together
better than it was before.
Let's talk about your crucial
role here at Evil Corp.
I'm gonna undo the hack.
Now, I can't decrypt
the data I fucked up,
that much is true.
But since I'm working
on the recovery team,
I can help them rebuild the database
and defend the fort at the same time.
There's a little talent
roaming around on this floor,
but the primo poon is on floor 31.
As of last week, it looks
like Tyrell was right.
Evil Corp has delivered
their paper records
from 17 of their 71 buildings
to their New York facility.
Pretty sure she would cheat
on her fiance for me, man.
She really... like, the way she
looks at me, dude, it's like,
slippery when wet, am I right?
But lucky for them, now they've got me.
Our current plan is deeply flawed
and massively inefficient.
This is William.
He's my technology manager.
If I can convince him
to convince his boss
to convince her boss
to digitize all the paper records
in their local facilities
instead of shipping them here, then...
We can avoid a single point of failure.
We would install hardware and softw...
Elliot, I hear your passion,
but I got tickets to the
Goo Goo Dolls reunion concert
tonight, so let's wrap this up. Okay?
His password was pretty easy
to figure out after that.
After going through his emails,
I quickly learned that he
was having the engineers
install rootkits on all
of Evil Corp's phones,
so they can illegally
sell private consumer data.
I tipped off the FBI,
got him arrested, and
promptly set a meeting
with the next exec up the chain.
But meetings can take forever to set.
So in the meantime, I
had to look for a stopgap.
In this case, E Shipping,
their shipping management console.
Wait a minute, this ain't right.
All our shipments are
supposed to go to New York.
The paper says "Sioux
Falls, South Dakota."
Yeah, you're in Sioux Falls, Earl,
which sure as shit don't make no sense.
But all right. Unpack her, boys!
I'm sending shipping requests
to the actual facilities,
but in the manifest,
I'm making it look like
all the paper's still
arriving in New York.
It'll take a while, but I
just need to buy enough time
until I can prove my
case to upper management.
By eliminating physical paper delivery,
we can cut E Shipping cost,
installing hardware and software at...
Elliot, you are ambitious,
I'll give you that,
but I got a SoulCycle
class I'm late for.
Let's pick this up
sometime next quarter?
Hacking Peter was as
easy as watching him.
I felt bad taking him down,
until I saw that he
had his engineering team
use special software to help E Corp's
auto manufacturing partners
cheat the emissions test
to hide how much pollution
they really created.
Factoring in the
bureaucracy and the line of
corrupt, moronic managers
I have to get through,
I'll need to keep up the illusion that
shipments are still happening.
These are the same damn
boxes you brought last week.
You know me. I do what the paper says.
All right!
Pack it up, boys!
Problem with my illusion is,
what if Tyrell and the Dark Army
think all the records
actually get there?
This is why I gotta keep
the UPS systems safe too,
because these innocuous backup batteries
in the New York facility
can turn into idle bombs
with the right malware.
And these are the frontline soldiers
trusted to protect them.
You guys gonna stop me?
Uh, I'm a bloodhound, girl.
I just dove right back
in, dude, just... ah.
This patch ensures that the UPS devices
will only run trusted code
that's digitally signed by Evil Corp.
Bottom line: even if they think
all the paper records got here,
they won't be able to
blow up that building.
In conclusion, digitizing locally
and not shipping paper records here
is the best option for
our recovery efforts.
Perfect.
Let's set a meeting with
the VP of Technology.
I want to get this in front of him.
Great work, Elliot.
Once upper management's on board,
we'll be on our way to
rebuilding the database
and the hack will
officially be behind us.
Doesn't mean that in
my spare time I can't
find ways to purge Evil
Corp of all their shitbags.
You know, your typical
subprime mortgage scammers,
Ponzi schemers...
Pension embezzlers,
and sexual harassers.
That way, when Evil Corp
gets back on its feet,
they'll no longer be evil.
We're proud to call you
a new member of Evil... E Corp.
Because changing the world
was never about tearing E Corp down.
It's about making them better.
Maybe I fucked up an
already fucked-up world,
but I'm fixing it now, hitting "undo."
And, friend, it feels great.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Okay, if I'm being real,
I haven't fixed everything.
The loneliness came back.
Worse than I remember.
I don't get it.
I know I'm doing the right thing.
You have to see that.
Then what is this?
Why do I feel this empty void inside?
Even the Zoloft isn't helping.
I don't know what to do.
Fuck.
What's wrong with me?
I'm really starting to lose it.
With everything going on,
my landlord at the office
hasn't been paying utilities
or maintenance, so...
I'll be working from my
home office for a while.
Am I supposed to say something?
It's a nice rug.
Thank you.
How are you feeling
about your birthday today?
Shit.
She's right.
Totally forgot.
It is my birthday today.
Do you have plans tonight?
Uh... no.
In our last session,
we talked about your sister.
We haven't been talking.
Can I ask why?
She's one of the reasons he comes out.
Talk about that.
Well, he's... been gone, right?
He hasn't come out since
I stopped talking to her.
How does that make you feel,
that he's not around anymore?
It's different.
It's better. For everyone.
You're still not answering the question.
How do you feel?
Good.
You miss him, don't you?
It's okay if you do.
I miss being a part of something.
Being a part of what, exactly?
Something important.
That meant something.
Where'd you go?
I remembered this time Darlene and I...
Never mind.
I'd love to hear it,
if you don't mind sharing it.
When we were kids,
this one year, there
was this huge snowstorm.
And Darlene and I were so excited.
And we spent all day
just playing outside.
We made this snowman,
and we called him...
Kevin McAllister,
you know, the kid from "Home Alone."
We were pretty obsessed with that movie.
We even did the hands to the face,
like how he does in the movie.
And how'd that turn out?
He just looked like a snowman
with no arms and weird cheeks.
And we were so proud of it, we promised
we'd steal my dad's camera and
take a picture of it before it melted.
And what happened
when you went back out?
I never got a chance to.
Why not?
That was the day of my accident,
when my dad pushed me out the window.
We were at the hospital
till pretty late.
Your dad pushed you out a window?
Yeah.
I've told you that before.
Elliot, you've never...
No, you've never told me this.
That's weird.
I remember...
I could have sworn I told you.
There's not much to it.
He pushed me out the window.
I broke my arm and went to the hospital.
Kevin melted.
Darlene was pissed.
End of story.
What made you think of this just now?
I don't know.
Truth bombs are coming
your way, Cody-ites.
Tonight, please welcome
our special guest,
Joanna Wellick. Thanks for being here.
Thank you for having me.
Scott Knowles has,
uh, been facing charges
for murdering his wife, Sharon Knowles.
Initially, your husband, Tyrell Wellick,
was accused of the murder,
until you claimed Scott Knowles
confessed to killing his
wife while beating you.
And since then, a bartender
from the night of the party
has also come forward to
corroborate your story.
I know that this must
be difficult for you.
You've been brave just coming here.
Do you want to tell us a
little more about what happened?
My lawyers have advised
me not to speak to that.
But what I can say, Frank, is that
I didn't need Scott Knowles
to be arrested to know
that my husband is innocent.
Mr. Knowles is...
clearly a troubled man
and has been fixating
on us for some time.
I understand that you and your son
have been tormented endlessly
by fanatics and paparazzi.
Some even went so far as to
claim you filed for divorce.
I did file for divorce...
a few months ago.
It was a moment of weakness.
I listened to the wrong people,
who were convincing me that
that was the right thing to do.
But I have and
always will be faithful
to Tyrell.
I have since dismissed
my petition for divorce.
He is...
the only man I've ever loved
and the only man
I ever will love.
In times of chaos and uncertainty,
when the world feels off balance,
we look to those who've stood
with us from the beginning.
Since 1884, we've had America's back.
We may get knocked down, but
we'll never be knocked out.
Still on your side.
Breaking news: a new fsociety video
has been released.
Hello, E Corp.
We are fsociety.
We are here to tell you that
though you survived our first blow,
you will not survive our last.
In the coming weeks,
we will be sending you
a message so loud
that it will make your
eardrums explode...
literally.
The clock is ticking.
We are fsociety.
We are malicious and hostile.
We do not compromise.
You have been warned.
It was released about an hour ago.
Six weeks, you've given us nothing.
And now we have this to deal with?
That video is bullshit.
That video came from
the same Vimeo account
as the last one you guys used.
Then it has to be Dark Army.
Cisco probably gave them access.
But that is not one of our guys,
okay, trust me on this...
You're a CHS.
You understand what that means, right?
I don't understand half the
letters you guys throw at me.
Confidential human source.
Cool. Now I get it.
See what speaking
English can accomplish?
Your job is to get intel
from Elliot on Tyrell Wellick.
That is the only reason
you're not in jail right now.
I don't know what you
want me to tell you, dude.
He's not talking to Tyrell.
How do you know that?
Five weeks ago, the
night we lost your tail...
And then gave us a
bullshit explanation as to
where you went? Yeah.
Stink on that still hasn't washed off.
I asked Elliot
point-blank, and he said no.
If you don't believe me,
bring him in. He'll
tell you the same thing.
You know that telling
Elliot anything about this
would violate the
terms of your immunity.
It would spook his connection to Tyrell.
Get woke already, dude.
He is not nor has he ever
had a fucking relationship with Tyrell.
June 16, 2015.
This is a call from Queensboro
Correctional Facility.
Hello?
Is it really you?
Who is this?
Bonsoir, Elliot.
You're listening to '80s XM radio.
You've been looking in the
mirror the whole drive home.
I need to make a stop.
Stay here.
You want to consider
your actions carefully.
She fucking lied to me.
She went on national television
and she said she still loves him.
You love me!
I know you do!
You told me we were gonna be together.
That's the only reason
I agreed to testify!
You made me lie to the
police to get Tyrell off!
But now I'm gonna tell them the truth!
Get up.
If you retract your
statement, you will die.
I'm not being overly
emotional about this.
It's just that's how little
we care about your life.
Forget this night
ever happened, move on.
Marry a nice, young lady
who actually finds
whatever you are charming.
But understand one thing:
as certain as the pain
you're feeling right now,
there is no option
where you and Joanna ever
see each other again.
Is everything under control?
Yes, ma'am.
He just needed a little clarity.
No, no, no, no, no.
The shooter didn't survive.
The driver looks like
he's gonna pull through.
We have someone down at the hospital,
ready to question,
but he's still in ICU.
This information is too sensitive
to share with the public.
We got lucky we were on the scene
before anyone saw the body.
What about the baby?
Once you contact the next of kin...
We're not contacting them.
He's going to social services.
Don't be soft. Not now.
Her husband is the most
wanted man in the world.
And you and I both
know that finding him is
more important than
anything else, especially
with that goddamn video
that just got released.
Something about that video.
I believe Darlene when
she says it's not real.
We have to assume fsociety's
grown past her at this point.
Yeah, but why wouldn't
she just say that then?
Her whole immunity's
based on giving us intel.
Right now all she wants to
do is protect her brother,
who took a job at E
Corp for Lord knows why.
There's no incentive
for her to lie to us.
She didn't even know he
was working with Tyrell.
Why would you trust her on this?
Because I still think there's
a Dark Army connection here.
We have our other
team looking into them.
Your focus needs to stay
on Tyrell and fsociety.
Guys back at CART are zeroing
in on the guy in the video.
We might have a good lead soon.
Let's just hope you're
reading your girl right.
I'm worried she's a flight risk.
No, she's good.
Trust me.
I'm surprised you came.
Thought you were going the distance
with the silent treatment.
If I remember correctly,
you were the one who
told me to go fuck myself.
Since when did you start
remembering everything so well?
Why'd you text me, Darlene?
What am I doing here?
Wanted to wish you a happy birthday.
Is that all?
God, what is your problem?
Why are you trying to shut me out?
- Because we can't talk.
- Why not?
You know why.
Maybe I want to hear you say it.
Because...
you're my trigger.
What am I, in a fucking therapy session?
Makes sense.
You're my sister, part of my childhood.
If I could take back what
happened to Dad, I would.
What happened to him fucked me up too.
So don't think for a second
our shitty childhood is only yours.
I wish Dad were here right now.
He'd know what to do.
I'm leaving.
First thing in the morning,
I'm gonna crash with a friend upstate.
I can't do this anymore.
I can't be here.
Just thought you'd want to know that.
Spending this last year
with you was never about
whatever the fuck you
want to call what we did.
The real reason I did all of this
was so that we could be close again.
I guess that's...
something else I thought
you'd want to know.
You remember when we
made Kevin McAllister,
the snowman?
Of course.
Do you... do you want to talk about it?
I want you to stay with me tonight.
I'm good, dude, you don't
have to worry about me.
It's not that.
I don't want to be alone.
Given the ripple effect
of rapid global inflation,
19 of the 20 members of
this international forum
have signed the
Five/Nine Economic Accord,
making Ecoin the currency
by which all others will be measured.
The only obstacle
is the illegitimate monetary imposter
that China has unofficially adopted...
Bitcoin.
China is weakening our economic state
by not signing this accord,
and the fact that they
have embraced Bitcoin
shows their resistance
and emphatic rejection
of our collective attempt
to rescue the global economy.
In short,
ladies and gentlemen...
They are declaring a currency war.
This has to be brief.
Truthfully, the only
reason I even agreed to meet
was that this room happens
to be on my way out...
Have your government
sign the goddamn accord!
In 11 days, you'll have what you want.
U.N. vote to annex the
Congo, it's as good as yours,
but this currency war must end.
The rest of the world needs
China to embrace Ecoin now.
We're at risk of other
countries pulling out.
Let me put this as simply as I can,
so that we never have to
belabor this point again.
Your success will always follow mine.
I don't give a fuck about your accord.
Until I get my U.N. vote,
don't waste my time.
Or maybe in 11 days,
the administration changes its mind
about your precious U.N. vote
I worked so hard to procure for you.
Your empty threat reminds me
that there's something
I never shared with you.
My associates found your pet employee
after she smuggled out documents on
the Washington Township plant.
Now that I've gotten a
chance to talk to her,
I can see why you like her.
She makes a very good companion.
And those eyes of hers...
I contemplated firing a
bullet into each of them,
but they're just so hypnotizing.
Don't mistake my generosity
for generosity.
What are you doing?
Why are you awake? It's early.
You're not answering my question.
What were you doing by my computer?
I saw you behind the monitor.
Jesus, I was looking for a pen.
To write you a note.
What's with the fucking paranoia?
A note for what?
I'm leaving. I have to catch my bus.
The buses aren't running.
There's a transportation
strike, it's all over the news.
Okay, the train then.
What's with the interrogation?
You were gonna leave
without saying good-bye.
Thus, the note.
And here I thought we were
in a good fucking place
after last night.
You're not answering
my fucking question.
Why are you here?
What do you mean? You invited me.
Jesus.
It's you.
What'd you do with the computer?
Why did you sleep here last night?
- You're scaring me...
- Answer me!
- Are you serious, Elliot?
- You're hurting me... stop!
- Answer me!
- Why...
- Stop!
Stay the fuck away from me,
you fucking psycho.
So how does it work?
How does what work?
If I wanted you to talk to him.
What happened? Did he come back?
I need you to talk to him.
Didn't you say that that could help?
Everyone's case is different.
But yes,
I think this can help you.
What do we do?
Let's just take a moment.
Why don't you sit back and relax?
I'd like you to close your eyes.
Take a deep breath.
Listen to the sound of my voice.
If you want me to talk to him,
just let him come to me.
Give him permission.
Elliot?
You should know that
nothing's gonna come from this.
We were doing just fine.
It's nice to finally meet you.
This was better when I
could just come and go
as I pleased,
when we were whole.
Now I'm seeing things that
he should be seeing too.
We're just getting torn apart.
You need to leave us alone so
I can get him back to our work.
Elliot never told me
how attractive you are.
You know, for a shrink,
you're, uh, pretty foxy.
Thank you, but...
I'm more interested
in talking about you.
Come on. Never thought about it?
Getting with one of your patients?
That would cross some
ethical boundaries for me.
Sucks for you.
Everybody knows crazy can be sexy.
So you think you're crazy?
Relax.
It's a figure of speech.
Can I ask for your name?
Well, what does he call me?
- Mr. Robot.
- Seriously?
He still calls me that?
Talk about labels.
I'd like to talk about why you're here.
"A civilization which leaves
so many of its citizens
unsatisfied and drives them into revolt
neither has nor deserves the prospect
of a lasting existence."
Who said that?
Freud.
Wow. Beautiful and smart.
Sorry.
As beautiful as you are,
you're not getting inside my head.
Why not?
Because before you found out about me,
we were good.
I'm trying to help him.
You're not trying to help him.
You're trying to destroy me.
I'm not trying to destroy you.
Quite the opposite, actually.
I want to understand you.
You understand shit.
You're just another phony
cooze playing friend.
Eh, it doesn't matter anymore anyway.
Because of her, we've been compromised.
She compromised us, and
Elliot didn't see it.
What do you mean,
you've been compromised?
I'm done talking to you.
Krista?
When are we gonna start?
What happened? Were you there?
Did you go with me or stay with him?
What did you see?
What did Mr. Robot mean,
"We've been compromised"?
You were there, you heard
it along with her, right?
What was Mr. Robot talking about?
Scan my QR code and I'll suck your dick.
Who compromised us? Who's even us?
Him and me? Or him and Tyrell?
No, he couldn't still
be working with Tyrell.
Could he?
Is Stage 2 still on?
No, I would know. That's impossible.
Stage 2 is down. I made sure of it.
Who compromised me?
And why do I suddenly feel so alive?
How do you do it?
How do you get so lucky?
Even when the world's going to shit,
you're sitting pretty.
The truth is,
I never gave a shit about the dog.
In fact, I hate the dog.
Vet bills are through the roof
because this little
piece of shit is sick.
She's been shitting all
over my house for weeks.
It's probably dying.
Figured you wanted her so badly,
let her shit all over your house.
Like you did mine.
Good job.
Stage 2.
I want it to happen on
the day of the U.N. vote.
Whether it goes our way or not.
Sir, Stage 2 is only
meant to be implemented
if Price doesn't come through.
If the U.N. approves our
annexation of the Congo,
we can finally move our operation
to the country's Luwow mine.
Why would you still
want to carry this out,
given the serious implications?
It's time Phillip
Price's hand got slapped.
Last time I buy from that coffee shop.
They only take Ecoin.
Gotta use Ecoin.
With the exchange rate,
dollar's worth shit now.
You get anything from Elliot's computer?
He hasn't logged in all day.
Last night he sent an
encrypted email with a link.
Could be lucky,
could be sending it to Tyrell, right?
Is this from last night?
Oh, also I was able to get
a clean audio recording of his place.
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
He dropped some good intel.
Here, let me play it for you.
Ugh.
That'll be stuck in my head all day now.
Turn it off.
Is that coming from downstairs?
Yeah, that's Darlene's apartment, but...
who the fuck is that?
- Is Darlene home?
- No, she's out.
You think she told someone
about the safe house?
This email he sent from his computer,
did you go to this link?
Yeah, downloaded the file, opened it,
but didn't find anything.
This email isn't for Tyrell.
It's for us.