Tyrell Wellick.
It's gonna be fun working with you.
I think you're beautiful. I want to take you home.
Detectives came by.
They want to speak with you.
They found a body on the roof.
And you both did know the deceased, Sharon Knowles.
our network was compromised yesterday.
That server needs to remain a honeypot.
We have specific orders from Tyrell Wellick
to keep the request as is.
There's a reason we met.
There's something between us. I can see it.
You're not seeing what's above you.
Tyrell Wellick's gone.
I wake up in his SUV and the world's about to fall apart.
We were there to investigate the hack,
and then we were under fire.
What you want, I want it, too.
Someone's trying to make contact with me
25th and 8th.
Stage 2, the femtocell, the back door--
I want it shut down.
I don't want to shoot you, but I will.
I've always told you we'd end up working together, Elliot.
Remember the night of the hack?
Remember what happened to you?
What is it?
It's happening.
It's almost as if...
Something's come alive.
Now wait a minute, Elliot.
Please, we should talk about this.
No!
Did you see what just happened?
Wait, wait, wait!
Do you not understand what just happened?
The only thing that happened is the gun jammed.
It won't happen again.
No, no, no! This is proof. Don't you understand?
- This is proof. - Proof of what?
Proof of what?
When you told me I couldn't see what was above me,
only in front of me.
What the fuck are you talking about?
We...
are gods.
You really are a lunatic.
You held that gun point blank at me and fired,
and yet I'm standing right here talking to you.
What are the chances?
I don't know. But shit happens all the time.
This wasn't chance.
This was an act of God.
And we have been invited into His circle
to lead this revolution.
You haven't been invited anywhere.
You forced yourself in.
There's more to your plan than this.
You're smart enough to know that this hack alone
isn't gonna kill Evil Corp.
Once they realize they can't recover the data,
they'll figure out a way to re-create it,
and that's where you'll need me.
Don't you see it yet?
From the first time we met,
I felt something between us.
This is what I felt.
An uncanny connection, a bond.
We are meant to work together.
That's what this has all been about.
Work together? You're a psychopath.
How do I even trust you?
Pull the trigger again.
ll accept whatever fate decides.
Pull it!
Okay, Looney Tunes.
You're right.
There is a second stage to this.
After tonight,
I don't know what kind of support I'll have.
I could use your help.
Thank you, Elliot.
I love--
Some things are better left unsaid.
Subtext, you know?
Sit down.
Take this.
You might just be the perfect kind of crazy who can protect me...
from me.
- This his car? - Yes.
What time did they arrive?
Shortly after 9:00 P.M.
This your first time seeing the Swede?
This, uh, Tyrell Wellick?
Yes.
What about the rest of their crew?
Nope. No sign of them.
All right, well...
Let's go.
You know the drill.
Let me monologue a little first
and hold off on showing the guns,
unless they get heroic.
Come on.
How's that Pontiac treating you?
Can't complain.
Yeah, well, I told you she was reliable.
They'll spend a couple weeks spinning their wheels,
trying to decrypt the data.
Once that fails, they'll try and collect all the paper records
from the local town halls and banks across the country.
Titles, deeds, loan records, bank statements--
that's our target.
I know which teams at E Corp
will be tasked with this and their procedures.
I'm gonna assume by your funny accent
that you're Tyrell Wellick
Who the fuck are you?
I wouldn't.
Mr. Wellick, I'm gonna need you to answer some questions.
Did anyone see you come here?
Mr. Wellick?
Does anyone know you're here now?
No.
Is that your SUV out there?
Yeah.
- I'm gonna need the keys. - What the fuck is this?
I will get to you in a moment.
Come on, Mr. Wellick.
My requests have been pretty simple so far.
Phone, too.
Do you know how to drive?
- Yes or no question. - Yes.
Good. I'm gonna need you to drive
to, uh, 17th and 6th.
Drop his car off at the parking lot there.
Put this on the dash. Go ahead.
And leave. Make sure no one sees you.
And then go home and lie low.
Okay? All right, Mr. Wellick, come on. Let's go.
No one's going anywhere until you tell me what--
If you're seeing me, that means you boys fucked up.
Apparently, your friend, James--E Corp IT, I believe--
after he completed your honeypot request,
he contacted a Gideon Goddard,
who reported the incident to the FBI tonight,
and then, well...
Do I really need to go any further?
From what I understand,
tonight got a little sloppy joes,
if I'm being kind, which I am.
And if I say no?
Mr. Wellick,
pretty soon you're gonna be the most wanted man in the world.
There will most likely be a manhunt,
the likes of which we haven't seen since bin Laden,
given what you two did tonight.
Now, I am your only shot at staying out of jail.
But, hey, if you want to try to make a go of it on your own,
well, that's on you.
I'll hightail it out of here
quicker than you can finish a box of Swedish Fish.
You should go.
Mr. Robot
How long do I have to be here?
Not sure.
If you absolutely need to contact your wife,
we have secure ways of doing it.
Just give me some time to work on it.
No. No contact.
If I'm gonna be here for a while,
the more distance I create, the--the better it is for me
the better it is for her.
That's the only way I'm gonna make it through this.
All right.
Well, I'll check in on you every couple days,
make sure you're okay.
You're leaving? So what--what about Elliot?
We have work to do.
I'm told that's being worked on.
I'll need my gun back.
If I'm gonna be here alone, I'll need protection.
We own 37 acres of the surrounding property,
all enclosed by ground sensors and
IR motion cameras, wrought-iron gates.
This place is like a chastity belt.
Nothing's gettin' in.
You want to be protected, don't leave the property.
Elliot Alderson. Are you Elliot Alderson?
Mr. Alderson, you're under arrest
for unauthorized use of a computer,
computer trespassing, grand larceny--
And I would be the greatest job president,
ever, in my opinion.
So, this is your house.
One of your houses, I assume.
I've never been to this island.
You know, it doesn't even show up on Google Maps.
You're going back to New York in 22 minutes.
Well, Jesus Christ, you could've called me
instead of putting me on a four-hour flight.
I got a bad L4.
I need you to start an image rehabilitation on Tyrell Wellick.
He's an ex-E Corp employee
who's about to be blamed for the Five/Nine hack.
No matter how public it gets,
it is important that he stays in a positive light.
Any chance Obama goes after him?
People love to defend anything he hates.
Also, there's a new narrative I would like you to explore.
I need you to put fsociety's origin on Iranian soil.
Iran, huh?
That's brown enough. Shouldn't be too hard.
One last thing--
I may have a potential candidate for president
I want you to back.
Now, I've created tens of thousands of jobs over my career,
tens of thousands.
Look, the country's desperate right now.
But you can't be serious.
I mean, the guy's a buffoon.
He's completely divorced from reality.
How would you even control him?
If you pull the right strings,
a puppet will dance any way you desire.
Right? Make America great again.
I say it.
Max, he's interfering with the resonator bomb.
Stop him!
I checked all the elevators, Max, it's not here.
It's got to be. Keep looking.
Mr. Wellick?
I'm Mr. Williams.
Please, come, come. Have a seat.
Would you like some tea?
I brought Soderblandning just for you.
No, I'm fine.
Are you comfortable here? You have everything you need?
No.
I've been here four days by myself.
What's going on? Where's Elliott?
Where Elliot is is an interesting story,
and I've been tasked to come here precisely for that reason--
to explain it to you.
Please sit.
First, I have a few questions.
We understand you were working with Elliot...
On Stage 2 before your bad luck. Is that correct?
Yes. And we need to get started on it.
E Corp might've already begun the recovery program.
We need to start our research.
We can't squander our lead time like this.
Four days is already too long.
Yes, well, uh...
before we commit our resources to you,
I was sent here
to confirm your loyalty to our cause.
This is something we take very seriously
if we're to work with someone at this level.
You mean the Dark Army?
Of course I will be loyal to you.
You're our partners--
Did you kill Sharon Knowles?
What?
I'm not sure I understand.
Don't look away. Look at me.
Did you kill Sharon Knowles?
What does this have to do with--
- Did you kill Sharon Knowles? - No.
- Do you love your wife? - What is this?
- Do you love your wife? - Of course I do!
Have you slept with anyone else since you've been married?
Don't look away. Look at me.
- No. - Will you be loyal to me?
- Yes. - Were you fired from E Corp?
No, I quit.
Are you afraid of becoming your father?
What?
- Do you hate your father? - No.
- Will you be loyal to me? - Yes.
Did you murder Sharon Knowles?
This is enough!
- Did you murder Sharon Knowles? - I said no!
- Do you hate your father? - No.
- Do you love your wife? - Of course I do.
- Were you fired? - No.
- Will you be loyal to me? - Yes!
Don't look away. Look at me. Do you hate your father?
- Are you afraid of becoming your father? - This is enough.
- Were you fired from E Corp? - This is enough!
Did you murder Sharon Knowles?
- Will you be loyal to me? - Yes!
Have you slept with anyone else since you've been married?
Yes.
Have you ever cheated on your wife?
No.
Do you hate your father?
Yeah.
Were you fired from E Corp?
Are you afraid of becoming your father?
Yes.
Did you murder Sharon Knowles?
Yes, yes, yes.
Will you be loyal to me?
No, I will not.
I will not.
But I will always be loyal to Elliot.
You'll need to prep Stage 2 from here
until we establish a more permanent headquarters.
We'll get you everything you need to begin reconnaissance.
You'll receive a phone and a laptop
with a VSAT to a satellite that we control.
Further instructions will follow.
We're naming this op Red Wheelbarrow.
It was Mr. Alderson's request.
But you still haven't told me...
Where is Elliot?
You have a collect call from an inmate
at the Queensboro Correctional Facility.
This call will be recorded and monitored.
Please press one to accept.
Hello?
Is it really you?
Who is this?
Bonsoir, Elliot.
"Death Likes It Hot" by Gore Vida--Chapter one.
The death of Peaches Sandoe, the midget,
at the hands, or rather feet--
In the sideshow of the circus at Madison Square Garden...
You seem frustrated.
It was Elliot. He was acting strange.
Doesn't exactly floor me.
Come outside with me for a moment.
Get a firm stance.
Solid grip.
Swing through the log!
I need to get back to work.
You know, if you're not careful,
you can lose your mind up here alone.
This is the best way to get you centered.
Balance is key.
Let me walk you through another one.
I used to do it as a child.
Why'd you ever stop?
Because I hated it.
Even better.
Here's the femtocell.
The malware's already installed.
Just need you to mod it and do your thing with the antennas.
Cool. I'll hit this up tonight.
Tonight?
Try now, kid. We're on a schedule.
We have some worrywarts back at the house.
Training Angela for this hack has been a bitch.
What's up? You're acting weird.
You ever think about not doing this shit anymore?
Just giving it up?
I mean, can't we just be a normal couple
that complains about the water bill
and looks up vacation packages to
Budapest?
I knew I should've never let you fuck me.
- Okay. - I'm joking, dickface.
Look, we're in the eye of a shitstorm,
and it ain't slowing down right now.
But it will.
Maybe then we can discuss Budapest.
She's antsy for it, so...
make sure you get it back to me soon.
She's a job.
Always was.
If anything gets fucked up,
she's protected, you're not.
Why are you telling me this?
Stop caring about her.
Trust me.
Bye.
That thing needs to go back to the city, ASAP.
There's additional code on here.
The Android malware--
this has nothing to do with our plan.
Why am I even discussing this with you?
Elliot and I should be working on this together.
If we were in the same room, this would've been done.
Are you finished?
How you holding up?
Thought this might cheer you up.
Help remind you of the old country.
Swedish Fish.
I take it you've read the news of your wife's divorce.
Listen...
don't believe everything you read, okay?
Those tabloids-they're always full of shit.
Look how they almost ruined Richard Gere's life,
and he's a damn fine actor.
"Primal Fear," Am I right?
No one who's been emasculated by crushing or cutting
may enter the assembly of the Lord--
Deuteronomy 23:1.
Thanks for getting me the sunglasses.
Freeze! Don't move!
Let me see your hands.
Hands in the air, now!
Yep, I'm looking at him right now.
Yes, sir.
I have the coordinates plugged into my GPS.
I should be there in about an hour.
Yes, sir. U-FAP. We'll keep this on lockdown.
Okay, Mr. Wellick, I need to let you know
that you're being detained locally by me
for unlawful flight to avoid prosecution.
I'll be transferring you to FBI custody,
where you'll be federally charged.
I can't believe it's actually you.
I just had a hunch.
Do you speak English?
You just got me a promotion, you know that?
Before the FBI takes you away, I got to get a selfie with you.
No one's gonna believe this.
You all right?
Finally.
I was thinking you guys were gonna send the cavalry.
You guys and your goddamn cute puzzles.
I could've gotten here sooner if you just gave me the address.
I had to solve a fucking math problem to figure it out.
You're lucky I covered the area
and made sure all the leads on Wellick came directly to me.
But I wasn't planning on killing a fucking cop.
What if he had called it in to the local Barney Fife?
I mean, if you had done your job--
You got to understand where I'm coming from.
Now, I am getting some serious heat at work,
which in my world eventually leads to suspicion--
suspicion because of the events you guys created.
I dodged a shootout in China.
That hasn't gone unnoticed.
Why was there a shootout?
Who the fuck knows? Because your boss is a maniac.
And now, with this FBI hack,
it's left us in a shitstorm over Berenstain.
Shit happens.
Today wasn't our best day, but we took care of it.
"We"?
I took care of it.
Yeah. Right. I forgot.
You guys don't give a shit about me.
Make sure this doesn't happen again.
You fucking weirdo.
Hey, don't mind him.
He's a little snake--
you know, the kind of guy
that will slice your throat when you fart.
So...
you want to tell me what that was all about--
running off like that?
You and I--our stories aren't that different.
I'm not wanted for the crime of the century.
I work a little more subtly.
But we're both married to our jobs...
Whether by nature or by choice.
That said...
my boys were everything to me.
Problem is, I fucked up.
Took too long to realize it.
And when my wife left me,
she took 'em.
- What happened? - I was lost--
as lost as you are right now.
And after chopping a fuckload of wood myself,
I realized I needed them in my life.
But I knew I had to have a lot of patience.
And when the time was right...
I was able to prove to my wife that I was a good provider...
a good father,
a good man.
Now, tonight,
when I get home, my kids are gonna run up and hug me.
We're gonna make Jiffy Pop
and watch "Big Brother" together.
When all is said and done here,
you'll have your chance to fix your situation.
And then your wife and son
will come running up to greet you
at the end of a long day's work.
My wife has to see me as someone strong again.
She has to know I will fix this.
But we have to get this mission back on track.
And that can't happen until Elliot and I are reunited.
Give me a few more weeks,
and I promise...
you'll see him.
- Couldn't close? - Nah, he walked.
What happened?
I'll tell you what happened.
You couldn't relate to him.
Take my thermos, for example.
Yeah, so what? You don't even have kids.
Point is, people want a connection.
Makes you more trustworthy.
You walk around with one of these,
and all of a sudden, you're that corny guy
who's proud of being a father,
helps them buy what you're selling.
Yeah. I'm gonna go in for the night.
Next time, make the sale.
So how'd it go?
It was cool.
Got to stab up a bunch of neo-Nazi motherfuckers to death.
You know, not that I'm a fan of murderin' and shit,
'cause I respect life and all,
but when it come to neo-Nazis...
Well, shit,
not gonna lie-- it was kind of fun.
I mean how'd it go with Alderson?
He got his papers.
Should be out soon.
By the way, get him laid when he gets out, man.
Homeboy is wound tighter than a chinchilla's asshole.
Go get packed.
He's being released.
It's perfect. He will love it.
Now, I'm giving this back to you
for safe keeping.
The barrel was jammed. Squib load.
Next shot would've blown your hand clean off.
Lucky for you, I took care of it.
So this is how the meet's gonna go down.
We've reached out to Elliot,
and you will be given further instructions
as soon as he makes contact.
Until then, we're gonna need you to stay here
so you'll be near the rendezvous point.
Now, you'll give our driver the address.
He won't know where you're going until you tell him.
If you get hungry, just call for room service.
Oh, stay away from the windows, okay?
We can't take any chances now that we're in the city.
- Okay. - Wait.
What about my suit?
- Tyrell, we discussed this. - I need it.
It's nonnegotiable.
I have to look my best for him.
It's in your closet.
I still strongly advise against wearing it.
You know, this isn't bumfuck nowhere.
You get picked up around here,
we can't protect you.
Mr. Willick, it sounds like someone's here downstairs.
I'll be right down.
- You Elliot? - How do you know my name?
No Elliot?
No, no, okay. Wait.
Chambers and Church.
We have to be careful now.
They said he's going to be okay.
You need to sit down.
When he wakes up, you shouldn't talk to him.
I will handle this.
He should be in a hospital.
The conditions here aren't suitable.
- It's--it's-- - He's in good hands.
I don't understand.
He and I were meant to be a team,
but he kept saying I wasn't real.
He said he didn't see me,
but I was standing right in front of him.
We were talking.
So why would he say I wasn't real, hmm?
I don't understand.
I just don't understand.
It was almost as if he were a different person.
Tyrell...
- He is-- - Tyrell.
There's something that I need to tell you about Elliot.
You're right.
He sometimes can become a different person.