Anything we do,
he will try to slow us down.
As long as he exists,
he will stop us.
Today is the day
I start working at Evil Corp.
I can help them
rebuild the database
and defend the fort
at the same time.
This patch ensures
that the UPS devices
will only run trusted code.
Bottom line, they won't be
able to blow up that building.
U.N. vote to annex the Congo,
it's as good as yours,
but this currency war must end.
Stage 2, I want it to happen
on the day of the U.N. vote.
Protesters have
surrounded the building.
Summon as much NYPD
as is necessary.
You know that telling Elliot
anything about this
would violate the terms
of your immunity?
I think I have a lead,
but I need to go at it alone.
I may have immunity,
but I'm gonna lose my brother.
- Stage 2 was never called off.
- How do we find them
and just end this
once and for all?
The best lead we've got is me.
Irving, he says
we'll be ready to go on Monday.
We've prepared for
an emergency evacuation.
We have?
I'll have Elliot's
access revoked.
I need you to fire
Elliot Alderson.
Consider it done.
You okay?
- What's happening?
- Angela, why is he here?
Everything's gonna be okay.
Elliot saw everything.
I had to knock him out.
You're staying here
this weekend.
We can't have anymore accidents.
He's gonna wake up again.
He only saw us
for a few seconds.
Maybe he won't remember.
Aller Anfang ist schwer.
Anfang ist anfang.
One, two, three four
One, two, three,
four, five, six
One, two, three, four
Five, six, seven, eight
To relay to
the Syrian President.
But Putin's stance
is that it would be a mistake
to abandon
the current government.
Meanwhile, the U.N. Security
Council has gathered today
for a much talked about vote,
the People's Republic of
China's proposed annexation
of the Democratic
Republic of the Congo.
As the world awaits
the result of the vote,
many questions are being raised:
What does it mean...
For the relationships
between world superpowers
and impoverished nations?
One, two, three, four
Five, six, seven, eight
Elliot?
Isn't that your phone?
Is it?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Hello?
Finally, I've been trying
to reach you all weekend.
Are you at work?
- Yeah.
- Don't go anywhere.
We need to talk, in person.
Meet me downstairs.
I'll be there in ten.
Okay? It's... it's important.
Is everything okay?
Everything's fine.
Hey...
we should grab lunch later.
Something isn't right.
Like something
slipped away from me.
What is it?
I can't put my finger on it.
What am I even doing here?
I'm arriving at work.
I'm walking toward my cubicle.
I'm just on autopilot,
running my routine.
Did my daily program crash?
When code runs,
it should run straight through
without interruption,
until all of its tasks
have been completed.
Unless something goes wrong.
A runtime error.
Sometimes, corrupted memory
can lead to one.
Is that what's happening
to me right now?
A runtime error?
Yo, what up, E?
I barely made it past
those protesters this morning.
I mean, the natives
are getting restless.
This shit's crazy AF, right?
Is it?
Hey, so I had
a piece of tang this weekend
you are not gonna believe, dude.
I was unlocking achievements
Saturday night
that went all the way through
to Sunday morning.
I even impressed myself.
Every morning starts like this,
graphic sex talk.
Thankfully, I'm able
to tune most of it out.
When people talk like this,
they're either insecure,
or they're full of shame.
Which one do you think it is?
I...
Sorry.
Shit. That was meant for you.
I'm really off today.
I mean...
Jesus, Elliot, I, um...
You know what, man? Fuck you.
I'm just trying to
brighten up your day
with my dopeass anecdotes,
but if you don't appreciate it,
I can just sit here in silence.
Really?
Is this gonna end up being
a beautiful accident?
No... no, I'm...
I'm sorry, bro.
I shouldn't have said that.
Spoke too soon.
I'm bigger than this, man,
and, in a way,
what you just said
actually helps me,
'cause I've always wondered
if people here thought I was
just trying to get attention,
but I was like, "Nah."
But I should've
started the day off
by asking what you did
this weekend.
He does raise a good question.
What did I do this weekend?
Instead I'm always just
rambling around some bullshit.
But you know what, I'm gonna
drop some truth on you, dude.
Since we're opening up here, I...
I've only ever
gotten laid twice.
Okay, actually,
it was 1 1/2 times,
but the first time, it was...
It was one of those highend
escorts, dude, a courtesan.
I saw her at the Plaza Hotel...
And actually, she saw me, dude.
She totally was hitting on me.
It cost me, like,
two weeks' pay.
I know what I did this weekend.
I rehearsed my proposal.
I have a big meeting with
the VP of Technology.
I've actually never had
penetration, dude.
I've never penetrated.
I just... I...
I went to one of
those rub and tugs...
No, wait,
I already had that meeting.
That was last week.
What happened this past weekend?
I just kept thinking
she was one of those girls
that got kidnapped
and was forced to do it.
I was, like, thinking of
her family the whole...
Hey, dude, thanks for
letting me confide in you.
Just don't tell any of
the guys about this. Cool?
It's hard what he just did...
- Yeah...
- Opening up facetoface,
which is why
I probably talk to you.
Why is my account locked out?
E Corp Help Desk.
Hey, I got locked
out of my account.
Can you do
a password reset for me?
Can I have your employee number?
072391.
Please hold.
My work email is
prompting me for a password.
Did someone try
to get on the domain
as me too many times?
Or has E Corp locked me out?
Did they discover
my shipping hack?
I need to check
my monitoring server.
Hey, Samar...
Samar, I got locked out.
Can I hop on your machine
to check something real quick?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, sure,
go for it.
Yeah...
Is this that bad feeling
I have looming over me?
Is this why today
doesn't feel right?
An update failure.
No, this can't be happening.
Maybe something's wrong
with my dashboard.
I need to check the full log.
Shit. This morning at 6:07 a.m.,
the Dark Army
tried to run Stage 2.
My patch stopped them,
but it doesn't change the fact
they're trying to blow up
the downtown building today.
Damn, dude, Bobbi from HR
is rolling up with Security.
Wonder who they're axing.
Mr. Alderson,
thank you for waiting.
I looked into this.
It looks like we cannot
restore your account
at this time.
Is there anything else I can...
Samar is right.
HR is firing someone.
Me. Fuck...
I can't leave the building
until I get back on a machine
and figure out
how they're planning on
getting around my patch.
Samar, I need you
to distract them for me.
Wait, what?
Help me figure this out.
Do not leave me. Stay focused.
Excuse me,
I had a question for you...
We're looking for
Elliot Alderson.
Do you know where he is?
Yeah, yeah, he's on floor 11.
You know, they have
the best bathrooms,
and he likes to take his
morning dump around this time.
Samar, you need to
be serious right now.
We have talked about these
microaggressions of yours.
I am being serious.
He told me he was crowning
his whole commute.
He was just here.
We need eyes on Elliot Alderson.
Elliot, I didn't know
if you'd be here.
- Janet, I...
- Great news on your proposal.
Starting with
the Southwest region this week,
all paper records
will be digitized locally.
I tried to find you on Friday.
I... you weren't in.
I wanted to congratulate you
in person.
Before we know it,
the database...
Did you hear what she said?
I wasn't in Friday. Where was I?
When did my program halt?
Why can't I remember? Wait...
- Mr. Robot...
- Mr. what?
What day is it today?
You know it's gonna be
a long week
if you gotta ask on a Monday.
Is everything all right?
Janet, I can't talk right now.
There's an I.T. emergency on 29.
Last thing I remember
was the E Corp party.
That was four days ago.
Did Mr. Robot really
take over for that long?
Don't look up. Security cameras.
That's right. Darlene.
I remember now.
She was supposed
to follow me... him.
You know what I fucking mean.
She must've seen Mr. Robot.
Darlene...
I can barely hear you.
It's a madhouse down here.
You were gone all weekend.
You left Flipper alone. I had
to give him to your landlord.
Listen to me. Did you follow me?
Did you see him?
Okay, just come downstairs.
I'm getting fired.
I can't leave until I've...
Ma'am. Check the stairway.
Elliot? Elli...
I'm going to get him.
All I know is it's been
six fucking weeks,
and I haven't had
a weekend with my son.
I did trade the car.
I'm taking the subway. So what?
I'm picking him up
from school today.
They cut my access privileges.
I completely disagree.
I think he definitely loves me.
Sir... Sir...
Are you gonna really
get into that right now?
That was one time
I told him I hated him.
I'm going to attract attention.
I have to remain calm.
Take deep breaths.
Be cool.
Don't panic.
Slow everything way down.
Blend in.
Look bored, broken.
Get a blank office stare
on my face.
This is how they do it,
isn't it?
How they're able
to watch the world
fall apart around them?
Because to them, this is normal.
It's all they know.
Maybe I can learn from them.
I wish I could see myself
through your eyes.
Don't you wish you could
see yourself through mine?
As we step through our code,
line by line,
debugging it to find the cause
of our runtime error.
What am I doing?
I'm still attracting attention.
I'll still get caught,
and it'll be
painfully slow to watch.
This isn't gonna work.
We need to find an open space,
a network jack.
God damn it, it's the start
of the work week.
Monday morning attendance:
All of the conference rooms
are booked,
and all of the cubicles
are full.
I'll have to get someone
off their work station.
Here...
She's the perfect candidate.
Hi, Edie, I'm Henry from I.T.
- Hello.
- We've detected you using
some unauthorized
remote access software
to connect to your computer
work station from home.
My. That can't be true.
Don't worry, I'm just gonna
take a look at your machine
and perform an assessment
to make sure you don't have
an unauthorized desktop
sharing service installed.
Well, I'm gonna
have to contest that.
I've hardened my install
further than the standard
configuration,
including a restrictive
host base firewall rule set,
and whitelisting to block
unauthorized apps from running.
I might've chosen
the wrong candidate.
I think I know your culprit,
though.
Fred over there
uses GoToMyPC all the time.
Let me introduce you.
Fred...
You loused it up again.
Hi, Fred.
Henry from I.T. Are you serious?
You gotta take a look
at my machine now?
I just got in.
Listen, I just need it
for 15 minutes.
I'm... I'm backlogged here, man.
I got my supervisors
giving me deadlines.
This isn't a matter of debate.
Whatever.
I'll be in the break room.
Log data from the Dark
Army's backdoored machine.
They're using this guy's
account: Frank Bowman.
He's a member of the code
signing architecture team.
This is what they're doing.
They wanna sign their own
firmware and bypass my patch.
If they do that, they'll blow up
the downtown recovery building.
My only chance to stop it
is to get to the hardware
security modules, the HSMs.
They're on the 23rd floor.
No, I haven't seen him.
Did he just come in?
Hi. How are you?
One sec, I'm just
finishing up an email.
I think that
you're in the wrong...
Almost finished.
All right...
Excuse me, very important memo.
We should get started.
I think you're in
the wrong room.
I'm sorry, you are?
- Sean, head of Sales.
- Sean. Of course.
Dave Kennedy.
I work with Craig
on the Q4 push.
I had longer hair then.
Listen, we're on a deadline.
We don't have time for this.
You are in the wrong room.
Well, maybe there's been
some confusion,
either on your end or mine.
What room did you say this was?
You know, I think
that's my room.
No.
All right,
let me check my calendar.
Service has been
spotty all morning.
All right, here it is.
You're right, so embarrassing.
I'm not supposed
to be on 44, 12C.
Yeah, I'm down one floor,
I should've known.
We always have
chocolate donuts too.
Jesus Christ,
you have wasted
enough of our time already.
We need to get started.
You know, Sean,
sometimes I get a lot like you,
where you have a lot of anxiety,
because of a deadline,
you know, where you feel
pressure, because...
something has to get done.
And then,
all of these damn little
unknown variables
keep popping up.
And when you find yourself
at the center of
one of those storms,
man, you just gotta breathe.
Just let go.
Get it done.
Mr. Alderson!
Hey, stop!
Mr. Alderson, stop!
St...
Shit,
I'm going through the lobby.
Security will force me out.
What should I do?
What would you do?
That's right,
you never answer me.
Is this why I created Mr. Robot?
To help me get out of
situations like this?
At least he interacts with me.
If Mr. Robot was here,
what would he do?
First thing he'd tell you
is to stop talking
to your imaginary friend.
You're not really him, though.
Would you stop trying to be
so technical about everything?
You know if he were here,
he'd tell you
exactly what he told you
when he said
to walk away from Vera.
This is a zerosum game.
Accept the truth.
That building
is going to blow up,
and there's not a damn thing
you can do to stop it.
I'll find a way
to destroy the HSMs.
Once I do that,
there'll be no way
for the Dark Army
to run Stage 2.
How are you gonna do that?
You're about to be
kicked out, Einstein.
So the real question is,
can you get to the HSMs
before they do?
All I need to do is get
to the ground floor.
Once I'm there,
I'll find a way to get back in.
With the security they have?
I'll tailgate someone.
Hate to see it, kiddo,
but you'd have better luck
tailgating the parking lot
at a YoYo Ma concert.
They got all their peepers
peeled for you.
- I know my way around.
- Even if you do get up there,
you got Bobbi and her
Keystone Cops looking for you.
You'll never get away with that.
And while you're busy
spinning your wheels,
trying to prove
that piece of wisdom wrong,
the recovery building's
going to explode,
and the people inside
right along with it.
He's right.
I need to worry about
the people in the building,
not the HSMs.
But there is no he.
That was just my imagination.
We haven't seen
each other in months.
We've been battling each other
in our own voids.
But at least now
I know my next move.
This is what
democracy looks like!
Elliot Alderson,
we've been instructed
to escort you off the premises.
Show me what
democracy looks like!
This is what
Show me what
democracy looks like!
This is what
Show me what
democracy looks like!
This is what
Show me what
democracy looks like!
This is what
E Corp Recovery Center.
How may I direct your call?
Listen, there's gonna be
a buildup of hydrogen
in the data center.
Sir, I'm having
trouble hearing you.
Would you like me to
connect you...
You've gotta get everyone
out of the building now.
A spark will ignite the hydrogen
and bring the whole place down.
Have someone look at
the battery room
for your UPS devices.
Sir, UPS?
We use E Shipping
for our freight services here.
Would you like me to
transfer you to the warehouse?
There's a fucking bomb
in your building.
Clear everyone out now.
Hopefully that gives everyone
enough time to get out.
Now all I need to do
is find a way to...
Elliot!
You've gotta help me
get back inside.
I have to tell you something.
There's a code signing
machine on 23.
We have to find a way to...
I'm working with the FBI.
After Cisco,
when the FBI questioned me,
they did more than that.
They had everything
laid out on this board:
Us, Angela, Trenton,
Mobley, everyone.
They had been following
our every move for months.
They knew everything.
And Tyrell, they think
he's at the center of it all.
Wait... wait a minute.
Back up.
This... this has been
going on since Cisco?
You've been working with them?
The FBI?
Why didn't you tell me?
I made a deal for us.
- All they want is Tyrell.
- What?
What deal?
Is that why you hacked me?
For them?
What's going on?
Are you wearing
a fucking wire right now?
No.
No, they don't even know
that I'm here.
Elliot,
I'm telling you the truth.
The truth?
You've been working with
the FBI behind my back?
You've been spying on me?
Am I to blame for this?
Not telling her
how much I miss Mr. Robot?
How a part of me may have
let all of this happen?
The other night,
I followed you
like you asked me to.
He snuck out of the apartment
around 2:00 a.m.,
and met up with Angela.
She knew it was him.
I think the two of them
have been working with...
Tyrell.
That's it.
My runtime error.
I saw her...
And him.
I was standing in a room...
and they were together.
Angela is the one behind this.
I gotta stop her.
Angela's been betraying you?
So have you.
You kept this from me.
You've been trying to play me
this whole fucking time?
This is what
democracy looks like!
Show me what
This is what
democracy looks like!
Show me what
This is what
democracy looks like!
- Four, three, two, one...
- We are live.
This is what
democracy looks like!
Okay, we've live in five,
four, three..
Thanks, Jack. I'm here
outside E Corp headquarters,
and while it's typical
to see daily protesters,
it's unusual for the crowd
to be this size and this vocal.
An NYPD official told me
they're taking the situation
very seriously,
and sending in additional units
for crowd control.
What's less clear is why today.
With an alltime high
unemployment rate of 26%,
giving many citizens
something to march about,
most of the protesters
I spoke with
did give me varying answers
as to why they're here.
From forced currency changes
to corporate greed
and corruption,
I even had one gentlemen tell me
he was here to protest
this morning's U.N. vote,
that he felt it was
somehow connected to E Corp.
This is what
democracy looks like!
Show me what
This is what
democracy looks like!
Show me what
This is what
democracy looks like!
Show me what
This is what
democracy looks like!
Show me what
This is what
democracy looks like!
Show me what
This is what
democracy looks like!
Settle down!
This is what
democracy looks like!
Everybody!
Settle down!
Everyone!
Everyone...
Scan your badge.
I said scan your badge now!
Tensions are running high,
as the United Nations vote
approaches.
While no one can predict
whether today's resolution
will pass, all five
permanent members,
China, France,
the Russian federation,
the United Kingdom,
and the United States
must be in unanimous agreement
for the measure to be adopted.
One, two, three, four
One, two, three,
four, five, six
One, two, three, four
Five, six, seven, eight
One, two, three,
four, five, six
Yeah! Got it, whoo!
Please stay on your floor.
Lock all doors, and find
your nearest safe zone.
Stay away from
elevators and stereos
until further notice.
This is Angela.
- Blankenship.
- Mentor.
Walk toward the elevator
bank on your floor.
There's a package waiting
for you at the reception desk.
Has your name it.
There's something going on.
I don't think
I can leave my office.
That's our distraction.
What do you mean
your distraction?
Get moving.
We don't have a lot of time.
This is an emergency.
Please stay on your floor.
- What's going on?
- Ran into a bit of a snag.
We're gonna need you
to go ahead and have
Elliot implement
our contingency plan.
Elliot?
What contingency plan?
He needs to get to
a computer called a, HSM,
make a backup of it.
Once we get that,
we'll be good to go.
Come on, let's go, let's go!
I got the package.
Good.
Take the package to Elliot.
It contains
all the hardware he'll need.
He'll pose as a member of
the internal audit team
based out of Detroit.
Everything he needs to know
is on a sheet of paper inside.
He'll get it done.
Call me when it's finished.
Attention, all E Corp employees,
this is an emergency.
Please stay on your floor.
Lock all doors, and find
your nearest safe zone.
Stay away from
elevators and stairwells...
Ma'am, what are you doing here?
It's not safe for you
to be on elevators.
I was, um...
I'm trying to get
to my office on 23.
There's a secure room
and a safe zone on 23
with no windows.
I'll take you there.
Okay. Thank you.
As no permanent members of
the council voted against it.
The draft resolution contained
in document S/2015/511
hereby passes,
allowing annexation
of the Congo by China.
I will now open the floor to
members that wish to extend...
This is Murphy.
I'm on elevator 4.
We just lost power.
I'm stuck between
floors 26 and 25.
Don't worry,
they'll sort it out.
We'll be fine.
What's in the package?
Hopefully
it's something we can eat.
We may be here a while.
Hard drives.
Probably not
the healthiest choice.
Here, let me help you with that.
No, it's okay.
What the heck is this?
It belongs to my direct report.
He... he ran out of a meeting
and left his badge
in a conference room.
I'm bringing it back to him.
Interesting that
your direct report
has special access
and you don't.
You're gonna have to
come with me.
Attention, all E Corp employees,
this is an emergency.
Please stay on your floor.
Lock all doors, and find
your nearest safe zone.
Stay away from
elevators and stairwells
until further notice.
I really should,
head back to my office.
It's actually just
right back there.
No, no, no, no, no, we're
gonna straighten this out.
Hey! Over here!
Douchebag!
- Hey, over here!
- Go, go, go!
Attention, all E Corp employees.
This is an emergency.
Please stay on your floor.
Lock all doors,
and find the nearest safe zone.
Stay away from
elevators and stairwells
until further notice.
This is the police!
Do not attempt
to cross the line.
This is the police.
Do not attempt
to cross the line.
Where's the USB key?
Attention,
all E Corp employees...
Fuck... Come on, come on,
there's gotta be one
around here somewhere.
Hey.
Fuck, you scared
the shit out of me.
Sorry.
Have you seen
what they're doing out there?
- It's insane.
- Yeah, I know.
You okay?
Yeah, I am now.
Wait...
How did you get in here?
I'm a part of
the internal audit team,
out of Detroit.
Was in the middle of
an unannounced
physical security audit
of the code signing operation.
You fucking bitch!
Thank God.
Yeah...
Attention, all E Corp employees,
this is an emergency.
Please stay on your floor.
Lock all doors, and find
your nearest safe zone.
Stay away from
elevators and stairwells
until further notice.
Yeah!
This great country didn't
start out with 50 states,
so why stop at 50 states?
And, let me add,
that this is why we need a man
with a business acumen like
Donald Trump as President.
If China makes another move
like they did today,
our standing
as a world superpower
will be put into question.
Mr. Trump has the drive,
the ambition to help us...
- Marlinspike.
- Moxie.
It's done, but we got a problem.
I was made.
There was a woman
in the CSAT room.
She saw me.
Wait, why were you in
that room instead of Elliot?
I couldn't find him.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Your distraction
is fucking overkill.
I couldn't find him in
the middle of a goddamn riot.
Your men came after me.
Well, they're not all ours.
Just 'cause we lit the fuse
doesn't mean
we control the explosion.
You weren't supposed to be
on that floor anyway.
You said you wanted it done
immediately, so I got it done.
This woman who saw you,
did you get her name?
Lydia Riley.
We'll take care of it.
So, you were able
to follow everything
on that sheet of paper?
Angela, if you didn't do
everything on that list...
Yes, yeah, I got it done.
Good.
There's a delivery man
waiting for you
at Reception on your floor.
Give him the package
with everything in it.
Irving?
Are you still gonna evacuate
the Recovery Center?
That's been done already.
- So this is really happening?
- We need you to stay strong.
It's like you said,
she can make all of this better.
This is a step toward that.
Remember the cause.
Attention, all E Corp employees,
this is an emergency.
Please stay on your floor.
Lock all doors, and find
your nearest safe zone.
Stay away from
elevators and stairwells
until further notice.
Attention, all E Corp employees,
this is an emergency.
Please stay on your floor.
Angela...
Is there something
you wanna tell me?
Attention, all E Corp employees,
this is an emergency.
Please stay on your floor.
Lock all doors, and find
your nearest safe zone.
Stay away from
elevators and stairwells
until further notice.
Attention, all E Corp employees,
this is an emergency.
Please stay on your floor.