I need you to keep an eye on me
You're the only person I can trust.
This is
what democracy looks like!
Elliot,
I'm working with the FBI.
You've been spying on me?
The other night,
I followed you.
He snuck out
and met up with Angela.
Stage 2... I want it to happen
on the day of the U.N. vote.
It's time Phillip Price's
hand got slapped.
This morning at 6:07 a.m.,
the Dark Army
tried to run Stage 2.
They're trying to blow up
the downtown building today.
We need to get Tyrell
before it's too late.
My wife, my son, and I
will go to the Ukraine
- after the plan is complete.
- I'll get into that.
Everybody...
This is a zero sum game.
Accept the truth.
The Recovery building's
going to explode,
and the people inside
right along with it.
Angela's the one
behind this.
I gotta stop her.
- I got it done.
- Oh, good.
Irving, are you still gonna
evacuate the Recovery center?
That's been done already.
I'm Emily Moss's daughter,
Angela Moss.
I'm here to discuss
the Washington Township case.
Dad, what's going on?
I'll let you two talk.
26 employees died from
similar types of leukemia.
Evil Corp killed my mom,
and my whole life,
I've always wanted justice...
for her death.
CREDITS
I think I've seen
this one, yeah.
Elliot has these on VHS.
Is Elliot here,
Mr. Alderson?
No, he didn't...
he didn't come.
Why?
Well, I guess he wasn't
feeling up to it.
I don't wanna
be here, either.
There's a lot of
nice people visiting.
Are you sure you don't wanna
join the party?
We got this cake.
Red Velvet.
Not hungry.
You know,
if that were me over there,
I would want Elliot and Darlene
to come over and talk to me.
But I don't want
to talk to her.
You remember the, uh,
Enchantment Under the Sea dance
in the first
"Back to the Future" movie?
Marty had to push his dad
to ask Lorraine to be his date.
And if George didn't
overcome his fear,
they would never
have gotten married,
and Marty would never
have been born,
and he would've disappeared
from that photograph, right?
I guess so.
I know it's scary,
but I also know
that you can do it.
Just might need a little push.
That's all.
Hey, Angela,
somewhere down the road,
if Elliot needs some help
and...
I can't
be there for him...
Just give him
a little push too, okay?
Okay.
- You understand?
- Of course, Emily.
Also, I know
we discussed it before,
but I wouldn't be doing my job
if I didn't bring it up again.
It's about the anonymous
benefactor who keeps...
- I'll let you two talk.
- Don...
Sorry, did I say something
I shouldn't have?
Not at all.
You're fine.
Well, he reached out again,
offering to pay for your...
That's very nice of him,
but I've made my decision.
No more treatments.
I wanna spend
what time I have left
with my friends and family.
Just know that there's still
people fighting for you,
for your family.
We're gonna continue
with the lawsuit
and do everything we can
in your name.
Hey, you.
Hi.
What do you think
of the party?
This isn't fun.
It's weird.
Weird how?
It's okay.
You can say it.
- I'm dying.
- I don't want to.
I hate this.
- I hate all of it.
- Angela...
you know this isn't
good-bye, right?
No, I know what dying is.
You're never
gonna see us again,
- not Dad, not me...
- Mm, no, listen,
I am always gonna
be there for you,
no matter what.
You wanna know what I believe?
What?
That this isn't the end,
that there's another world
out there for both of us,
that we'll see
each other again.
And we'll play and dance
and... bake and sing.
Doesn't that sound beautiful?
Will you believe with me?
Angela...
Attention.
Is there something
you wanna tell me?
This is an emergency...
I don't know
what you're talking about.
I saw you.
The 23rd floor.
You were at
the code signing machine.
What did you do?
We need to let today happen.
They're blowing up
a building.
Yes, I know.
And you're okay with that?
How long have you been
working with Tyrell?
- What did he tell you?
- None of that matters
right now.
This whole time...
I thought you were helping me,
but you've been...
you've been manipulating me!
This is what you wanted.
After today,
your revolution succeeds.
You just need the courage
to see it through.
You sound like him.
You, you mean.
I need to stop this.
Today's work,
what White Rose is doing,
is going to change everything
for the better.
You met White Rose?
What the fuck is happening?
She's going to save the
world, but we need to let her.
Save the world?
Angela, whatever White Rose
told you is a lie.
She's a fucking terrorist,
and if you let this happen...
Then we're going to
look back
and see that these consequences
were necessary...
- People are going to die!
- No, they're going to be fine!
Including your father
and my mother.
What the fuck
are you talking about?
You're not making any sense.
Angela...
Listen to me.
Whatever you pulled
off of that machine,
I need you to give it to me.
- Now.
- I can't.
- I don't have it anymore.
- Where is it?
Who did you give it to?
Tell me what you know.
Where are they operating from?
Where's Tyrell?
Where the fuck is he?
I'm sorry, Mr. Alderson,
but are you even allowed
to be in this building?
I heard you were let go
this morning.
So much depends
upon a red wheelbarrow...
Glazed with rain water...
Beside the white chickens.
Should've put a wire on her.
- What did you say to him?
- What I had to.
Well, excuse me
for doubting you,
but you never struck me as
a country-first type of gal.
- I don't like you very much.
- Ditto.
What are you, six?
It's him.
Pick it up.
Elliot, where are you?
What's going on?
I texted you the address.
- Is that where Tyrell is?
- Yes.
We need confirmation.
- Are you sure?
- Positive.
Get the FBI there to stop him.
You gotta do it now.
Make him come to us.
Find out where he's headed.
- Where are you going?
- Just take care of Tyrell.
Push him.
We can keep him safe.
Elliot, just please
don't do anything stupid, okay?
- Just come meet me...
- I gotta go.
Elliot, wait.
Everything I said this morning
and everything I've done...
I'm sorry.
Call ended.
Got the location.
It's a restaurant called
Red Wheelbarrow.
Let's move.
Dom, you heard him.
He said the info was good.
Let's go.
What aren't you telling me?
Dom...
Between the rioters
and the police
at E Corp's headquarters,
I can't connect there.
I can't access
my back-doored machine,
but I need to
log in to that UPS,
or everything's fucked.
Fastest way of connecting
is to go into
the Recovery building myself.
I heard the conversation
myself.
Our CHS has confirmation.
- So she had eyes on him?
- No, not exactly, but...
The intel
seems credible, sir.
We gotta act
before Wellick disappears
for another five months.
Here's what we'll do:
I'll put surveillance
on the location
until we have
visual confirmation.
Surveillance?
Santiago, the lead is solid.
This is coming from Darlene.
This is why we have her.
I can't move
on the word of a CHS
who has basically, so far,
given us jack shit,
and then disappeared on us
for almost a week,
without so much as a word.
I need something more concrete.
If Wellick is there,
we have time.
He's not going anywhere.
Before we send SWAT
bashing down doors,
let me coordinate
with S.O. teams
to get eyes on the place.
Ask the S.O. ASAC
to get aviation in the air.
We get confirmation, we go in,
we take down Wellick.
Dom...
we may only get
one shot at this.
I wanna make sure
we do it right.
_
I suppose congratulations
are in order.
After all our tit-for-tat,
you finally got your U.N. vote.
Quite the frenetic day for
the 24-hour newshounds.
I wondered
if you'd make it today,
given everything
going on at E Corp.
An eventful morning indeed.
But something told me
I shouldn't miss our little...
soirée,
not for the world.
Speaking of my dear little,
wounded E Corp,
I'll be expecting China
to sign that economic accord.
All will be done
by end of day.
You have my word.
Oh...
thank God that's settled.
For now, let's...
break from
our usual brinksmanship.
No need to spoil
this afternoon.
We both won, as intended.
It's time to drink
and be merry.
Good point.
Another fine choice
of venue by Sergey.
Utterly tasteless.
I passed that buffoon
of an owner in the lobby.
You're gonna take him up
on his offer
- to go boating tomorrow?
- Oh, please, don't remind me.
Those swim trunks
he insists upon wearing,
a bit too snug...
and a bit too short,
wouldn't you say?
Mm. I believe the appropriate
term is "hanging brain."
Good.
Sir, it's about Mr. Wellick.
Our contact says his location
has been compromised.
Well, that doesn't
change anything.
You know what to do.
Kill process:
when an unwanted process
is running
and you need to terminate it.
I need to kill Stage 2
before it kills anyone else.
Wrap it up.
False alarm.
We're outta here.
Back it up!
Let's go.
False alarm, folks.
It's safe to go back to work.
What are they doing?
What about my bomb threat?
False alarm.
Go ahead, go up.
Why is everyone
going back in?
Everything's fine.
False alarm.
No, it's not safe.
You gotta get them
out of there.
ESU swept the floor.
All's clear.
Uh, it's, uh...
It's... it's safe
to go back to work.
I called in a bomb threat
with no bomb for them to find.
There's no tangible explosive.
They had no idea
what they were looking for.
- But I do.
- Folks, you need E Corp I.D.
to re-enter the building.
Please have them out
where we can see them.
Keep it moving.
Have your badges out and ready.
Let's go. One at a time.
Can you give us a status
update on the seventh floor?
Seventh floor clear.
Heading back down to you.
I was right.
Angela helped them
get around my patch
and sign their own malware
with a cloned HSM.
If I can roll it back,
the clean version
will overwrite Tyrell
and Mr. Robot's malware
and buy me some time
to revoke the stolen keys.
A couple of minutes,
and we'll be...
Why can't I do this?
Why can't I start the restore?
Ohh!
Names are Fattie,
Fattina, and Georgie.
Georgie was named
after my aunt.
Lovely woman.
Fat fingers, though.
What the fuck is going on?
Anyway, it's nice to have
a customer flag me down.
Since 5/9, we haven't had
a whole lot of customers.
Hey...
Stop, stop.
What's the problem?
You told me
Houston on Avenue A.
- When did I say that?
- 20 seconds ago.
Mr. Robot.
I lost time. We know that.
But how much did he take?
15 minutes.
I can't spare 15 minutes.
Stop the goddamn car.
Pull over now!
If the malware's
already loaded,
hydrogen is filling up
the battery room right now.
There are too many factors
to predict
when it's going to blow.
Could be two hours,
or it could explode
at any second.
Why do we always cut
these things so damn close?
Agent DiPierro.
Tell me you have
something, Dom.
I am sitting here,
fucking pins and needles,
losing my shit.
You know I can't share
any information, Darlene.
Have you heard
anything more from Elliot?
No, I've been
trying to call him,
- but he's not answering.
- Unless you've got more intel
that can further this case,
I'm hanging up.
We gave you this lead.
You wouldn't have shit
without us.
Don't think for a second
that I don't know
that you're keeping
something from me.
Given what's at stake,
whoever you're protecting,
I sure as shit hope
they're worth it.
Wrong fucking day, girls.
You hungry?
Yeah, I could eat.
No, I mean,
do you wanna go get lunch?
I can get lunch
if you wanna get lunch.
I'd be up for it.
All right then,
I guess we're going to lunch.
I don't understand.
Why is everyone leaving?
They should be
monitoring the fallout.
Where are Joanna and my son?
What time is
our flight to Kiev?
What is this?
What's going on?
Everything's gone.
Motherfucker.
Is Mr. Robot gaining control,
or am I losing control?
If he has the power to switch,
does that mean I do too?
Is this a matter of
who wants to win the most?
Yeah, I agree,
this is fucking confusing.
Your trip to the Ukraine,
it's not gonna work out
the way we discussed it.
I've got 14 customers,
four cooks behind the line,
two girls working checkout.
No sign of Wellick.
We had a deal.
I... I found a solution.
You... you said
you'd bring my family to me.
- What's going on out front?
- I've got eyes on the door.
Nothing unusual
there or nearby.
You fucking promised!
The plan is happening
because of me,
and this is how you repay me?
I'm afraid the situation
is more nuanced than that.
Shit, there it is again,
his presence.
Do you feel it too?
No, I need more time.
At least he didn't
get too far this time.
Five minutes.
I'm narrowing the gap,
but still,
this isn't one of our bullshit
stalemate prison chess games.
In this case, a stalemate
means Mr. Robot wins.
So, this is it?
This is how it's going to end?
Bathroom's in use.
Make that 15 customers.
Follow
the instructions inside,
and then burn them.
Well, unless Tyrell's taking
a leak, what do you wanna do?
I'm gonna eat.
You're not going to kill me?
Tyrell...
I'm sorry.
Stay focused.
The stronger I am,
the better chance I have of...
Three more minutes gone.
Who knows how many
I have to spare?
I'm running out of options.
Instead of fighting,
maybe it's time we talk.
The soda fountain's
behind you there.
Have a seat, and we'll call
your number when it's ready.
Oh, and here's
our loyalty card.
Ten wheelbarrows punched,
and you get
a free milkshake on us.
You know, I... I don't get
to this neighborhood too often.
How long have you been open?
_
A little over six weeks,
but if you're talking about
the grand opening special,
that's over.
Just curious. Thanks, hon.
_
I guess
he didn't like my note.
I need to get
to the battery room.
Enjoy your meal, ma'am.
I got a worker exiting now,
red apron.
Keep an eye on him.
10-4.
Mom, it's me.
Listen, I don't have
a lot of time.
I need you to stay home
for the rest of the day.
Don't go out.
I'll ship you some Ensure.
Just don't go...
I'll have it delivered today.
Yes, yes, they have
same-day delivery now.
I promise.
Just stay home.
I love you too.
So, I'm going to move in with
my oldest daughter, Louise.
We agreed it's best to pool
our resources these days,
but......
I don't wanna be a burden.
Don't think like that.
You know
it's the best thing to do.
And it doesn't make sense
for you to be living all alone.
You're probably right.
And my... my ulcerated colitis
is kicking in again,
so it'd be nice
to have family around,
you know,
in case anything happens.
You can never be too safe.
Did you hear about the melee
at E Corp this morning?
The whole world's going to hell
in a hand basket.
Give me your purses, now!
Oh!
Give it!
Ecoin wallet, where is it?
Please, please don't hurt me!
Please!
The fuck you waiting on?
Hand over your purse!
What's going on?
What's in there?
There's a fire. I've got smoke
coming from the backroom.
I'm looking at the floor plan
now, and there is no backroom.
Last time I ask bitch!
Do it!
Cred 22958 to Op Center.
Emergency transmission.
Go with your message, 22958.
I've got a fire coming from
Red Wheelbarrow restaurant,
1197 Broadway.
Notify ASAC Santiago
and 5/9 task force
- of a possible Wellick sighting.
- Copy that.
What are you doing?
Give him your purse!
Norm, I'm going in.
Get around to the backdoor now,
in case Tyrell's in there
and tries to run.
You could've died.
No.
No one's gonna die.
The battery room
has a halocarbon
fire suppression system.
If I can activate it,
it'll suck all the oxygen
out of the room in 30 seconds,
seal all the doors,
and create a vacuum,
making it impossible
to create any kind of spark,
which would prevent...
The kill command.
Here I am, trying to use it
to stop this attack
while Mr. Robot
is trying to use it on me.
Does that just mean
we cancel each other out,
fighting so hard,
we end up standing in place?
Fuck that.
I gotta keep moving.
Dude, you okay?
Yeah.
You disobeyed a direct order.
I told you, flat out...
I already told you
it was a site survey.
Report me if you want.
Then why am I standing
in a goddamn basement
- with the door kicked in?
- There were signs of a fire.
I did my job.
I'd do it again,
if given the opportunity.
Anything else?
All right.
Look...
despite your blatant disregard
for chain of command,
this was still a win.
Wellick was here.
The evidence ERT pulls
out of this shit hole
can only bring us closer
to capturing him.
Now, we've got task force
canvassing the tunnels.
If Tyrell is in there,
we'll get him.
Why don't you head back
to the office?
When the evidence comes in,
you start sorting through it.
I can see your big ass eye.
Open up.
- What do you want?
- Open the goddamn door.
- Small coffee, black.
- You got it.
I'm gonna head up
to the office.
- You gonna be okay?
- I'll be up in a minute.
You fucked us,
bent us over the sink
and went to town.
You're not making any sense.
We're on the same side.
No... Fuck!
Oh, come on, please! Fuck!
Fuck!
I saw you
manipulating my brother,
turning his condition
against him.
Taking down E Corp
was your plan. Remember?
_
Hey... hey!
No! Stop the attack!
You have to stop the attack!
Get on the ground!
- Get on the ground!
- Listen to me,
- you have to stop the attack!
- On the ground!
You're the ones
who dragged me into this.
We didn't ask you
to blow up a goddamn building
full of people.
You don't know
what you're talking about.
They're evacuating
the building.
_
It's gonna happen any second.
Please, listen to me,
I can help you!
Let's go!
Go, go, go!
Tell me why I shouldn't
call the FBI and turn you in.
What is it that
you really want, Darlene?
With all their paper records
consolidated there,
this is going to mark
the official end of E Corp.
_
Folks, get back!
Please stop.
_
You can lie to yourself
all you want...
But when you're alone at night,
this shit will haunt you.
Trust me on that.
- Move... move.
- You don't understand!
No, no, no, listen to me,
you have to stop the attack!
Now, I can have you
in handcuffs right now,
so I'm giving you
one last chance.
Convince me not to.
People are gonna die!
Stop the attack!
_
Go ahead and turn me in.
What attack?
I know what I'm doing
is right...
What attack?
Holy shit...
He did it.
We did it.
So what now?
Am I forever in limbo,
not knowing
which side I'm really on?
And what about Mr. Robot?
Does he now understand
that Tyrell and the Dark Army
have corrupted
his alleged revolution?
Does he have any fight left?
If so, who's he gonna fight?
Them or me?
There were no paper records
in the building,
and the Dark Army knew that,
so why did they
try to go today?
What was White Rose's
real plan?
Does she know
something I don't?
Does everybody know
Reports are still coming in
from across the country...
I fought so hard to protect
the New York facility
that I couldn't see
the bigger picture.
It wasn't a single point
of failure.
I was.
In a series of seemingly
orchestrated strikes
across the country,
a reported 71 buildings
owned by E Corp
exploded or caught fire.
There has been
no official confirmation,
or even speculation,
as to what caused
the explosions
and fires to occur.
Officials with
knowledge of the attacks
have stated that
the death toll
is expected to be
well into the thousands.
Meanwhile, first responders
continue to fight fires
and sort through the rubble,
with the hope of
finding survivors.
President Obama
is scheduled to hold
an emergency press conference
later this afternoon
to address
the American public.
As of now, no one has...