Everywhere I look you're there.
- _
- That is why I wanted to meet.
So I could find out why you are
so special to Phillip Price.
Why come after me?
Your pet project
Angela Moss was allowed to
continue with her lawsuit
which put my plans in jeopardy.
We're not safe here. I have to warn her.
She has to know what they heard.
Ms. Moss. Ms. Moss, I'm gonna
need you to come with us.
We're ready.
My exploit will give me full access
to their management interface.
Now I own the Dark Army.
I suppose there's some banal excuse
why a month isn't enough time
to get my project shipped to the Congo?
Trenton's right.
Encryption keys were exported
the night of the hack.
Why would Romero do this?
He did it for the reason
we need those keys now:
in case our revolution failed.
Bang!
- I don't trust him.
- All of his data's
in the FBI evidence storage system.
The FBI. The Dark Army
has a man on the inside.
- I'll hit up my contact.
- We can't trust them.
- I might have an angle.
- She was in my home
attempting to steal my
badge to get on Sentinel.
There are files that can help
decrypt all of E Corp's data.
What's the plan here?
She talks like she knows everything.
How do you want to proceed?
We haven't seen each other in months.
We've been battling each
other in our own voids.
When we were kids, Darlene
and I, we made this snowman.
That was the day my dad
pushed me out the window.
You remember when we
made Kevin McCallister?
Do you want to talk about it?
Do you remember when you said
Elliot would one day follow
in the footsteps of his father?
I think it's time he died for us too.
_
Darlene's not responding
to any of my texts.
If Dark Army's targeting me,
then they're gonna target her next.
Hopefully, she made
it to our rendezvous.
Wake up.
Let's go. You're coming with me.
Finally you guys came to your sen...
- Dude, what the fuck?
- Shut up.
Are you seriously gonna
arrest me right now?
I told you we can fix this, okay?
Let's just log into Sentinel.
I said shut the fuck up.
It's the EC and 302 from
last night, the Alderson case.
I just submitted it for upload.
Why are you giving me this?
Um, sorry, Santiago
must not have told you.
You're on the Alderson arrest.
I brought her in last night.
No clue what you're talking about.
I'm headed to JFK in 20.
Got a flight to San Fran today.
Santiago!
What are you doing?
Taking her to holding.
I thought you were
putting Agent Kaz on this.
Why are you doing this yourself?
The ADIC wanted her in holding.
That's what I'm doing. Get back inside.
Fine, I'll take it
up with the ADIC then.
Are you gonna finally tell
me what the fuck is going on?
I can't talk to you about it, Dom.
You're not authorized to know.
There's intel you're not privy
to that's connected to this.
I'd be more comfortable if
we took it up with the ADIC.
If you want to call him, you can.
But I...
I just don't want you
to embarrass yourself.
What?
Are you scared of me now?
There are cameras everywhere.
You really think I'm going to do...
She's not here.
Mr. Robot's note.
If what he said is true and
the Dark Army owns the FBI,
then maybe she ran into them
while she was trying to access Sentinel.
Shit.
Dark Army has dozens of operatives
who live in and around Manhattan.
Combing through their
command and control server
is going to take too long.
There are over 600,000
compromised systems on here.
I can't go through every one.
I don't even know
what I'm searching for.
I need something to go on.
A name, place, something, anything.
Think, think, think. What do I know?
Anything you can remember? Any detail?
Anything. Tell me something.
Don't you get it? She's gonna die.
Darlene's gonna die. She's gonna die.
She's gonna fucking
die like everyone else.
I should have never done this.
I should have left this alone.
I'll never learn.
I brought this on myself.
This is on me.
For how many?
One.
So, Ferris wheel.
Cute touch.
I need information from you.
You do not get to summon
me like you're Ali Baba,
squeeze me for information
then shove me back in some lamp.
Darlene's in trouble!
She might already be dead.
The whole reason you're
in this goddamn mess
is because we're not working together,
because you refuse to talk to me.
I wish that were true.
The sick part is...
I actually missed you.
The only reason we
haven't been talking...
Is because I haven't let myself.
'Cause I've been scared of you.
The part of... me that is you.
Why are we talking now?
The 71 buildings.
I didn't know about that.
If you did, would you have done it?
Would you have done it?
I would have...
I would have found another way.
Because as much as there
is a part of you in me...
there is a part of me in you.
Your note on the mirror,
what did you mean by it?
What do you know?
I need to find Darlene.
Tell me what you know.
The FBI...
has a mole.
You piece of shit.
The attack in China.
While you were hiding in your room,
knowing the rest of us were
getting blown to pieces.
Cisco.
You helped them get to him
before we did, didn't you?
And the Tyrell cover-up.
You helped frame...
Markesh and Biswas.
This whole time, we've been
punching ourselves in the face
because of you!
All I know is, if you
were put in my position...
Nothing would make me betray
everything I stand for.
You know one thing I'll
say about you, DiPierro,
your naivete is adorable.
It's easy for you to play
a hero in the back seat,
but that's all world's ever amounted to.
The back seat.
The things I did.
I mean, the... the things
that I have to do...
Are you seriously trying to
paint yourself a saint now
after what you've put us through?
You know, the only reason
your girlfriend here is alive
is because I never told
the Dark Army she was a CHS.
Believe or not, I'm
not a bad guy, DiPierro.
You don't understand
what they put me through.
What they hold over me, but you will.
Soon enough.
There's the cocksucker.
Dead center.
According to Wellick,
he's been working both
sides the whole time.
Probably the reason we didn't
get pegged for Five/Nine.
We gotta find a way to trace him.
Why don't we jump on his desktop?
I already did that
remotely, nothing useful.
Which means whatever we're
looking for is physical.
Number sets.
It's another cipher code.
Not this shit again.
This has gotta give us a location.
Elliot. Just give me a minute.
Elliot.
Just finished this book.
I got it on tape.
Didn't care much for the ending.
I mean, a story can
have a mediocre beginning
and middle, and oftentimes it does,
but always got to have a wow ending.
Otherwise, what's the point?
Shit.
If he's here that means
they must have Darlene.
Maybe I can manipulate
him into helping us.
Quick.
- What do we know about...
- Whatever scheme
you're trying to come up with right now
It ain't gonna change
the inevitable, so...
I strongly recommend you
choose the easy way here
and come with me.
How'd you sleep last night?
I didn't.
I've been waiting all night.
I need to see her as soon as possible.
I have important information for her.
It's a beautiful day, don't you think?
Look.
There are people that
are trying to stop her.
I need to tell her.
Oh, I'm just the house manager.
But you can discuss that with
Mr. Price when he arrives.
I thought we'd get some breakfast first.
Do you like pancakes?
It's this way.
- Elliot.
- Don't fucking move.
We are walking into some
fucking hillbilly shit here.
Now, look.
I know this is all fucked
up, but it's salvageable.
There's a lot of clean-up at the FBI
you're going to have
to take care of for me.
Mm-hmm.
So this is the plus-one
you've been squawking about?
You're not turning this around on me.
Not after the fucking day I've had,
cleaning up your mess once again.
I'm over it. You hear me?
It's high time you guys start
cleaning up my mess for a change.
Uh-huh.
And by "mess" I assume you mean her.
I know how to fix this.
So do I.
All right.
Come on, Miss, let's go.
Leon, you got this?
Yeah, I got it.
Are you okay?
Is that a joke?
We're in a fucking barn
out in the middle of nowhere
with a handful of psychos.
"No" is the answer.
Listen, sir.
I don't know what you
think I did, but...
This guy's a liability to
you. He's gotten sloppy.
- You don't have to do this.
- Dom.
My bosses know about everything.
There's security camera
footage of him kidnapping
- Ms. Alderson and me...
- Miss.
Stop talking.
Hm?
Okay, we got two operatives.
Leon's pretty good with a knife.
What are you thinking?
I'm not trying to escape.
Elliot, these guys
aren't fucking around.
Who do you think you're
going to talk to out here?
Who do you think?
Whiterose.
You've played that game already.
She doesn't want to see you.
She's seeing us right now.
Fuck me.
Now wait a minute.
Let's just slow things down a bit.
We can flip her.
She can be very valuable.
- No way I'm flipping.
- Dom.
Don't be stupid. Listen to me.
I'm trying to get you out of this alive.
Valuable, huh?
You think she would've
gone far in the Bureau?
She would have been one
of the youngest ASACs ever,
still could be.
No, she's a rising star.
Gumption.
But it's like she said,
no way she's flipping.
Hey.
Oh, no, no, don't get
too worked up, Miss.
Just look at the sky.
Take a deep breath.
Try to enjoy the fresh air.
Wait, wait, wait. Dom.
Just tell him you'll flip.
This isn't worth it. You can...
Oh, don't mind that.
We're retiring this shit-stain.
And you're taking his place.
You work for the Dark Army now.
You're gonna go back to the FBI.
It's gonna be business as usual.
You're gonna feed us any information
and answer all our requests.
- Fuck you.
- Now, Dom.
You're gonna need to get your head
around the position you're in here.
I'm no traitor.
You should kill me now
because the first thing I do
when you let me go is
arrest your fucking ass.
The name of your youngest family member,
what is it?
Oh, that's right.
Four-year-old Jamie
DiPierro of Morrisville.
That's your brother Joseph's kid, right?
Yeah.
I want you to look at this jerk-off
and imagine it's little Jamie.
Now I want you to
imagine your mom Trudie...
in Philly.
Now imagine Uncle Chris one morning
as he's picking up his copy...
of the "Dallas Morning Star"!
Or you're older brother, Jerry,
while he's watching
"Wheel... of... Fortune!"
Am I illustrating my point?
Dom, I'm going to need
verbal confirmation
that you're grasping the
details of this agreement!
Okay.
In time...
this will get easier to live with.
I promise.
Head into the barn and
await further instructions
on how to clear up Santiago's missteps.
Now, forgive me
while I take a moment to center myself.
This next bunch...
These are for me.
Jesus, Dom, what happened?
Looks like she's just
got her initiation.
Want some of this catnip, girl?
All right. Suit yourself.
All right, if we don't figure
out a way get out of here,
they are going to kill us.
Look around you.
They've been instructed to wait.
Not act.
Wait for what?
They're preparing for
someone important to come.
I took care of everything.
As instructed.
Everyone's loaded up in the barn.
You might want to send your guys
to the woodpile over there.
I had to kill the FBI mole.
That's the bad news.
Good news, I got you
someone even better.
She doesn't have as high of a rank,
but she's got tremendous upside.
Besides...
That guy was a dickhead.
Anyway.
She's in the barn as well.
Where are you going?
Me, I'm gonna take
that overdue sabbatical
I keep talking about.
Finally get to finish my book.
Well, that's the goal anyway.
I'm thinking the Sandals in Barbados.
They got a good special
running this month.
You are not going anywhere.
We have work to do.
Tell me something.
She still making her
spontaneous overtures?
She make you taste her yet?
Remember, doll face,
I was you years ago.
And I've already done my time.
I think she'll be good with me.
Glad we did this.
I want to leave.
My staff not keeping you comfortable?
I wouldn't have come
if I had known this was your house.
I was getting concerned about you.
Hadn't been to work for weeks,
you're not answering
your phone, your emails.
I sent someone to your apartment.
When I saw what you
were doing, I felt I...
I had to intervene.
I'm not supposed to be here.
And where do you think
you're supposed to be?
You know where.
With her.
She has a plan.
Yes, I've known about her
delusional plan for years.
You don't know anything.
Mr. Alderson.
I had a chance to review your
paperwork for Stage Three.
- Surprisingly...
- It's bullshit.
There is no Stage Three,
but you already knew that.
I'm glad we can be honest.
Now we can talk.
The only reason you're
involved in any of this
is because I had Colby hire you.
I needed to manipulate you into dropping
that contingency from your lawsuit.
You were threatening her plant.
And she would have done anything
to stop those inspections,
including killing you.
Why would you care if she killed me?
You don't care about
anyone but yourself.
Let go of them.
Then we can talk.
But if I didn't have her
then how am I going to keep you honest?
I own everything.
I own every single system
the Dark Army has compromised.
I met your mother.
Emily.
32 years ago.
When you took my laptop,
you infected yourself with my malware.
If you hurt her,
it will all get released.
Every bribe, blackmail,
extortion, operation,
all your illegal connections,
everything will go public.
The entire Dark Army history.
That's impossible.
And here I thought we
were going to be honest.
We were both working at E Corp.
We dated for quite some time.
Seven days ago, the Russian government
hired you to hack the DNC.
- Elliot.
- Two days before that,
you bribed the president of
South Korea to allow backdoors
in all of their military networks.
- You're just pissing him off.
- Three weeks before that,
you used Phillip Price to
annex the Congo for China.
Am I being more honest now?
I loved her.
Deeply.
But I never told her.
If one of us dies,
everything gets leaked.
Well, we can survive a leak.
You can't survive a
bullet through your throat.
The closer we became,
the more I held back.
I was cruel to her
in that way.
It made me feel strong...
To torture her like that... Like that.
We have an opportunity for both of us
to leave with what we want.
I know exactly what you want.
You want to reverse Five/Nine.
And honestly we couldn't
care less about that.
It's already served its purpose.
When she told me she was pregnant,
she was very emphatic that her child
wasn't going to be raised by a monster,
as she put it.
No!
I also know how to move
whatever project you have
in the Washington Township
Plant to the Congo.
While you sit back,
missing your deadlines, doing nothing,
I've engineered a hack that
can solve all of your problems
and I'm willing to give it to you.
Do you hear me?
I can move your projects to the Congo!
You'll get what you want!
We won't bother you anymore!
Sometime after that she met and then...
She married your father.
Who agreed to raise you as his own.
You're very sure of yourself.
You are just one hacker.
What makes you believe
that you are better
than an army of people exactly like you?
Because I am.
I did something in one night
you've been trying to
pull off for months.
I never planned on telling you,
until I realized what
whiterose had done to you.
Look, it's not possible
what she's talking about.
Angela, this so-called project of hers,
it stems from an obsessive,
psychotic denial of reality.
Don't do this.
Let me help you.
I'm sorry, Mr. Alderson.
You're good at playing games.
But this was simply
the wrong hand to play.
She has murdered countless people
to fulfill this...
this ridiculous fantasy.
History...
is finally coming for you.
What is this?
I don't believe you.
You're lying.
I am your father.
Biologically speaking, anyway.
I think that's you, brah.
The Cyber Bombings...
All of those people.
That was my fault.
She used me for that.
Your jealousy has always blinded you
to Mr. Alderson's value.
That is why you can never see
my plan through to the end.
I have to believe
there was a purpose.
Pettiness.
It was a dig at me.
It's that small, unfortunately.
You can't believe him.
He's... he's lying.
Know that I will find you
as soon as our project is complete.
But for the here and now...
our time has come...
to an end.
_
No, it's not over.
It's not over. It can't be.
She was gonna bring my mom back.
We were gonna be reunited.
You made an offer, cuz.
Now it's time to pay up.
Please tell me you're not bluffing.
What are you gonna do to her?
What are you asking?
Retribution.
I want it.
Coast Guard is allowing the shipment
of humanitarian aid to Iran.
Trust me.
It'll work.
I'm afraid your only move here...
Accept that you've been conned.
It's downloaded.
Now, you know
I ain't got to tell you
what they going to do
if this don't check out right.
It'll check out.
You know I've always
had faith in you, cuz.
Do your thing.
Find a way to live with what you did.
What do we do now?
Undo the hack.
Don't think I'm doing this for you.
Dom.
You are a terrible person.
Don't ever convince
yourself of anything else.
All you deserve for
the rest of your life...
is pure and utter agony.
That'll begin to scratch the surface
of how I feel about you.
You've taken everything from me.
My whole life...
is ruined because of you.
Live with that.
Die with that.
The FBI had Romero's keylogger files,
but he encrypted them with a password.
Thing is, the FBI didn't know Romero.
I do.
Is this really it?
The moment this can all truly end?
Reverse everything we've done.
Finally bring Five/Nine to an end.
This is it.
Everything that was
typed on those machines
at the arcade on the night of the hack.
So what'd you find?
He didn't do it.
Romero was just spying on us.
He caught someone else
exporting the key data.
If he didn't do it,
then who the fuck did?
Reminder, today's city-wide curfew
starts at 9:00 p.m. this evening
until 4:00 a.m. tomorrow morning.
Stay indoors and stay off the streets.
Why did you bring up Kevin McCallister?
The snowman.
When we were in Coney Island,
you asked me if I remembered.
What was that all
about? It felt so random.
That was the day Dad
pushed me out the window.
What are you... What do you mean...
Dad pushed you out the window?
He was mad that I told
Mom about his cancer,
and he pushed me out the window.
You were young.
I guess I never told you.
What are you talking about Elliot?
I was there.
We were in your room
looking for a camera
when Dad came home.
For some reason
you freaked out and told
me to go hid in the closet.
Then Dad came in the
room, and all of the sudden
you... I don't know. You just snapped.
You started swinging your baseball bat,
hitting everything.
No.
That's not what happened.
Trust me, I remember.
You took your baseball bat
and you smashed the window,
and then you kept telling
Dad you were gonna jump.
Elliot, you weren't pushed.
You jumped.
I don't remember any of that.
Well, I'm here to remember for you.
This is our stop.
I'm gonna ride the
train a little longer.
Are you okay?
I'll get it done.
Hey. The email from Trenton.
I know she sent it to you
because she could trust you.
The same as I always have.
I'm gonna get off at the next stop.
I think you should come with me.
It wasn't Romero.
It was you who exported the keys.
Why?
We're close, Elliot.
You pull the ripcord now
and everything will be for nothing.
There was a huge cost
to get to this point.
I still believe if we
hold out a little longer...
No.
You do this,
and they will have won.
You really believe undoing
this is going to fix anything?
Huh? Do you?
I mean, who is this really gonna help?
Me.
I'm doing this for me.
I can't live with what I did anymore.
And you're wrong.
They won't win.
Because one good thing
came out of all of this.
They showed themselves,
the top 1% of the 1%,
the ones in control,
the ones who play God
without permission.
And now I'm gonna take them down.
All of them.
Whatever happens after this,
I want us to keep talking.
I want us to be a team.
I know I can't force you so...
I'm asking.
I jumped.
I wasn't pushed.
Did you know that?
You asked me before why I did this.
We, the damned!
The reason is I thought...
What if we were wrong?
What if there's something
we weren't seeing?
What if we failed?
The real reason is it's...
It's because it's
what you would've done.
You were right.
There was a part of you in me.
I never wanted to tell you that
because it's not in my nature.
It's not why I exist.
Only you know why I'm here.
On the night of the hack,
I transferred the keys
from the arcade...
to a remote virtual machine
on our box at home.
I then burned it to a CD.
You'll find the seed
data and the algorithm
embedded in one of those pictures.
You'll know the one.
With those two pieces, you
should be able to regenerate
the keys that were used
to encrypt all of E Corp's data.
And with that...
You can make it like
Five/Nine never happened.
This is a reminder,
today's city-wide curfew
begins at 9:00 p.m. this evening
through 4:00 a.m. tomorrow morning.
Stay indoors and off the streets.
Dude, what the fuck? Slow down.
Fucking asshole.
Shit.
Like I was saying, this
shit has been fucking rough.
I hear you. It's hit everybody.
Yeah, the difference
being when it hits you,
you don't have to suck
some cuck's shrimp dick
to buy a damn sandwich.
This is true.
I think things are gonna change though.
For the better.
Soon, so...
Hang in there.
Hanging's what I do best.
But I don't know what you mean.
E Corp's in a world of shit.
Daddy lost both his homes
and his bike 'cause of them.
And now this country's attackin' Iran.
If anything, this is the
calm before the damn storm.
Yeah, well...
Hold out hope.
Trust me. I think...
I think E Corp will be able
to bring back their lost data.
Yeah, well, I hope not.
That just means debt's gonna come back.
And I certainly don't know
how my $80,000 student loan
I owe Parsons is gonna
help me fix anything.
Well, it's a start.
Path to recovery.
The economy will start to bounce back.
Girl, you don't have
to sound so simplistic.
That's not the way this
crony capitalism works.
Shit, educate yourself on some Marx
before you go just theorizing
about economic forces.
Okay, so...
What do you think would
fix all of this then?
An act of God.
And right about now,
he needs a hell of a
good blowjob, just like
every other stressed-out,
powerful motherfucker
trying to hold their
shit together, right?
Well, this is me.
I'm really glad I met you tonight.
You too, babes.
Why you coming to this
ugly ass building anyways?
My brother lives here.
You think he'd be down
for a good time tonight?
Well, he definitely
needs to get laid, but...
I don't think that's gonna happen.
- Shit.
- What?
There go them damn eses again.
Fuck, and now they parking.
Look.
I got to go, babe.
Can I help you, fellas?
My sister,
only the north stars of the cosmos
can help a visionary like me.
But, yes,
you can shine a light on
a dark corner of my mind.
What?
Who are you?
I'm just...
I'm just a brave traveler
who's finally come home.