_
Anything?
Nothing yet.
Who is that? Who is that,
that guy on the bike?
He looks like he's coming
straight toward me.
Okay, he's closing in. We're coming.
- No, wait.
- It's too risky.
- We need to fly in.
- Wait.
Are you... from E Corp?
- Who are you?
- Just making a delivery.
Please sign here.
- What is this?
- Someone grab the biker.
- Grab the biker.
- No, no, no,
they haven't picked up the money yet.
Mr. Knowles, we don't recommend that.
We should have our unit search it first.
Sir, are you all right?
Should we come in? Are you all right?
Is that your phone?
You have ten seconds to do what it says,
or every Bank of E
system will be bricked.
Sir, who was the caller?
Mr. Knowles, what are you doing?
There's no way.
We've already committed $900 billion.
It would be irresponsible
if the feds sent more.
And we're not going
to ask the government
to pony up the cash.
How do you burn through
that kind of money
in 30 days anyway?
You have something right... right there.
Finally you're seeing my point.
No, no, on your face.
The point is, Phillip,
we've already given you our
burst of cash on hand.
We can't give you any more.
Well, we'll sell the
T-bills to the Chinese,
and that money in return
will be used as a loan for our company.
Look, the real recovery program
is months from being done.
The public is hoarding cash.
The housing market is
grinding to a halt.
The big three are on
the verge of collapse.
Everyone at the commission
needs to see results
within the next three weeks
before we can do anything else.
Look, rebuilding our database
is the only solution to this problem.
This is not my opinion.
These are the facts,
ladies and gentlemen.
Now, I've cooperated
with you on every level.
I even have the goddamn FBI
working out of my offices.
Janet, Mary, Jack, please.
Tell me you didn't ask me
to fly down all the way to D.C.
just so you could, what,
hear yourselves complain?
You've got to resign.
We have no other options.
The President can't go to Congress
with a bailout right now.
In the fallout of the Great Depression,
FDR closed all the banks
for a bank holiday,
and then he reopened them in stages
when they were reported to being sound.
Later, historians discovered
what we in this room now know,
that those reports,
they were mostly lies.
Nevertheless, it worked.
It worked because the public believed
the government had
everything under control.
You see, that is the business model
for this great nation of ours.
Every business day when
that market bell rings,
we con people into
believing in something,
the American dream, family values.
Could be freedom fries for all I care.
It doesn't matter
as long as the con works
and people buy and sell
whatever it is we want them to.
If I resign,
then any scrap of confidence
the public is already clinging
onto will be destroyed,
and we all know
a con doesn't work
without the confidence.
If this was the best idea
you could come up with for a win,
I shouldn't be the one resigning.
I have to head back to New York.
Let me know when you've
locked up the votes,
and wipe your goddamn mouth.
Well?
You moved.
And?
Now I'm gonna punish you.
Ahem.
Ah, you know, usual, coffee,
black, turkey sandwich
on whole wheat, lettuce,
mayo, muenster cheese.
Already working on it.
You always take good care of me, Ahmed.
How's the wife doing?
She's good, she's good, thank you.
Oh, I haven't seen her in a while.
Where is she these days?
- Our daughter is sick.
- Oh, that right?
That's too bad.
- Now, which one is she again?
- Sally.
Sally, uh, the young one, right?
- Yeah.
- Sally, such a pretty name.
Now, is that traditionally
an Iranian name, or...
Come on, lady, I'm in a rush here.
Jesus H, all right.
God, Calm down.
Well, I guess I should pay up, Ahmed,
before I get lynched over here.
_, am I right?
Um...
and this?
DiPierro, he's waiting for us.
Yup.
When you look closely at
the seams between order
and chaos,
do you see the same things I see?
The strain, the tears,
the glimpses of truth hidden underneath.
Why do they fight so desperately
to mask what they are?
Or is it that they become who they are
when they put on the mask?
Sometimes I wonder what you hide behind,
my silent friend.
What mask do you wear?
Or are you just as afraid
as the rest of them?
Me?
Am I afraid?
Nah, man.
I'm different.
Hey, dipshit,
can't you see we need the ball?
- This ball?
- Yeah, that ball.
What, you slow or something?
What's up?
Nah, I ain't slow, bro.
Go get your own ball.
- Yo, man.
- What?
What's your problem, son?
- What's your problem?
- You my problem.
You need to learn how
to speak to people.
Oh, you need to have respect, son.
I got it.
Hey, I got it.
We're all just here to
have a good time, right?
Yes, sir.
Maxine's been acting
a little off lately.
She really perked up when she saw you.
You a dog person?
Used to have one.
Oh, yeah?
What happened to it?
Don't have her anymore.
Hmm.
Elliot, right?
I'm Ray.
I've seen you here before.
You must like the games, huh?
They put Bradstreet in.
He's good on the boards.
Come on, boys.
Look at these guys. What do you see?
A lot of care and effort
over what amounts to a
pretty shitty game.
What's Maxine see?
A bunch of dumb animals,
can't think past anything
but getting a ball in a hoop.
What do they want you to see?
Badass homies...
ready to kill if you step to 'em.
Question is...
which is the truth?
Maybe all of 'em.
Maybe none of 'em.
Maybe truth don't even exist.
Maybe what we think is all we got,
which is why I'm a little
jealous of Maxine over here,
'cause all she gives a shit
about is eating and sleeping.
Ain't that right, girl?
Not the loquacious type, I get it.
Me, I talk all the time,
but I guess you picked up on that.
It's cool though. Communication...
is good for my line of work.
Takes a lot of it to
run a good business.
But unlike you, when
it comes to computers,
well,
I get them about as much as
Maxine here gets E. E. Cummings,
so when I heard...
Whatever you heard, it's not true.
I don't do that anymore.
Just tell him you'll help.
Try it once, huh?
Let that old feeling come back.
You know, this morning
over breakfast my wife
told me I'd make a friend today.
Not many people to talk to around here
except for these knuckleheads.
It's cool if we continue talking?
No, thanks.
Damn, man.
That's some cold, brutal
shit right there.
I'ma have to go listen
to some Adele on repeat
when I get back home.
Okay, I can take a hint.
Come on, babe.
How long you gonna keep us
in this analog nightmare?
As long as it takes.
Without my weapon of choice,
Mr. Robot is unplugged, powerless.
He'll try to wear us down,
but as long as we stick to the regimen,
he can't take control
no matter how much of an
illusion he thinks this is.
I mean, it's a disgrace,
an absolutely disgrace police
have not found this guy.
Not only does all the evidence
behind the Five/Nine
attacks lead to him,
but he is the leading suspect
behind the Sharon Knowles murder.
I've said it before. I'll say it again.
The misogynistic blind eye by
law enforcement in this...
My problem, Stassi.
I hit her for a (BLEEP) reason.
She (BLEEP) my ex-boyfriend...
Hey, "Vanderpump's" on.
You want to watch?
- Another time.
- You know what?
I'll walk away and let
this be about you.
How was I that time? Did I do okay?
I didn't hurt you too bad, right?
You're spoiling it again.
At least I didn't break a couple up.
Do you want to go have
a drink at the bar?
You know, I know the guy who works here
makes awesome mescal cocktails.
We used to bartend together
back at this place...
We're not to be seen together, remember?
That was our agreement.
That's him, isn't it?
Freaks me out. Can't he wait downstairs?
He's doing his job.
She's still in the tub.
You said 2:00. It's 2:15.
Hand me a towel?
Go.
We can't leave together.
So unfair.
She came out of nowhere a month ago.
Sometimes I see her talking to herself.
Oh, my gosh, you did too?
So weird.
Yeah, Melissa hates her too.
Shit, I got to take this.
I'll call you back.
I'm telling you, it's non-negotiable.
No one's going to let you
take that question off the table.
The money burning is a big part
of why everyone wants the exclusive.
Bloomberg, line two for you.
Except for CNN, which
you guys don't want...
I got to call you back. Hi, Foster.
I thought the deadline was noon.
It's noon now.
It's five past, Angela, and...
Ryder's agreeing to the questions.
He's also giving us top
of the hour and Kelly.
Price doesn't even like Kelly.
I'll budge on the time slot,
but I can't on the question.
It's fair game.
Talk to the segment
producer and call me back.
Angela, I already know the answer.
You were supposed to make this
happen five minutes ago...
Just call me back.
Call Markinson.
We don't want CNBC,
or Fox News, for that matter.
I think you should let
Melissa handle this.
- Done deal?
- Not gonna happen.
Scott Knowles burning $5.9 million
is on the table or not at all.
We're going with CNBC.
They're sending a deal memo as we speak.
You know I would rather go with you.
You got to twist their arm.
Bullshit.
Did you just hang up on Bloomberg?
Are you trying to get fired?
Leave.
Excuse me?
When Melissa finds out...
Get her.
Go ahead and get her. Tell
her whatever you want,
but right now get out
of my fucking cubicle.
Fine, we'll take it off,
but we're talking about the bailout
and Plouffe's suicide.
I can't do Plouffe.
Then we're walking for real.
Segment producer is pissed
that this is what...
The guy committed
suicide on national TV.
It's out of respect for his family.
Trust me, I'm doing you a favor.
You don't want to ask about that.
Please, it's been a month.
One question, and I have to approve it.
Hi, Melissa.
Bloomberg TV agreed to all the points
on the exclusive.
Foster's sending you the deal memo.
I need to get coffee
before the staff meeting.
Sorry I'm late.
Coming up to the city
was just a nightmare.
The tunnel was at a snail's pace.
E-ZPass is down again.
They're saying indefinitely this time,
but I cannot take the
train in this heat.
It must have been in the 90s today.
Okay, sorry.
So?
I've decided to stay.
We agreed to discuss this.
We have for several weeks now.
Need I remind you I was against
you taking Colby's job
offer in the first place?
And then even when you convinced me
that we should wait to
see where it would lead,
we agreed it was only gonna
be for a brief trial basis.
I think we were both clearly
wrong about their motives.
Oh, I think you are being naive.
And I don't think that we need
to have these talks anymore.
I like my job, and I'm not quitting.
That's my decision.
You never had any intention
of leaving, did you?
I know you think they're
pulling something,
but that's because you
can't imagine anyone ever
valuing me as a real asset,
when the truth is I've done
more for you and the lawsuit
than you've ever done
for me or yourself.
I have value,
and even though you
don't see it, they do.
They are barbarians in $10,000 suits,
but I see your resolve.
I know when to cut my losses.
A guy walks up to a woman at a bar.
He flirts with her.
He makes small talk,
but the woman insists she
isn't gonna go home with him.
Guy says, "What if I
offer you $1 million
to sleep with me?"
The woman's never had a
million dollars in her life.
She stops and considers
the offer very seriously.
The guy changes his mind, says,
"What if I change my offer
to a dollar instead?"
Woman is aghast.
"What kind of woman do you think I am?"
Guy says, "We already figured that out.
Now we're just negotiating."
Are you alone?
Welcome to positive
affirmations volume three,
success and money.
You'll hear the affirmations
repeated twice.
I will leave a space for
you to either repeat
mentally or out loud.
Please use this on a consistent basis
to form new neural pathways.
Good luck.
I am confident.
My confidence is powerful.
I recognize myself as exceptional.
I will follow my dreams no matter what.
Come on, sit down.
Maxine wanted to come over and say hi.
She missed you.
I think the damn dog
might actually like you more than me.
See that smile?
Even though we're
technically not friends,
I told my wife we were,
was too embarrassed to say otherwise.
You know, you two would get along.
She likes to ignore me too.
Hey, man, I don't mean to be an asshole,
but like I said before, I'm all good.
Sorry, I actually don't
know why I'm laughing.
I though you made some joke I don't get,
so I usually just fake laugh at those,
but...
really, I'm confused.
I thought we were on the same page.
About what?
When we spoke last night.
I don't know what you're
talking about, man.
I didn't see you last night.
You really don't remember.
You feeling okay, chief?
That's what the control,
the regimen, the journal,
my perfectly constructed loop,
what this whole thing's been about.
Last night till this morning,
while I was sleeping, I
can't account for it,
a gap in my consciousness,
and somehow he...
What do they see when
they see you coming?
And this is why I'm different.
Sometimes my mask takes over.
Why did you talk to him?
Because I'm gonna make you realize.
What?
What will you make me realize?
That they see me.
What's so funny?
We started a movement.
We were meant to lead it.
Now, get back on a terminal now.
Give me what I want or keep shooting me.
Tell me where Tyrell is,
or shoot me again
'cause the only one it's
gonna drive mad is you...
not me.
I'm late for my church group.
Peace.
This time targeting
the Bank of E network
in an elaborate ransomware attack.
The malicious malware targeted
the bank's computer servers
and spread to multiple branches
in North America, encrypting the data
and rendering the systems unusable
until a ransom was paid.
This more militant variant
of the hacker collective
forced Scott Knowles, the CTO of E Corp,
to burn $5.9 million in public view.
Shortly thereafter pictures
surfaced on social media
under the name #OPdailyallowance.
Now, this is considered
a direct response
to E Corp's unpopular program,
which would lower their daily
cash withdrawal allowances
for customers to $50.
Some stunt, huh?
Everybody's laughing it
off as a dumb prank,
but these guys know what they're doing.
Who thought that hard cash would
be this valuable right now?
We're reliving Black Tuesday,
the Great Depression.
Warning lights were flashing.
I mean, in the last two years
the Army Corps of Engineers,
the Energy Department,
the State Department,
and the Office of Personnel Management
were all hacked.
The government claimed they
were boosting security,
but what came of it?
The same as 1929.
Shit hit the fan.
An act like this changes
people, changes society.
I'm just having a drink.
I'm sorry,
and I'm rambling like a fanatic.
Is there something else
you want to talk about?
The beaches of Barbados,
espresso on Rue Montmartre,
sitting around a campfire
in the Adirondacks?
I'm married.
I'm Brock...
and I know you're Gideon Goddard.
- I watch way too much news.
- God.
I can't believe I'm a tabloid sensation.
More of a diehard fan.
I got a smile.
I'm on a roll.
When did he leave you?
What, was that on the news too?
No, just your face.
It's obvious why they
use you as their patsy.
You give off a very sympathetic
and honest vibe.
You're the perfect
vessel for their lies.
Yeah, well, I don't... I don't know
what to say to that, but, uh...
I'll agree with you that
it sure as hell feels like
there's something bigger
than me in control.
Thank you.
For what?
Tomorrow I'm gonna be a hero.
I'm sorry?
You may just be a patsy, but
you're an important one.
In fact, I don't think I've ever met
a bigger crisis actor than you before.
This is for our country.
And there shall be no more death,
neither sorrow nor crying,
neither shall there be any more pain,
for the former things are passed away,
and he that sat upon the throne said,
"Behold, I make all things new,"
and he said unto me,
"Write, for these words
are true and faithful,"
and he said unto me, "It is done.
"I am Alpha and Omega,
"the beginning and the end.
"I will give unto him that
is athirst of the fountain
"of the water of life freely.
"He that overcometh shall
inherit all things,
"and I will be his God
"and he shall be my son."
Hello?
Is it really you?
Who is this?
Bonsoir, Elliot.