What is it about society that
disappoints you so much?
Sometimes I dream of saving the world,
saving everyone from the invisible hand,
the one that controls us every
day without us knowing it.
What if this all went away?
The city, the money, all of it?
Hey, kiddo.
Exciting time in the world
right now, exciting time.
Tell me about your father.
He had leukemia, made me
swear to never tell anyone.
Finally I got so worried, I told my mom.
I tried to hug him, tell him I'm sorry,
and he shoved me so hard I
fell backwards out the window.
I was eight years old.
If you don't take this deal,
you'll become like me,
losing everyone's respect.
I gave up everything for this case.
- I don't want you to.
- I'm not working there.
They killed my mother.
If you want to change things,
perhaps you should try from within.
And I'm gonna erase
all the debts we owe.
Every record of every credit card, loan,
and mortgage will be wiped clean.
What do we all do now?
Guys, this isn't about
what we'll do tomorrow.
This is about what we did.
They're free because of us.
Jesus, what did I do?
I told you we shouldn't have done this.
I'm a little concerned for Tyrell
because he was acting very
strange last I saw him.
I know you're behind it,
fsociety, the server, Colby, Allsafe.
You're one constant in
a sea of variables.
No matter what anyone tries
to do, I will never leave.
I will always be right here.
Do you understand that?
They're gonna try and get rid of me
again, and I need you to not let them.
Listen to me. I will never leave you.
I will never leave you alone again.
I am Mr. Robot.
I've always told you we'd end up
working together, Elliot, but still
I have to know, why did you do it?
I wanted to save the world.
_
Why this mask?
It's a bit silly, isn't it?
Wellick.
I see.
I understand.
James, yes.
Yes, I'm aware of Mr. Goddard's request,
but it needs to be removed this moment.
Can you escalate it?
Thank you, James.
It should be ready.
What is it?
It's happening.
It's almost as if...
something's come alive.
- Oh, my God.
- This is your fault!
- It's your fault!
- I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry!
What did you do, you son of a bitch?
- He's bleeding!
- It was an accident.
God says there are no accidents!
Son, son, please talk to me.
Talk to me please.
God help us, he's bleeding.
The neighbors are looking.
This is embarrassing.
Son, son, wake up. Wake up!
God, is he okay? Ask if he's okay!
Can't you see he's not
responding, Magda?
- It's your fault, it's your fault!
- It was an accident.
God says there are no accidents.
I'm so sorry. Please call an ambulance!
Call an ambulance!
As you can see by the images,
everything appears to be normal,
which is good news
because there were no lesions
from the scan,
no hemorrhaging or bleeding,
mild concussion, a few stitches.
The forearm, however, is broken,
so that will require a cast.
- How much will that be?
- Excuse me?
How much will the co-pay be?
Well, that's something
you need to discuss with
the billing department.
- We'll talk about that later...
- Shut up.
You've lost your job.
We have no money.
How are we supposed to pay for this
on top of all your other bills?
Don't touch me.
I told you, there won't be any bills.
Mr. and Mrs. Alderson, please,
I'm going to have to ask you
to step outside for a second.
I'd like to talk to Elliot alone.
Elliot.
Elliot, I want you to know
that you are going to be just fine.
Now, that was quite a
spill you took today,
but I promise, you have a long
and healthy life ahead of you.
Now, Elliot, there are
just a few questions
that I need to ask you.
Time to get up.
Today started just like yesterday
and the day before that
and every day for the last month,
a loop, my perfectly constructed loop.
This is going to be
affecting our economy
in ways that are
extraordinarily significant.
The FBI announced today,
and we can confirm,
that Tyrell Wellick
and fsociety engaged in this attack.
They caused a lot of damage,
and we will respond.
We will respond proportionally,
and we will respond in a place
and time that we choose.
That's not something
that I will announce
at a press conference.
At 8:00 a.m. my daily program
begins by having breakfast
with my friend, Leon.
There's this one episode
where they go to this
Chinese restaurant,
and they're just waiting for
a table the entire time.
Like, they don't even
eat at the end, bro.
He just discovered "Seinfeld."
Maybe I'm overthinking it, though.
And talks way too much about it.
It's really fucking with him.
It's really fucking with me.
But it's perfect for me.
I don't have to say anything.
I can just listen.
God, man, that Kramer dude,
if I knew him in real life,
I'd knock his ass out.
At 10:00 a.m. I help
out around the house.
More broadly, though,
this points to the need
for us to work with the
international community
to start setting up
some very clear rules of the road.
Right now it's sort of the Wild West.
At 12:00 p.m. I have lunch with Leon.
And then there's this one
where they're stuck in a
garage the whole time.
Like, what?
That's not a TV show, bro.
Like, where's the story?
It just makes no sense.
At 2:00 p.m. we'll check
out a basketball game.
Hot Carla, the local
pyro, is usually there.
She's become like my personal totem.
Whoo, three points, bitch.
I still don't understand
why people like sports.
They get so emotional
over the weirdest things.
But I do see the beauty in the rules,
the invisible code of chaos hiding
behind the menacing face of order.
At 4:30 p.m. I clean up
around the house again.
There hasn't been anything
like this in the past.
That's part of what makes
this issue of cybersecurity
so urgent.
At 6:00 p.m.
I have dinner with Leon.
Though maybe I just
need to make peace with it,
you know what I'm saying?
As you can tell, we eat
most meals together.
Like, maybe that's the show's point,
that shit is just pointless, you know?
Like, life, love,
and the meanings therein.
I'll tell you, the human condition
is a straight-up tragedy, cuz. Word.
Like I said, I never have to talk,
and the repetition is good for me now.
It keeps my regimen intact.
Two days a week I go to a church group.
I don't get the rules here either,
but I need to keep socializing myself.
It's good for me.
Besides, these people seem normal.
- Amen.
Do not get into a pattern
in which you are intimidated by
these kind of criminal attacks.
America knows how to solve problems,
and when we work together,
we can't be stopped.
A new future is ready to be written.
I've been keeping a journal.
It's the only way to keep my program
running like it's supposed to.
See you in the morning.
And then I go to bed.
My mom has no computer
or Internet access
to tempt me into the night.
All that's left for me is
just ordinary analog sleep
ending the day's loop.
You might not think it's a way to live,
but why not?
Repeating the same tasks each day
without ever having to think about them,
isn't that what everybody does?
Keep things on repeat
to go along with their "NCISes"
and Lexapro.
Isn't that where it's comfortable?
In the sameness?
Why your mom?
Why her specifically?
She's the strictest person I know.
But you've attributed a lot
of your childhood trauma...
Better the devil you know than the devil
you don't, right?
Do you feel alone?
Darlene comes by sometimes.
Is there anything you
miss about your old life?
It doesn't matter even if I did.
Why would you say that?
'Cause I can't trust myself back there.
Why do you think you
can't trust yourself?
I'd like you to respond
to my question, please.
Elliot, it took a lot for me
to talk to you after what you did,
but I agreed with the condition
that you were going to
be more open with me.
I was very clear when we discussed...
It's not that I don't trust myself.
I don't trust him.
Hello again.
Yes, I'm talking to you this time.
I'm sure you wanted to hear
what I told Krista back there,
but I'm not ready to trust you yet,
not after what you did.
You kept things from
me, and I don't know
if I can tell you secrets like before.
Friends are supposed to be
honest with each other,
and you weren't.
It's gonna take a while to
rebuild this relation...
Talking to your friend again?
I thought we were done with all that.
Here.
Check that out.
Lots of nicer friends in there for you.
We can't stay here.
There's more work to be done.
Our revolution needs a leader,
and what are we doing instead?
Journaling.
Che Guevara is throwing up
in his grave right now.
You think this is gonna get rid of me?
I am not to be gotten rid of.
This zombie act you're pulling?
It don't work on us.
This control you think you have?
It's an illusion.
You want my attention?
Tell me what I want to know.
Tell me where Tyrell is.
I can't do that.
Then go fu...
Are you done?
What's next on this roller coaster
of a regimen, needle-pointing?
It is not hyperbole to say
we're in a grave financial situation.
All of this cautionary
sentiment out there,
it's not just Wall Street hoopla.
The more I talk about it, the
more terrified I become.
Fortuntately, the original
plan that was put in place
was ineffective.
Most experts agree that
this is not just a crisis,
but a very dire one.
Something absolutely needs to be done.
Even though the European Union has been
denying that it could affect them,
this week we saw that they were wrong.
The banks cannot lend money
that they don't have
so the economy is at a standstill.
And I'm just the messenger.
I am telling you, folks,
this is what they don't
want you to hear,
because a union strike on
the Comet natural gas plant
will cause an energy shortage the likes
of which has never been
seen in the northeast.
Without literal power
we will have no power.
This is part of a strategy
to declare economic war on this country,
and they know it, they know
exactly what they are doing,
and 2015 will be known as
the year that America,
this great nation,
swapped democracy for dictatorship.
Ahh! Ahh! Ahh!
On television blabbing on and on and on,
telling people... lying to them.
Instead, bring honesty...
somebody who can explain it best.
because this "crisis" is happening.
Hello? Hello?
Why don't you tell your viewers
about the Weimar Republic?
Because the similarities
between them are disturbing.
Meaning the end of the
world as we know it.
Tyranny in the streets.
- Hello?
- Hello.
That's right.
Stop!
Well, what am I supposed to do?
I mean, nothing is working.
Unplug what?
Everything is inside the walls.
That's how it was installed
when I ordered the smart house package.
Now the alarm is going
off, and it's freezing.
It's below 40.
I have a place in Greenwich,
but you don't expect me to...
How long is it gonna take
before this all gets fixed?
The tracking on her phone is working,
and she's headed north as we speak.
How long you think she's
gonna stay away for?
Long enough.
The collective result of these attacks
could be a cyber Pearl Harbor,
physical destruction
and the loss of life,
and create a new, profound sense
of vulnerability.
As director of the CIA and
Secretary of Defense,
I have understood that cyber attacks...
I hope you don't mind I came.
Something wrong?
It's good to see you, Gideon.
You, too.
I know we didn't leave
things on the best of terms.
Is it true? What I heard about Allsafe?
Oh, there is no Allsafe.
I've had to furlough everyone.
I'm hoping to get up and running again,
but everyone's telling me it's over.
Gee, I wonder whose fault that is.
Was that you or me?
Getting all mixed up, I can't recall.
Let me get to my point.
The FBI believes that
I was behind the hack
or complicit in some way.
I've given them all the evidence I can.
I've cooperated every step of the way,
but they still keep coming at me.
They don't trust me.
In fact, I think they might
be hacking my email.
I know someone is.
And now you're wondering who
that someone is, aren't you?
There are logins from times and
machines I don't recognize.
Because if it was me, then
that means it was you.
How about it, huh?
Could you live with yourself
knowing that you framed Gideon?
I keep changing the password,
but it still hap...
Elliot?
- What's wrong?
- Go ahead, tell him.
Tell him that you're slowly
descending into madness.
- Stop.
- What? Stop what?
There are only so many times
before my bullets finally
penetrate that thick skull of yours,
and as the blood trickles out,
so goes any sense of reason.
Round and round we go,
you not knowing what
you did or didn't do,
our infinite loop of insanity.
If you know anything at all,
or if there's anything
you can do to help me...
I need you to.
I can't help you.
Are you really gonna let him
take the fall for this?
Look at him, a scared, small animal.
Well, that's... that's unacceptable.
Now he's doing what all small
animals do when they're scared,
pretend they're bigger and scarier.
Look, if you're not gonna
do anything about this,
I'm afraid you've left me no choice
but to go to them with what I know,
which, given the things I
know about the day you left,
it's pretty damning.
Now, I'm asking you one last time
to do the right thing.
He does have a point.
He does know a lot, perhaps too much.
I wonder if I slashed
open his neck right now,
would it be me doing it,
or would it be you?
- No.
- Yes.
I am going to go to them.
I'm going to tell them everything.
Do you understand, Elliot? Everything.
Truth is, though, right,
it doesn't matter.
You start adding up all the choices
you've been making, they
all add up to one thing.
You add up to one thing...
me.
What's going on over there?
I'm not gonna lie, Gideon got to me,
but now is when I need
the regimen the most.
After all, that's the whole
reason for the routine,
to stay as sane as possible
until he's gone,
and once he's gone,
I can finally be the real me again.
No, not just that it's pointless,
but maybe
it just means nothing, you know?
Like Costanza says, a
cold, random universe.
Bro, what's up with the...
Nothing, man.
Gideon's gonna rat you out.
He probably already has.
Hey, you can't ignore this.
They have eyes on you.
This is how they work you.
I'm not gonna change my mind.
I'm sticking to my regimen.
Hey, I am not some tumor to be excised,
do you understand? The opposite.
I'm the organ vital to your existence.
Now, if you insist on keeping this up,
I'm gonna go from annoyed
to hurt, and, kiddo,
trust me, you do not want
to hurt my feelings.
How do I take off a mask
when it stops being a mask,
when it's as much a part of me as I am?
We keep fighting.
Like the world we unmasked,
we will find our true selves again.
Maybe after wiping away
the thick, grimy film
of Facebook friend requests
and Vine stars
we can all see the light of day.
I know we haven't talked in a while.
Maybe you only trust me about as much
as I trust you right now,
but I'm gonna ask you to
have hope for me anyway.
Just, please, have hope.
I'm gonna take a selfie.
You guys ready?
Yeah!
- We got the balls!
- Whoo!
Whoo!
We got the balls!
Give me your phone.
- Why? I didn't post any...
- Give me your phone.
Ahh!
We are in a war,
and we are on the losing side of it.
We are on our knees
with guns to our heads,
and they are picking us off one by one.
Susan Jacobs,
the general counsel at E Corp.
You want to know what her nickname is
inside the company?
Madam Executioner,
not just because she could kill
any lawsuit filed against them,
but because those lawsuits
usually involved deaths.
These are the cowards
we are dealing with.
We have been on our knees for too long,
and it's time to stand up.
Make it a four-hour SDR if necessary.
Take surveillance detection stops.
Go into pharmacies. Run errands.
Disrupt data points.
No one takes the same
route back here twice.
I don't want anyone
burning this location.
Where is everyone else?
Don't know.
They were always half in.
What... what you're doing here,
Darlene, and what you're saying?
I mean, you sounded like George W. Bush,
for crying out loud.
Okay, first of all, that's low.
Secondly, give me some credit.
The speech is bullshit, but it works.
- It riles them up.
- Yeah, to what end though?
You know, sawing off balls,
making protest signs?
We were more than that.
I mean, we... you know, we
accomplished something.
We... we took them down.
Then why does it feel like
they're still winning?
That what we did made
it worse, not better?
You know I'm right.
We didn't finish them off.
That's all there is to it.
People everywhere came out
to support us mobiley,
and right now they need to
know we haven't given up,
that we meant what we said
about changing the world.
Don't be half in like the others.
This thing we started, it
deserves more than that.
Have you, uh, have you seen Elliot?
That's not important.
This is everything right now.
Absolutely unfair, madam,
absolutely unfair.
We were done with our payments.
Ma'am, we are doing our best here.
At this moment we cannot verify
that you paid all your payments.
Absolutely ridiculous. I have.
I have all my bills right here.
I was never late on one,
and I also have copies of
the checks that I sent...
People have been forging paper records.
We haven't set up a system to
verify these sorts of claims.
It took me three weeks to get
this appointment, madam.
Now you're telling me you can't help me?
What kind of business is this?
I've been responsible
for the last 20 years
in paying off my home.
Where's your accountability?
Yet, if the tables were turned,
you would have kicked
me out of my own house.
You know what? Cancel my account.
I'm done doing business with you crooks.
You deserve what you're getting.
Ma'am, I can't say
for sure we can give you all your money
if you close right now.
Unbelievable.
I know what I have.
I just want to cancel.
It's on my computer too.
I have the IT guy helping me right now.
Sorry I'm late.
I was coming from my place in Greenwich.
I was on the phone with
the FBI all night.
We can't confirm the sender,
but the email we received is authentic,
more than likely the same hackers
from the ransomware.
Unbelievable.
What are their demands, again?
$5.9 million.
$5.9 million
to be delivered to Battery Park City,
9:00 p.m. tonight, no police.
If we want to pay the ransom,
the FBI will not sanction it.
We cannot negotiate with these people.
Our techs are looking into it.
We'll find a way to decrypt
it and get the system...
How long?
Five days, tops.
Five days for our banking
system to be down?
That's a lot of money down the drain.
I don't even want to mention the optics.
We can't afford this hack right now,
and frankly, I think we
can find $5.9 million
in between our couch cushions.
It's nothing.
My opinion as general
counsel is to pay it.
What's this other request they made?
"You must send one of your chiefs
and no one else?"
I think they meant one
of our chief officers.
This is a joke.
Did they really expect one
of us to go out there, hmm?
What are we talking about here?
These people
are terrorists, pure and simple.
Unfortunately, I have to
agree with Scott on this.
It's risky.
We have no idea what these
guys are capable of.
So you think we should pay the ransom,
but you don't want any of us to do it?
We can get one of our security
officers to go undercover.
Yes, and risk all of this
blowing up in our faces.
No.
If we're going to even
consider doing this,
we shouldn't give them any
reason to do more damage.
I'll do it.
I'm Chief Technology Officer.
I qualify.
I'll do it.
If we're gonna pay these bastards,
I want to be the one that faces them.