What if this all went away?
The money, this city, all of it?
The world is filled
with stupid people,
and I get paid a lot to be smart.
Susan Jacobs,
the general counsel at E Corp.
Madam executioner.
The tracking on her phone is working.
How long you think she's
gonna stay away for?
Long enough.
Have you ever considered which part
of our scheme motivates you?
The FBI announced today
Tyrell Wellick and fsociety
engaged in this attack.
Are you alone?
That's called a femtocell.
So we can get every FBI email,
text message, and document.
We just owned the FBI.
They have something called
Operation Berenstain.
Possibly heavy surveillance.
They're trying to cover their tracks,
and right now, we're the tracks.
HAPPY THANKSGIVING
RON'S COFFEE
Go ahead.
Whole milk.
Must be some kind of revolutionary.
No... I...
Just 'cause everyone's into this
almond coconut shit nowadays.
It's...
not...
What kind of phone do you have?
Oh... this?
Yeah, it's... it's a Nexus.
Yeah, I'm an Android guy.
Hate Apple.
Think iPhones are for pussies.
What are you on?
iPhone.
Right.
You think they suck so
much, but they're faster.
Bullshit.
I mean, if you're talking boot times,
then it's Android all day,
and if you're talking net speed,
Chrome on Android has
better HTML5 compliance
and runs JavaScript so
much faster than Safari.
No competition.
Oh, yeah?
Prove it.
Go to this benchmarking website.
We'll compare speeds.
Okay.
Game on.
Are you on the Wi-Fi here?
- Yes.
(Start hioctane 2.0A)
- It's slow as shit.
(Running hioctane...)
Agreed. It's hit or miss.
There's another Ron's Coffee Shop.
Oh, 14th Street. Yeah, I know.
Everyone always Reddits about that one.
Crazy fast.
You can practically stream
4K videos on your laptop.
LISTENING FOR INCOMING CONNECTIONS
RECEIVING CONNECTION FROM 192.251.68.243
Why aren't you there now, then?
ATTEMPTING ROOT PRIVILEGE ESCALATION
HIOCTANE SCORE
You got me.
iPhones suck.
I'm... meeting someone.
What about you?
- Same.
- Cool, cool, cool.
MOBLEY_ANDROID
Oh, the old malicious
browser benchmark trick.
I see you already own
this newb's whole system.
I like it.
Didn't your mom ever tell
you not to surf websites
that have an embedded
Stagefright exploit?
Can't drop the proverbial soap
around a black-hat bitch
like this, Mobley.
Darlene, I...
I thought I was meeting Elliot.
Me too.
Relax, kids, this isn't the
stranger danger episode.
Elliot couldn't make it,
but no need to connip.
I'll download you.
Well, I'm not gonna shout.
Get over here, tubs.
Don't...
Before we start, he wanted
me to read you guys something.
Now, keep in mind these
are his words, not mine.
He's a touch melodramatic.
"What I'm about to tell
you is top secret.
"A conspiracy bigger than all of us.
"There's a powerful group
of people out there
"that are secretly running the world.
"I'm talking about the
guys no one knows about,
"the guys that are invisible,
the top 1% of the top 1%"...
*MR.ROBOT*
Season 02 Episode 08
"eps2.6_succ3ss0r,p12"
Precisely Synchronized by srjanapala
What's with the looks?
And this is happening tomorrow?
DATABASE BROWSER
CONFERENCE CALL FBI/L...
DISCUSS ON-GOING INVESTIGATION
"BERENSTAIN"
CONNECTED
RECORDER
ACCESS CODE: 7174800
Your passcode has been confirmed.
Please wait while you're
joined to the conference.
Hello?
Hello.
Hey, Douglas Gitelman, WFO.
Lorin Connor, FBI New York.
Hi, guys, Michael
Kirkpatrick, New York.
Anyone else on?
Just waiting on you.
Hello, all. Everyone on?
It's Kirby, Megan, and Zach
from the seventh floor.
Yup, all here.
Great. Don't have a ton of time.
It is the nation's birthday, after all,
so let's get down to brass tacks.
E Corp, Google, AT&T, Uber,
Apple, Verizon, Facebook...
all 23 of these listed
companies have been complicit
in aiding the FBI in
Operation Berenstain.
Jesus, what is that noise?
Okay, tape's busted.
Just grab another one
and we'll do it again.
Yeah.
- Okay.
- F.... it.
I'll keep it simple.
Happy Fourth of July, fellow Americans.
On this patriotic holiday,
we wanted to remind you,
under the Universal
Declaration of Human Rights,
Privacy is a Right.
Or at least it used to be.
Listen closely to a
classified conference call
we recently intercepted
between the FBI agents
that so earnestly promise you
fidelity, bravery, and integrity.
We've all been down this warrantless
wiretapping road, Doug.
If word were to get out about
Operation Berenstain...
Technically we're covered under
public safety of the Patriot Act.
Not to this scale.
Three million Americans under surveillance
for Five/Nine without a warrant?
Not to mention back door access
to every goddamn smart phone
out there. It's never going to...
Come on, Kirby, screw the 3 million.
They got us the 17 we're
building our case around now.
Sixteen... in the code name case...
Right, sixteen, one's deceased.
Doesn't help that Comey
hasn't signed off on it.
The fact that we're keeping it from him
does not bode well for your case.
He's an uptight choirboy.
No one's gonna be crying over
how we catch these terrorists.
I guarantee that.
The FBI has 3 million
of you innocent citizens
under surveillance for no reason.
Their tyrannical rape of
our private data ends now.
FBI, be warned.
Your access to our lives
is officially denied.
Pursue us at your own peril.
We do not compromise.
We will not back down.
We will destroy you.
We are...
fsociety.
COPY FUXFBI.MP4
UPLOAD YOUR VIDEOS TO VIMEO
CHOOSE FILES TO UPLOAD
FUXFBI.MP4 - OPEN
Smartphone out there...
It's never going to be...
Come on, Kirby, screw the 3 million...
Video's up.
16 in the code name case.
Right, 16. One's deceased.
It doesn't help that Comey
hasn't signed off on it.
Stop listening to that. It's
making you more paranoid.
What about this... code name case thing?
They said they have 16
suspects under surveillance.
Video's getting hits. It's
starting to get reposted.
They said one of the suspects
is dead.
They gotta be talking
about Romero, right?
We have to be on that list.
I uploaded the full Berenstain call
and transcript to WikiLeaks.
Oh!... Oh! Come on, slow your roll, bro.
No one's going anywhere.
We gotta monitor the
fallout of the video
before anyone makes a move.
Exposing their program
is gonna shut down the investigation.
I don't care anymore.
I'm officially done.
You don't wanna do this.
You mean the... the Dark Army
doesn't want me to do this, bro?
No, no, no, no, I mean you.
'Cause when the Dark Army
finds out the FBI nails you,
which they will...
It's lights out.
No questions asked. You feel me?
Hey, stop.
You really think you
can force me to stay?
Without a doubt.
Guys!
JULY 4TH LIVE BAND
KARAOKE!
Happy Fourth of July,
fellow Americans.
On this patriotic holiday,
we wanted to remind you,
under the Universal
Declaration of Human Rights,
- Privacy is a Right...
- Yo.
We're still on a date, remember?
Why is this video such
a big deal to you?
I'm gonna get another drink.
Hey, hey there, Ang.
Steve?
What are you doing here?
Oh, karaoke.
You know, gotta please the missus.
Missed you at your dad's barbecue today.
Yeah, I couldn't make it.
Right. Yeah, right.
You gotta be busy these days.
Congrats on everything.
Still, though, that's gotta be
tough on your father, though.
Having to watch while you bow down
to those bastards that
killed your mother.
That can't be an easy
pill for him to swallow.
For you, though, swallowing's
not really a problem,
now, is it?
Just... who the hell do
you think you are, anyway?
You're a plumber.
Right, Steve?
You've had, what,
60 years at life?
That's the best you can come up with?
Literally cleaning shit for a living?
I'm 27,
and I've got a six-figure salary
at the biggest conglomerate in history,
and I'm just getting started.
That's who I am.
Don't do this!
Now you're only at class B
felony kidnapping charges.
Don't bump it up to class A.
Shut the f... up!
You have no idea the shit you're in.
One of us should have
been watching the GPS.
This is some next-level shit, man.
Okay, we didn't have a choice.
We couldn't let her go to the cops.
Yeah, well, she can ID all of us now.
She saw everything, our whole setup.
- She knows who we are.
- Help!
Hello? I know you can see me!
God damn it. Trenton, go shut her up.
Go!
F... it.
I say we take our chances out there.
Let her go. Take off.
- Go our separate ways.
- Yeah, right.
Then there'll be a manhunt
with our faces on it.
Yeah, if there isn't one already.
Hello!
I need the bathroom.
Not yet.
I kinda can't control it.
Let me check downstairs first.
I really need to go.
It'll only take a second.
You guys don't know what
the hell you're doing,
do you?
You're Muslim?
Is that what all this is about?
ISIS or something?
You're all a bunch of goddamn animals.
Make it quick.
We were all there. You heard the call.
They have a secret
surveillance program on us.
Jesus, you're a broken record.
Man, you wanna live in denial?!
Go ahead, okay? Go right ahead.
All of you can't accept the
fact that maybe we f...d up.
Okay? Take a look at the city.
It's going to shit, man.
Now, first it'll be blackouts.
Then it'll be the National Guard.
- Either we go now or...
- Jesus!
Keep it together!
Darlene.
This isn't exactly what
I meant by "shut her up."
Okay, well...
maybe our problem solved itself.
Oh, so, what, we just let her die?
We need to get her to a hospital.
No.
No, not until we're sure she won't talk.
Tie her up.
That's a nasty head wound.
Okay, well, then we
don't have much time.
To do what?
Own her.
♪ Welcome to your life ♪
♪ There's no turning back ♪
Grab her phone.
♪ Even while we sleep ♪
- PHONE EXTRACTION SUMMARY
- Got it.
I'll jump on her laptop.
♪ We will find you ♪
♪ Acting on your ♪
♪ Best behavior ♪
♪ Turn your back on Mother Nature... ♪
She's got three email
accounts on her phone.
♪ Wants to rule the world ♪
NYU CARDIOLOGY, NICOLE, ORDERS, SUBURBS
Not seeing anything on
her corporate or Hotmail.
MY USERNAME IS MISSING, ADDRESS
CHANGE, PURCHASES BY...
♪ It's my own desire ♪
There's gotta be something
we can blackmail her with.
Just keep looking.
♪ It's my own remorse ♪
- HOW CAN WE HELP? I FORGOT MY PASSWORD
- ♪ Help me to decide ♪
♪ Help me to decide ♪
♪ Help me make ♪
♪ The most of freedom and of pleasure ♪
♪ Nothing ever lasts forever ♪
♪ Everybody wants ♪
I got into her Gmail.
Don't see anything in here.
NYU CARDIOLOGY: LIVING WITH A PACEMAKER
Did you check for any hidden partitions?
- Obviously.
- I'll check the office.
♪ The light won't find you ♪
♪ Holding hand while the walls ♪
♪ Come crumblin' down ♪
- Okay, anything?
- No, nothing.
She's a lawyer. She's gotta have dirt.
AMAZON CHECKOUT, AMAZON
BOOKS, GOOGLE MAPS...
Wait, I see Yahoo Mail
in her web history.
Maybe we do a pass on her drive?
Try to recover any deleted files.
♪ Had to fade it ♪
♪ Everybody wants to rule the world ♪
Maybe we could target
Yahoo's server logs
and cross-reference any
incoming connections from here.
Might lead to an account
name and password hash.
- I could use bash bug.
- Or what about this?
YAHOO USERNAME AND PASSWORD
What if we do find
something on her, huh?
What then?
Cazadores on the rocks, please.
I love that song.
You really have a desire
to rule the world?
Oh, my desires go way beyond that.
Pretty sure my
daughter's older than you.
What about your granddaughter?
No, no, she'll be ten tomorrow.
I'm taking her to the zoo, actually.
Thanks.
Well, better get back to my colleagues.
You could do that,
or you could stay here,
talk to me.
I had nothing to do with Five/Nine.
I'm in finance, for f...'s sake.
You think I wanted to
implode the economy?
Come on...
No, I agree with Mr. Jones here.
I've been scratching
my head on this one,
but evidence is evidence,
and holiday or not, I had
to follow up on this.
Found this incriminating little guy
at a critical location tied
to the Five/Nine hack.
The shell's microstamp leads
right to your client's gun.
The gun that he had in the
city of New York illegally,
I might add.
Immunity is on the table
in exchange for a name.
That's all I care about.
Let's keep this friendly.
I need a doctor.
Yeah, it's pretty bad.
Nice place you got.
Comfy.
Is your place in Greenwich this cush?
I worked hard for what I have.
You know, I'm glad
you came home,
but my friends
are freaking out.
Came up with this neat little plan
to blackmail you for your silence.
Hacked your emails.
We got some good stuff too.
Nice little Petraeus email
scam you got going on there.
You shouldn't get hot and heavy
with your presiding judges, Suze.
I'm sure you're aware that's illegal,
but...
I know you don't care
about things like that.
You'd slime your way around it
and f... us over just
like you did my dad.
Who's dead, by the way.
But you...
You aged very well.
The first time I saw you, I was four.
Still remember it.
On the news
in the courtroom when
they cleared E Corp
of all the bullshit they
put my family through.
And you were in the back
behind a sea of suits,
and you laughed.
It was so quick, no one even noticed.
No one but me.
Four-year-old little me.
So...
I'm happy
I get to look you in the eye.
I have taken down your company,
taken over your home,
and now...
I have you.
Okay.
So you got me.
Where do we go from here?
I'm sure we can figure something out.
I already have.
She just...
flipped out.
I was just trying to scare her back.
It was just a stun gun.
No.
No, no, she...
No, she had a heart condition.
I mean, there were lots of emails
from her doctor.
You di...
you didn't see any of those?
No.
Just go.
You two don't need to be here.
We'll wipe down the house
and figure it out.
INBOX
ACCOUNT
AUTOMATIC REPLIES (OUT OFF OFFICE)
DO NOT SEND AUTOMATIC REPLIES
SEND AUTOMATIC REPLIES
I WILL BE OUT OF THE OFFICE FROM...
I WILL BE OUT OF THE OFFICE FROM
JULY 7TH TO JULY 27TH.
FOR ANY EMERGENCIES PLEASE CONTACT:
LEGAL@E-CORP-USA.COM.
SORRY FOR ANY INCONVENIENCE.
HAVE A GREAT DAY.
You think she actually...
Has to be self-defense.
What's the plan?
We can't stay here.
Who knows who's gonna be
waiting for you at home?
Dark Army, FBI, cops.
I can't leave my family.
If you had that much to lose,
you shouldn't have done
this in the first place.
But I did this for them.
What we did was
colossally fu...g stupid,
and we can't afford not
to realize that anymore.
Peace, Trent.
Yeah, I'm on my way.
All right, my vote,
we leave it here,
wipe our prints, and
just make a run for it.
We can't.
The others'll be back soon.
They'll find her.
Why don't I just... just text them
and tell them the place is burned?
Can't take the risk they won't listen
and come back anyway.
We need to get rid of it.
We ain't doing shit.
I'll see if my guys can take care of it.
Okay, no offense, but I
don't trust them either.
This is my responsibility.
Well, if this is the
part of the conversation
where you start throwing out ideas
like acid and wood chippers,
I ain't obliging.
This isn't a conversation.
We need to do what we
always do when we go
into full wipe-down mode after a hack.
Hurry up.
You know you screwed me last time?
You let all the dogs go.
I almost got fired.
What was that all about anyway?
Not like it matters. They
all ended up back here.
So as a matter of policy,
it's gonna cost you double this time.
Double?
Wait, we don't have double, man.
We... we barely pull out cash.
What about Ecoin?
It's worth more than cash anyway.
Pull out your phone.
What the f... is in there?
I'm paying you enough for privacy.
PAY TO...
AMOUNT TO PAY: E 2000.00
ECOIN: PAYMENT SENT
It's done.
All yours.
Susan donated them
from her cold storage.
It's not as if she can use them anymore.
She can pay for her own funeral.
No...
Oh, no, easy, easy, wait.
Just move it...
God.
Rug's too big.
No shit.
We need to take her out.
This is some traumatizing
shit. You know that?
Hey.
Come to my place tonight.
Come on, let's get some sleep.
You shouldn't be alone right now.
I didn't know I could do that.
You did what you had to do.
No, that's the thing.
I don't feel bad.
I always knew there was a part of me
that wanted to do this to her
for what she did, but...
I figured when that time came,
something would stop me...
But it didn't.
Hey, come on. Look,
you're just in shock.
All right? Look, come on.
Just... let's get some sleep.
Okay?
Okay.
I did what you say for me.
Okay, I used key under mat.
I put pizza inside.
No one inside. No one.
You didn't see anything weird or...
No, no one inside.
No one inside.
Okay, fine.
That's $20.
Wait.
Ca... can I... can I
have the other pizza?
It's another delivery, man.
It's another delivery.
Look, give me the other pizza.
I'm f... g nervous, man.
Have you guys ever
thought about moving?
What's this?
Maybe we should move
somewhere cheaper.
I don't think the
city is safe anymore,
not with everything going on.
Don't be silly. Moving
is impossible right now.
The bank is fighting us on the deed.
It's a mess. They're not
letting anyone sell.
In fact, we may be at a bigger risk
of losing the money we
did invest in this home.
But we can find another place.
Dinner's almost ready.
I'll check outside.
Sir, open up. FBI.
Sir, if you don't open the door,
we're gonna break it down.
Mr. Markesh, we didn't
mean for you to be
waiting here this long,
but with all the
bureaucracy and red tape,
it's getting a little
bonkers around here.
Yeah, well, I've been
waiting here all night.
What the f... is going on?
I feel your pain.
I've been stuck here all night too.
It's depressing, isn't it?
Here's what we're gonna do.
We're gonna talk, and all
you have to do is listen.
Because, believe it or not, Mr. Markesh,
you could be real instrumental
in helping to solve this Five/Nine case.
Leslie Romero.
Forgive me, hon, you do know
your friend was found murdered?
My heart goes out to you.
It's very unfortunate.
I went over to his mother's
after everything went down.
I wanted to offer my condolences,
and I took a quick look around
while I was over there.
That's when I found this.
An end of the world party
featuring DJ Mobley.
I'm not an EDM fan myself,
but a quick search on
the wayback machine,
and guess what we found
all the way from 2003.
You.
An Angelfire page that you created
from back in the day.
Your very own DJ Mobley fan page.
In fact, curiously enough,
you were the only one that ever
created a fan page of this guy.
Must have really spoken to you.
Trust me, I feel the same way
about "Romy and Michele's
High School Reunion."
But like you, I found myself
very much in the minority.
So a big fan.
Obscure DJ with a unique name.
Seems like the perfect recipe
for how a hacker handle gets born.
Here's the deal:
we want Tyrell Wellick,
not Tyrell Wellick's DJ.
Your friend is dead, and
that's a sad thing,
but at this point, the best
thing that could happen
would be if there's
something you can tell me...
names, people,
any information at all
that you can give us from
that party that would help.
Lawyer.
I want a lawyer.
Did you have any evidence on this guy?
This is not the strategy
we have implemented.
Top down, not bottom up.
We needed to get some traction.
This is a way.
He's a minor player that
won't blow our strategy.
He'll start flushing
some of these guys out.
Are you not watching the news?
We are in a world of shit
because of this leaked conference call.
The OPR is going to be
coming down on us any day.
It's all over the Senate
Intelligence Hearings.
The deputy director,
assistant director of Cyber Division
and the EAD are all getting fired.
Comey's about to announce that
Operation Berenstain is dead,
and you just held this guy for 12 hours
for no reason.
You have to think about
how this looks, Dom.
Whatever paranoia you've
put into him is done,
just by picking him up.
Let him go.
NEW CONVERSATION
TO TRENTON
DESTRUCTS IN 5 SECONDS
WIPE DATA/FACTORY RESET
YES. DELETE ALL USER DATA.
WIPING DATA
WICKR MESSENGER:
YOU HAVE 1 NEW MESSAGE
MESSAGE FROM DJMOBLEY
WE'RE BURNT. MUST LEAVE ASAP.
MEET ME AT THE PLACE WE FIRST MET. 12PM.
I'll be back later.
I lost her.
I don't know what I did wrong.
I thought she was into me.
Don't let it get you in the dumps.
Getting into the mind of a woman,
it's the toughest route for
even the best sources.
I can't get into it right now.
This fsociety video's
blowing up in our face.
That's some f... d-up
shit you guys did.
It's got me all paranoid.
How do I know you guys
aren't watching me too?
We look like fools. Shit's
worse than Snowden.
Privacy rights
activist Edward Snowden.
When you say I don't care
- about the right to privacy...
- Speak of the devil.
Because I have nothing to hide,
that's no different than saying
I don't care about freedom of speech
because I have nothing to say.
Despite the cybersecurity breach
in obtaining the information
on Operation Berenstain,
the controversy over Privacy Rights
has prompted calls for greater
government transparency.
- Advocates are demanding...
- Look, I'm done with this.
You know, she's stone cold anyway, Dom.
I'm not gonna lie...
I kinda got hurt.
She never talked about fsociety
or her old friends from back in the day?
She hasn't given up anything
since you first put me on her,
and she bailed on me for
some old dude at the bar.
A contact?
I think she's just into old dudes.
Paying employees only a
portion of their wages.
In a statement, UWUA leaders claimed...
REGULATORS! LET'S DANCE
Cisco?
Yo, what's up?
What's up?
PASSWORD
How long you been up?
I just got up.
I jumped straight in the shower.
I'll be out in a sec, though.
You all right?
Yeah, fine.
NEW CONVERSATION
TO: DJMOBLEY
I'M HERE. WHERE R U?
BEEN WAITING 2 HOURS.
DESTRUCTS IN 5 SECONDS
Cisco: I have her, she's with me.
Good job with the femtocell,
the backdoor is in play...
...Stage 2 is about to begin.
You all right?
Yo, what the f.. ?