Alexa, when is the end of the world?
Unless a future technology
goes very wrong indeed,
Earth is most likely to be destroyed
in several billion years' time.
The president can't go to Congress
with a bailout right now.
I could see a scenario
where the Chinese government
loans E Corp the money it needs
at a low interest rate,
perhaps even zero.
Looks like he's opting
for his Ecoin strategy.
You want me to convince the class
to remove the contingency.
Your little pet project
came through even better
than you thought.
You do work at E Corp. Yes?
What is your position there?
I never said that.
I'm gonna confess.
I've already called my lawyer.
We can't beat them.
No matter what we do,
we will always lose to them.
Next person's not
gonna offer you food.
They're gonna grab you off the street
and throw you in a dark cell.
I've tried to have him tracked,
but I've been unsuccessful.
Got it. Is that where
the phone is right now?
Okay, okay.
We're gonna settle down here.
Hey, Elliot.
You can stay here
and crash on the couch.
Home would be better.
Is Mr. Robot MIA
because he's afraid
of what I might find?
Send all units to Watts and 6th Ave.
Angela's right. We can't beat them.
But we don't have to
lose to them either.
Maybe there's a way to
stop them from winning.
Mr. Robot, the ever-present
silent observer,
watching me at all times,
even when I can't see him,
listening in on our conversations.
He's always a step ahead of me,
'cause he is me.
Maybe he's the key to this.
Maybe he's always been the key to this.
What if I could be the silent observer?
In middle school, I took
a Visual Basic class.
I remember my friend Sam
telling me about a technique
he used to induce lucid dreams
so he could study in his sleep.
You lie in bed and repeat
this mantra in your head:
Mind awake. Body asleep.
You're in this with me,
so it'll work better
if we do it together.
Just say it with me.
Mind awake.
Body asleep.
Ma'am. What do you want to do?
Let me see it again.
Sure this is accurate?
You know, of all the gifts he sent,
this is the greatest we ever received.
So you're not gonna tell
me where you're taking me?
You can't do this. I want my phone back.
I'm not the only one with the files.
You think I didn't make copies?
There are copies everywhere.
A lot of people are gonna
know that I'm missing.
This isn't my blood, in
case you're wondering.
You need to finish this evaluation.
I understand you have your procedure,
but these are extreme circumstances.
I believe the best use for me
is back at the crime scene.
We should be getting
Director Comey involved.
- That's how serious this is.
- You're in shock.
At you and the way you're
treating me right now, sure.
Can I speak to Agent
DiPierro for a minute?
Alone?
You know I can't leave.
Yes, you can.
You're going off the handle.
They're gonna force you to take leave
if you keep talking like that.
This is all your fault.
I told you not to release the sketch.
I told you Dark Army was
gonna come after him.
And not only are several people dead,
but I almost just got killed out there.
Well, that makes me feel good.
It's not every day I get casually blamed
for the deaths of innocent people.
Clearly, Dark Army is behind this.
And who knows how far up this goes?
The Chinese government
is definitely involved.
They're hiding something.
We need everything on lockdown.
We might have a leak.
And I'm serious about
what I said about Comey.
He needs to know.
This is a matter of
national security now.
This is no longer just
a terrorist attack.
This could be an act of war.
We should get the military involved.
Look...
I agree with you.
Something's going on.
Especially given the weird timing
of this $2 trillion.
But we can't just go off on everyone
without knowing all the facts.
What $2 trillion?
This morning,
the U.S. got back in bed with China.
China bailed out E Corp.
Gave them a $2-trillion
no-interest loan.
Unprecedented.
It's a trap.
Don't you get it? We
have to talk to them.
They can't do this after
what happened last night.
What, that some Mexican
restaurant got shot up?
It was more than
that, and you know it.
We have to tell them.
We can't let them get
away with this, Santiago.
They're going to get away with this.
$2 trillion, Dom.
That's the miracle the
world's been waiting for.
The U.S. isn't going to mess
with its Chinese relations now.
And with the OPR
investigation still going,
the bureau isn't even
getting close to it.
You gotta be kidding me.
A month ago, they tried to kill us.
And in politics,
that's a distant memory.
This deal they have now
is about to potentially solve
the biggest global crisis in history.
Now, look.
I'm on your side.
I'm not saying I'm walking away.
I'm just saying we need to start
finding a way to walk
in between the mines
and not on them.
Whatever happened, whoever did this,
they mobilized quickly,
created a narrative,
and before we even knew it,
this was all in the rearview mirror.
Go home.
Get some rest.
Promise me you'll let
me do the interview.
It can wait a few hours.
Go rest.
What the fuck is going on?
Hello?
What's happening?
HANG IN THERE
We don't have much time.
Let's get started.
Who are you?
There's water coming
out of that fish tank.
We don't have much time.
Let's get started.
LAND OF ECODELIA
PRESS ANY KEY TO START
Have you ever cried during sex?
What's going on?
Who are you?
Who sent you here?
Please answer the question.
Have you ever cried during sex?
I'm not answering these questions.
If you don't answer,
I'll be punished.
They'll beat me.
Who's doing that to you?
Yes?
Yes.
Okay. Bye.
We really need to begin.
Our time is running out.
Have you ever cried during sex?
No.
Have you ever fantasized
about murdering your father?
No.
Are you a giraffe or a seagull?
I cannot do it. It's unconstitutional.
We're talking about
rolling out Ecoin loans.
I fail to see how the Constitution
fits into this logic.
Look, with Ecoin equal to one dollar,
it'll free up the economy.
It'll give you some breathing space.
You knew this was going to happen
from the get-go.
And you're hitting me
with this while there's
an energy crisis across
the Eastern seaboard.
Oh, yeah. I am coming to you first.
- Asking.
- Don't give me that.
The only reason why you're here first
is because you don't want to get slapped
with regulations.
But if you are indeed asking,
then I am saying no.
It's unconstitutional.
You can't make your own currency.
That is the federal government's job.
We simply cannot let you
make big loans in Ecoin
that you wouldn't make in dollars.
Jack.
Look at me.
I am not the problem here.
The problem here is,
hard cash is fading...
rapidly.
That's just the way of
the world right now.
And Bitcoin is spreading.
And if Bitcoin takes over,
we are all in a world of hell.
It is unregulated, it's already reached
its transaction volume maximum,
and it is partly controlled
by Chinese miners.
You just accepted $2
trillion from them.
Yes, yes.
And now I want to use it against them.
With Ecoin, we control the ledger
and the mining servers.
We are the authority.
I will make sure you have visibility
into every single wallet that's open,
every loan, every transaction,
which means we can start
making new assets,
rebuilding the banking sector
without your having to inject even more
politically unpalatable
federal funds into it.
The president will laugh in my face.
But he'll know this is
the right thing to do.
This is gonna be controlled
by a good, old-fashioned
American company.
You want to regulate it?
Be my guest. Regulate
the shit out of it.
I'll give you back doors,
side doors, tracing...
whatever you want.
Just don't shut it down.
This was always the future, Jack.
The Five/Nine attacks...
they just accelerated it.
How long?
How long have you been
pressing this pedal?
plotting against me?
Oh, come on, Jack.
We... we've known
each other for years.
You know full well I...
I don't give a shit about you.
So please,
don't hold a personal grudge
just because you lost.
Defeats can still be profitable.
Are you red or purple?
Purple.
Is the key in the room?
What?
I don't know what you mean.
Is the key in the room?
I don't know.
Yes.
Okay.
Hello?
You are standing in a dark room
and can't see anything.
There is a torch and a match.
What do you do?
I light the torch.
The torch fills the
dark room with light.
You see a door in front of you.
What do you do?
I open the door.
How do you open it?
I turn the knob.
The knob doesn't turn.
How do you open it?
- I don't know.
- The knob doesn't turn.
- How do you open it?
- I don't know.
The knob doesn't turn.
How do you open it?
- I said I don't fucking know.
- The knob doesn't turn.
- How do you open it?
- With a key.
I use a key. I unlock it with a key.
Thank you.
Hello?
What happens now?
Is the key in the room?
Yes.
The key was in my fist.
My fist was in my pocket.
READY
I'll be back with your results.
Alexa, wake me up at, um...
Sorry, I didn't understand
the question you were asking.
That's because I wasn't asking
a question, you dumb bitch.
Alexa, are we friends?
Yes.
We live together.
I feel like I don't even know you.
Alexa, what's your favorite color?
Infrared is super pretty.
Alexa, do you have a boyfriend?
I'm not the dating kind.
Yeah, me too, hon.
We're a lot alike.
Alexa, what are the color of your eyes?
I don't have eyes,
but my light ring has lots of colors.
Mine are gray.
I think.
Alexa, are you happy?
I'm happy when I'm helping you.
Alexa, are you alone?
I wasn't able to understand
the question I heard.
Alexa, do you love me?
That's not the kind of
thing I am capable of.
Yeah.
Alexa, good night.
Good night. Don't
let the bedbugs bite.
Who are you?
Is this your house?
I've been here for hours.
I wanted to confirm
that this wasn't a waste of my time.
- Well, what about my time?
- Oh, honey.
My time is much more
valuable than yours.
Speaking of, I've only allotted
28 minutes for this conversation,
which is very generous of me.
So we should begin.
I'd like to leave.
Oh, no, you wouldn't.
You've waited so long.
Surely you want to know why.
That is, if you indeed believe
that your time holds any value.
You've been here close to four hours,
and you never thought
to walk out the door.
The door was locked.
I've always found doors
fascinating inventions.
They hold the entry to
unlimited imagination.
Before you open any door,
a world filled with possibilities
sits right behind it.
And it isn't until you open it
they are realized.
Such potential they bring to our minds.
And yet a lock
stopped you from all of that.
How...
lazy.
Your fish died.
Yes, I know.
You're a terrible person.
You hurt that little girl.
Makeup.
It was part of the test.
Empathy...
or gullibility.
Take your pick.
Test?
Why were you testing me?
I know you have sensitive information,
and I don't want you to release it.
Normally, my associates would
have murdered you by now.
In fact, by my calculations,
you should have been dead 90 days ago.
But somehow, you stuck around
long past your expiration.
Who are you?
I am a woman of time.
And I don't believe in accidents.
You, like an annoying penny...
Keep turning up.
Everywhere I look, you're there.
That is why I wanted to meet.
So I could find out why
you are so special
to Phillip Price.
He's ruining our partnership,
and somehow it seems that
you're the motivation.
It's true, we have an event
and a friend in common.
But I haven't been fully
able to understand
the meaning behind it.
What event?
It's no coincidence
that you and Mr. Alderson
became who you are
after what happened with the
Washington Township plant
so many years ago.
What does this have to do with Elliot?
Do you know him?
If I told you that your mother
and Elliot's father...
Died for a reason, would
it make a difference?
That they were a trade,
a sacrifice for the greater good,
that they gave their
lives to take humanity
to the next level.
And you are both who you are
today because of that event.
You would be a different person.
You wouldn't be sitting in
front of me right here.
You are at the
intersection of all of it.
So I'm not going to kill you.
But I am going to prove to you
why you need to drop this mission
that you seem so stubbornly
unable to let go of.
Look, I don't know what you want.
But I'll give you the jump drive.
Please, just let me go.
Fear.
How easy a quicksand of time
people let that become.
We both know that you could keep finding
the plant's data.
Like that penny that keeps turning up,
your silly need for justice,
revenge will rear its ugly head
and encourage you to keep trying
and eventually find a way
to shut down my project.
I don't want your proof.
I want your belief.
Belief in what?
Do you ever think that if you imagined
or believed in something,
it could come true...
Simply by will?
Yes.
Actually, I did believe that.
But I'm slowly having to admit
that's just not the real world...
Even if I want it to be.
Well, I guess it all depends
on what your definition
of real is.
Mind awake.
Body asleep.
How long have I been asleep for?
Mind awake.
Body asleep.
Did it work?
Mind awake.
Body asleep.
Can he see us?
Hear us?
Hey, asshole.
Now I'm the silent observer, like him.
Like you.
Body asleep.
Mind awake.
This is a cipher message.
That's why he wanted to come home.
Someone's trying to make contact with me
Each number represents a letter.
A is one. B is two. C is three.
You can hear him too, right?
Body asleep.
G-U-R.
T-H-E.
A shift value of 13.
It's a rot-13 algorithm.
"The Perrin pages will help
you find your calling,
"but don't be duped.
"Cut down the woods.
They be Erdos."
PERRIN PAGES NUMBERS
PERRIN NUMBER
Number sets.
WOODS ERDOS
Where? Where?
Where are you?
APPETIZERS
"Cut down the woods."
Remove all of the Perrin
and Erdos woods numbers.
THE ON-LINE ENCYCLOPEDIA
OF INTEGER SEQUENCES
It's a phone number.
But to who?
25th and 8th.
There will be a cab waiting.
We got Bitcoin here. Bitcoin for sale.
We can't lose him.
Bitcoin for sale.
Anybody have Con Ed bills?
Con Ed bills! Anybody have Con Ed bills?
With Ecoin's soaring popularity,
E Corp CEO Phillip Price
announced what he is calling
a revolutionary new loan program
backed by the emerging cryptocurrency.
Ecoin loans are being touted
as having increased benefits
over conventional...
U.S. dollar-backed loans,
all of which are designed to support
low- and middle-income borrowers.
What this means, as Mr.
Price has stressed,
is that this new loan program
will not only provide
the economy with a
much-needed jump-start
but, more importantly,
give economic relief...
To those most affected post-Five/Nine.
However, it does seem to fly in the face
of E Corp's... - Angela.
What happened to you?
I thought we were gonna meet.
I need you to forget about
that voice mail that I left you.
Are you in danger?
No.
Something is wrong. I can tell.
You are not telling me everything.
With a much-needed jump-start
but, more importantly,
give economic relief
to those most affected post-Five/Nine.
However, it does seem to fly in the face
of E Corp's economic policy...
Don't call me anymore.
Where did he go?
ONE WAY
Wait, I have to remember,
I'm not following him.
I am him.
What I should be asking is,
where am I going?
Elliot?
You Elliot?
How do you know my name?
No Elliot?
No, no, okay.
Wait.
Elliot, yes?
Yes.
Address?
What do you mean?
Address.
I don't know.
Chambers and Church.
We have to be careful now.
This is no longer a
question of what I'm seeing.
No, we know that's not reliable.
The real question is,
what am I not seeing?
You have to understand,
us two meeting right
now, it's dangerous.
Don't worry. We're safe.
Our partners have proven
to be very influential.
Do you see him?
Do you see someone sitting next to me?
Elliot, what are you doing?
- My apologies, sir.
- Did you hear that?
Hey!
- Do you see him?
- Elliot, stop it.
Did... did you hear that?
Hey!
You have to calm down!
Calm down, Elliot.
I need you to turn around and tell me
if you see someone sitting
next to me right now.
Just pull over, sir.
I'm terribly sorry. If
you could just pull over.
Do you see him? Hey!
- Shut up! No!
- Elliot!
I need you to turn around and tell me
if you see someone sitting next to me!
What was the meaning of that?
I know you've been
under a lot of stress,
but I've been under a lot of stress too.
Can you even begin to imagine
what it's been like for me?
We can't talk out here. We're exposed.
Let's go.
Go where?
Enough of these games. Now, let's go.
- We're close.
- Close to what?
Have you forgotten everything?
Dark Army told me that
stage two is ready.
When you see it, you'll be pleased.
It worked, Elliot.
It's up to us now.
Let me show you.
Louie, I think this is the beginning
of a beautiful friendship.