Unless you go to work
tomorrow, I'm gonna be forced
to do something very
bad to your mother.
Give me your phone.
I rigged Signal's API
to beam GPS coords so
we can share locations.
My whole life is ruined because of you.
All you deserve is pure and utter agony.
Olivia was Susan Jacobs' contact.
She's an addict.
If she gets caught
using, she loses her kid.
I'm not like most people.
I'm starting to pick up on that.
My mom got killed. Murdered, actually.
Olivia's access isn't good enough.
You know why we came back here, right?
So you could be king of New York.
And in order for our
kingdom to be built,
I need a brilliant architect.
- I'm trying to help him.
- You're trying to destroy me.
I'm done talking to you.
One of your patients hacked me.
- Krista.
- I don't feel safe around you.
She knows something I gotta know.
It's time we talked.
I'm gonna tell you a story.
A story of a true "Xmas" miracle.
This is the tale of a bully
and a little bitch.
I'm talking about a mean, nasty bully
and a scrawny-ass little bitch.
This bully would pick
on the little bitch
every day after school.
If little bitch had cash,
little bitch got robbed.
If little bitch bowed up,
little bitch got stomped.
Point I'm trying to make here is,
this bully owned that bitch
like a Lincoln Continental,
but something happened to change it all.
On this Xmas of our tale,
little bitch got lucky
with the gifts, see?
Something little bitch
loved more than anything...
before family, God, and country was...
baseball.
Loved the shit out of it.
Well,
on this Xmas morning
when he got out of his little bedroom
and looked under his little tree,
guess what he found.
An Easton Magnum aluminum baseball bat.
Little bitch grabbed that bat
and went right outside to play.
Didn't even take the bow
off, he was so excited.
And there he was on
the corner ball field,
hitting balls like he was Sammy Sosa
when...
his bully comes up,
eyeing that bat.
And just as the bully
made his way up to him,
without any warning...
bam!
Blood.
Fuckin' everywhere.
Blood on the ground,
blood on little bitch,
blood dripping down the bow
still wrapped around that bat.
Little bitch knocked every tooth out
of that motherfucker's head.
Cracked his skull open,
popped his eyeball out on home plate.
All because little bitch saw the truth.
That bat may have
been made to play ball,
but that wasn't its purpose.
Nuh-uh.
In that moment in little bitch's hands,
it was there to break
this nigga's head open.
See, Ms. Krista,
we all have a purpose in this world,
and it's our lot in life
to wait for the cosmos
to reveal what that is.
But you don't have to look no more...
'Cause for you, that day has come.
Want to know why?
I'm gonna break Elliot...
and you gonna be my aluminum bat.
I'm, uh... I'm on my
way to Olivia's now.
How are we gonna get to her boss?
We still need his login credentials
to transfer the money.
Don't worry about it. I have a plan.
Did the proxy hack at
Virtual Realty check out?
Yeah, we're good.
I'm seeing all the
unencrypted network traffic.
What about the venue for
this Deus Group shindig?
Do we know where it's going down?
Uh, Price sent me the location.
It should be in your inbox.
There's a hotel across the street
that we should work out of.
Are you there?
Darlene?
Yeah.
The other day, when...
I said that I should never
have let you back in my life...
I was an asshole.
I'm sorry.
You still have my Signal mod
running on your phone, right?
Yeah, why?
Just be careful, okay?
Keep your phone on you so
I can see where you are.
I don't want to lose you again.
Oh, thank you.
I... I got to go.
Elli.
Ah, long time no see, cuz.
Where do I know this place from?
Do you have it?
Of course I got it, bro.
Under the table.
Where you going?
I got to go.
Damn, you just gon' leave like that?
Thought we gonna catch up.
Sorry, man, I... I got shit to do.
Listen, just so you know,
I'm full-time freelance now.
Only loyalty is to the almighty paper.
So hang on to my number.
Should you need anything,
you know I'm your guy.
You be strange, now,
but don't be a stranger,
know what I mean?
Peace, Elli.
We don't have to do this.
We can find a way to talk to her.
And if she says no?
Then we reason with her.
And if she still says no?
We don't have time for taking risks.
This is the only way.
Hey. What you're about
to do is crossing a line.
Well, it's a little late
for that, don't you think?
He's right.
We used to have a code.
Lines we would not
cross, parameters we set.
Those seem to have been
seriously modified.
Question is, can we bring
those boundaries back?
Or is it like he said, too late?
Two large peppermint mochas.
What were you doing in
Pike's Hollow this morning?
How did you get in here?
Where's your brother?
Did you take him somewhere?
Is he still in the city?
Okay.
Fuck, Darlene, you
should have kept driving.
Who are you calling?
You can't call this in to the FBI.
If the Dark Army finds
out about that crime scene,
they're gonna send someone...
They already did.
Have a seat.
A guy who continually talks
to an invisible entity
that isn't there...
Has arguments with him.
The invisible entity
interrupts him sometimes.
- Clorox.
- Market.
- How may I help you?
- I have her.
Oh, well done.
And her brother?
No, and she's not giving him up.
Uh-huh.
Well, that's not great.
Keep her close. Let me
run it up the flagpole.
Call you back in a bit.
Return of a biblical prophet,
Jan Matthys is preaching
death and repentance
before the Second Coming,
and those who are not part
of the chosen people...
Hello, sweetheart.
Are going to be horribly killed.
I brought peppermint mochas.
They said it was Christmas in a cup.
Well, it is indeed Christmas.
Very sweet.
Do you want to come in?
Yeah.
Okay.
What I'm about to tell
you is gonna sound...
A little crazy.
What's up?
It's about your clients.
My clients?
At Cyprus National Bank.
I never told you where I work.
A bank that primarily does business
with the Deus Group.
Whoa.
What the fuck is this?
They're a criminal enterprise
that uses their power and
wealth to run the world
without anyone knowing it.
Okay, I don't know why you're...
Tiananmen Square,
civil war in the Congo,
both Iraq wars,
the paramilitary
massacre in El Salado...
The cyber bombings.
That's not even their top five.
Okay...
You're really starting to scare me.
Tell me what you're doing.
Why do you know where I work?
I hacked you.
Excuse me?
Why?
I need you to do something for me.
What... what is this?
I need you to make one
phone call to your boss.
I'm already on their proxy server.
I just need him to log in so
I can swipe his credentials.
I know this doesn't make
sense to you right now,
but trust me, Olivia...
they're using you.
They're using me?
They are, but I can stop them.
I can stop them once and for all.
All I need is one phone call from you.
Get out.
- Don't do this.
- Are you fucking kidding me?
This conversation's over.
Get the fuck out.
Now.
What happens if you fail a drug test?
What did you say?
I know about your custody battle.
If you test positive for Oxy...
What the fuck are you talking about?
I'm eight years clean.
No, you're not.
You drugged me?
I had to make sure you would listen.
You're gonna call your boss in Cyprus.
You're gonna get him to
log in to the bank website,
and that's it.
Then I'm gone.
If you don't do what I say...
you lose your son.
Why are you doing this?
I was running out of time.
This was the fastest
way to convince you.
This was taken one mile
from where the van
following Mr. Alderson
was found burned.
We have his sister,
but we're still searching for him.
The minute we find him,
I think...
You think what?
It's time, Minister Zhang.
He's too much of a liability.
Oh, you're being foolish.
If we kill him,
his shipping hack dies with him.
We have the Deus Group meeting tonight.
Think about what you're saying.
The entire membership will be there.
It's too risky.
I will not get this close
only to watch it slip away again.
I want you to locate Mr. Alderson
and bring him in.
He should see the full potential
of what we're working towards.
It's time he learns
we're on the same side.
- Placemat.
- Bandit.
How's everything over there?
- Fine.
- Good news and bad news.
The higher-ups want
Elliot, not his sister.
I don't suppose she's
mentioned where he is yet?
She wouldn't do that.
I heard her talking
to him earlier, though.
We can get his location off her phone.
Oh, interesting.
And you have her phone, I assume.
Yeah, I got it right
here, so we don't need her.
Fantastic.
Well, then, I'll be there with
my team to collect the phone.
And her?
Kill her.
What?
You said it yourself. We don't need her.
Cleaner this way.
You can handle that, right?
Mm-hmm.
Because I recall the last time
you didn't feel 100...
No.
I'm fine.
I'm just saying, if you don't feel 100%
like last time, you should
let me know right now
so I can set aside the time
to kill your mother
and your entire family.
No.
I can handle it.
Great. I'll be there at 3:30 on the dot.
Make sure it's done by then.
What?
What did they say?
Fuck! What the fuck?
Wait!
Wait! Fucking wait!
Get up!
What the fuck are you doing?
Keeping my family safe.
On your knees!
So this is it, then?
They tell you to kill me,
and you're just gonna do it?
Your phone gives them Elliot's location,
so they don't need you.
This is crazy. This isn't you, Dom!
You don't need to fucking do this!
I can't believe you have
the balls to say that.
You ruined my life.
I did. I'll own that, okay?
But that doesn't make you this!
You don't just fucking
shoot people in cold blood!
- I'm here because of you.
- I know.
- You did this to me!
- I know!
Okay, you were right.
Okay? I was wrong.
Give me a chance to make it right.
I can get you out of this.
- There's no way out.
- I have a plan.
You think I give a shit about your plan?
We are gonna take down the
Dark Army once and for all.
It's happening tonight.
It's too late.
Please, Dom, it's not too late.
No, it has to be like this.
There's not enough time. It's too late.
- Dom, listen to me!
- They coming at 3:30.
Listen to me. I know I fucked up, okay?
But it's not too late.
If you let me go, I can stop this, okay?
I swear to God, if you just let me go.
- Please!
- I'm sorry.
No, no, no, please!
Don't be sorry, Dom.
Don't be, don't be!
Don't be sorry, Dom, okay?
Please, Dom, don't be sorry.
You don't need to do this.
You are a good person!
- This isn't you!
- Shut up!
Shit, shit, shit.
Shit.
How soon can he get back to me?
It's urgent, yes.
I know, but it's
regarding Mr. Kuklachev.
He'll want to know.
Okay, great.
Merry Christmas.
How long do you think it'll be?
Fuck you.
My life is over. I
want you to know that.
You just have to talk to him.
Then I'll go.
Nothing will be traced to you.
And you think that's it, huh?
You just drugged an addict.
You'll get through it.
You arrogant piece of shit.
Maybe you can have a slip
and it's not the end of
the world, but I can't.
It destroys me.
So fuck you.
Maybe you should have thought about that
before you worked for them.
What's that supposed to mean?
Offshore bank in Cyprus.
Kind of money that goes through there.
You know, come on.
You're not dumb.
I'm sure a part of you has always known.
You chose to look the other way.
My choices are none of your business.
I get it.
You needed a job. They were paying well.
That's how they do it.
That's their business model.
They back everyone into a corner
until all that's left is for
us to compromise ourselves.
That's why what I'm
doing has to be done.
They're hurting you...
just like they're hurting all of us.
The only one hurting me right now is you.
I wonder how many
people you've had to hurt
to get what you want.
Hmm?
How many has it been, Elliot?
How many people have had to suffer
because of you?
Was it worth it?
I'm a mess.
Can I use the bathroom?
Yeah, go ahead.
So was fucking me part of the plan,
or was that just a happy accident?
It was an accident.
That's sweet.
It's almost done.
Once her boss calls back,
we'll get what we need and go.
This would have all been simpler
if she wasn't so deep in denial
about who she's working for.
There it is.
That sense of dread.
It only happens when you cross a line
you didn't even know existed.
Maybe that dread is a good thing.
After all, when you realize
you've crossed a line...
That means you still had one.
When those crossed lines
are all behind you,
up ahead is only darkness.
He has insomnia,
social anxiety.
I... I don't know what else to tell you.
Morphine addiction,
jail time, dead daddy.
You're giving me the knockoffs, girl.
I want the brand name.
Please let me go.
Whatever you're looking
for, I don't have it.
I know the two of you had
a special relationship.
"Special"?
He hacked me.
He threatened my last boyfriend.
He threatened me.
You know, I had to stop seeing him
because he scared me so much.
You weren't scared of him!
You loved his ass!
I saw the look on your face.
Don't lie to me.
This isn't going to work.
Your outbursts.
Just because you were bullied as a kid,
because people hurt you...
until that day you swung a bat
and learned how to hurt them back...
doesn't mean it's going to work with me.
W-wait a minute.
Wait a fucking second.
Miss Krista, are you...
are you calling me a little bitch?
Yo, Peanuts.
You hear that, what she called me?
She called you a little bitch.
Hey, Javi.
You hear her calling me a little bitch?
That's what I heard.
See?
That's why you're good.
Not even my bitch can
call me a little bitch.
Oh, my God!
- Who's that?
- Jason.
Jason, huh?
That your boy?
Maybe we should bring him in here.
Maybe that's what'll...
what'll get you going.
Hello, babe.
Are you in there?
How about that, Miss Krista?
We gon' have one big merry-merry.
I was able to stop the bleeding.
Gonna be okay.
I'm sorry.
I don't believe you.
You said the people I work for...
They were behind the
massacre in El Salado?
My mom died there.
I know.
Olivia...
I can stop them.
Hi.
Um, I'm sorry to
bother you on a holiday,
but Mr. Kuklachev
needs the authorization
to transfer funds.
You don't see the request?
Are you sure?
I still don't see it.
Okay, that's strange.
He said it was urgent.
Maybe he changed his mind.
I'll just...
I'll just check back with him
and... and get back to you.
Okay, thanks.
Merry Christmas to you too.
I'll wipe all the traces of you
and your boss's involvement.
Nothing will be linked back to you.
You know, I may work for monsters...
But you are one.
And you're the worst kind,
because you don't even know it.
Oh, damn.
Your boy's upset you didn't let him in.
Ah, all right.
Now...
before your boy came and went,
you were calling me a little bitch?
Chill, girl.
I didn't take no offense.
In fact, this was my bad,
'cause I didn't tell
you the whole story.
See,
I was just explaining your role to you.
That you my bat.
But that bat ain't the end of the story.
Nah.
That's where I come in.
So after being beaten
within an inch of his life
by that badass little bitch,
the bully woke up in the hospital.
It was right then when
little bitch walked in
like the fucking ghost of Xmas past.
Bully sees him and starts crying.
I mean, this nigga was scared.
He must have thought that boy
had come to finish him off.
But you know what happened?
Little bitch just walked right up
to his bully's bed...
And held his hand.
Yep.
He held his hand...
Just like so.
Real soft and gentle-like.
And then he got real close.
He looks at his bully,
all sniffling and crying.
He looked at him and said...
"I see you now."
Little bitch showed up
when no one else would.
He saw his bully
like no one else could...
and that was all it took.
And, Miss Krista,
from that moment on,
he owned that bully for life.
Now, if I want to own Elliot,
I don't just gotta break him.
Me and Elliot are linked
on a spiritual plane.
I got to come at him on the
same level I find myself,
and... and breaking him
only gets you so far.
I gotta break him so I can build him up.
I need to wound his soul
so I can be the one to heal him.
That is how you own a nigga.
Now, the next words out of your mouth
have to be exactly what I want.
Not for my sake,
but for yours and for your boy Jason,
who lives up on 1404 Jay Street.
Now, you know what I want.
You got to give it to me.
You do that,
I got no reason not to turn you loose.
Look me in my eye.
Trust me.
Go to the filing cabinet in my office.
There's a folder in the bottom drawer.
Go to the tab that
says "September 2015."
Look for Elliot's name.
What am I gonna find there?
Mr. Robot.
What's that?
That...
is how you'll break him.
Oh, my head hurts.
I thought you were gonna kill me.
They gave me an hour.
How long has it been?
Just unlock your phone.
All they want is Elliot's location.
- I can't.
- You can.
What would you do if it was your family?
I'm doing it.
You know that night we spent together?
I know you probably think of it
as the worst night of your life...
The night all this shit went to shit.
But when I think about it, it was...
Don't.
Nice.
The last time I remember
actually feeling good.
You were just using me.
You know it was more than that.
Look...
whatever you have to do, I get it.
Okay? But just... just
at least believe that.
I'm out of time.
Get up.
- Where are we going?
- Come on, get up.
- Up.
Come on, let's go.
You got the jump on me,
and before I knew what
was happening, it was over.
What are you talking about?
Take it and make it quick.
- You want me to shoot you?
- It's the only way.
Come on, we're running out of time.
You have to kill me.
I'm not fucking killing you, okay?
Let's go. We can make a run for it.
If they show up and we're gone,
my family's dead.
Don't you get it?
My life puts everyone I love in danger.
This won't stop until I'm dead.
I'm not gonna fucking kill you.
I'd do it myself if I could.
I've thought about it every
day for the past two months,
but I can't do it.
I can't do it.
Please, Darlene, just
pull the fucking trigger.
- I can't.
- Just pull the fucking trigger!
- Dom, please.
- Pull the fucking trigger!
- I can't.
- Do it!
Dominique?
Well, now, I was not expecting this.
I... I'm stunned.
I... I don't know what to say.
My goodness.
Oh. Oh, don't worry,
I'm not gonna kill you.
You are still far too
useful to us for that.
But this is going to be
so painful for you.
Now, where's the phone?
I want you to understand,
I mean you no ill will.
My instructions were
to find your brother.
Well, in that case,
my phone's not gonna do you any good.
I just wiped it.
Huh.
Shouldn't we be talking
about what just happened?
We got the access we needed
to transfer the money
from the bank's side.
Once we hack all of the
members' phones tonight
at their meeting, we can rob them blind.
That's not what I meant.
What you meant doesn't matter.
- Krista?
- Elliot, I need to see you.
I'm actually kind of
busy. Can I call you tomorrow?
I was kidnapped by someone you know.
Fernando Vera.
He wanted to know everything
about you, everything I knew.
I'm sorry, I didn't know what to do.
I didn't have a choice. He had a gun.
Once he got what he
wanted, he let me go.
I went to the police,
but now I'm too afraid to go back home.
- I'm scared.
- Wait, wait, slow down.
- Where are you right now?
- I'm-I don't know.
Downtown, I think.
I can meet you at
Washington Square Park.
- Can you get there?
- I think so.
- I'll see you soon.
- Okay.
There's no way he's
just gonna let her go.
I know.
Here we go again, off to play the hero.
But is that even who we are anymore?
You saw what we did back there.
We just watched him
destroy someone's life
and none of us did a thing about it.
Rules, morals, parameters...
they only break
if you're broken to begin with.
Did we change under pressure,
or did this only reveal
who we really are?
I don't know anymore.
- The one thing I do know is...
- Hey, hey!
Wait, wait, wait!
Help!
Hey!
Hey, hey!
Help!