_
Is this really it...
The moment this can all truly end,
reverse everything we've done,
finally bring Five/Nine to an end?
This is what democracy looks like!
I fought so hard to protect
the New York facility
that I couldn't see the bigger picture.
A reported 71 buildings
exploded or caught fire.
You have been appointed CTO at E Corp.
The CTO title is nothing more than that.
The position is worthless. You heard him.
We can use it.
I suppose there's some
banal excuse why a month
isn't enough time to get my
project shipped to the Congo!
Now I want you to
imagine your mom, Trudie.
Am I illustrating my point?
You work for the Dark Army now.
It was you who exported the keys.
You could make it like
Five/Nine never happened.
Whatever happens after this,
I want us to keep talking.
I want us to be a team.
My associates found your pet employee.
I am your father.
Angela Moss was allowed
to continue with her lawsuit,
which put my plant in jeopardy.
You're panicking right now.
The minute you remove emotion from this,
you'll do just fine.
You need to talk to Angela.
She is not doing well.
Last time I saw her,
she was going through
a full-on breakdown.
The cyber bombing, that was my fault.
She used me for that.
I have to believe that
there was a purpose.
Pettiness.
It was a dig at me.
It's that small, unfortunately.
No, it's not over.
It's not over. It can't be.
She was gonna bring my mom back.
We were gonna be reunited.
What are you gonna do to her?
What are you asking?
Retribution...
I want it.
I'm afraid your only move here:
accept that you've been conned.
Find a way to live with what you did.
No.
You're wrong about her project.
I know it's possible. I've seen it.
And I know how to take it from her.
Don't you get it?
With everything that we know,
this is what we have to do.
- Shut up.
- We can expose her.
We can tell everyone what she showed me.
Shut up!
Sh-shut up.
No, I won't.
And if you're not gonna help me,
I'm gonna do it on my own.
And there is nothing you
can do or say to stop me.
I wish you hadn't said that.
You have to understand.
I have been trying to
stop her from hurting you.
That's... that's why I brought you here.
But you ta... you talk like
this, and I cannot protect you.
You have to relent.
There's a chance, if...
if you... if you beg.
It's the only way out of
this, please, please, please.
Shh.
You're panicking right now.
Remove all emotion,
and you'll do just fine.
Isn't that what you're good at?
I'm not gonna run.
So you should probably leave.
She made her choice.
Choice?
That's not allowed when it comes to you.
No, no, you...
you did this to her.
You... you... you
recruited her and you k...
you killed...
And you let it happen, didn't you?
It wasn't without a valiant
attempt on your part, though,
trying to talk some sense into her.
It isn't your fault that
she wouldn't listen.
You didn't give me enough time. She...
She could have... she
could... she could...
she could have come around.
I meant everything I said to her.
You are psychotic.
You're certainly not mincing
words today, are you?
It's all psychotic.
Phillip, if you feel you
must take this out on me,
then I am happy to bear the burden.
I've become very good
at it over the years,
don't you think?
She was my daughter.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Our team has an update
on the shipment hack
we obtained from Mr. Alderson.
It appears it will grant us
the clearance we need
by the end of the year.
It's October now,
so that's two more
months we'll have to wait.
Just in time for the holidays.
What is it?
Mr. Alderson is a good-for-nothing wretch
that is not to be trusted.
Oh, Wang Shu, you needn't worry.
Once our project ships,
he'll have served his purpose
and then he can be terminated.
In the meantime, he needs
to be kept on a short leash
and trained not to bite his master.
Very well, then.
Send him a reminder of what's at stake,
should there be any interference.
I hope you enjoy your last Christmas,
my dear Elliot.
And then she says to me,
"I don't think that's the North Pole."
Freddy, got a package for you.
And I got a package for you.
That's not funny.
Can we at least get
the Secret Santa going?
It's already 8:00.
Fred?
Come on, we gotta start wrapping it up.
My babysitter keeps texting me.
Just a sec.
Oh, that's great.
Can you say it again?
What?
Can you tell me you like me?
I like you.
Tell me you love me.
Uh, I love you.
Okay.
Maybe, uh, stand up, turn
around, and say it again.
You want me to stand up?
Yeah.
How ya doin', Freddy?
Not too good? That's okay. I get it.
Jerking off to underage girls
on live video chats is one thing.
When it's played back,
though, kinda loses its magic.
- Who is this?
- Check your email.
You should have received
a message from me.
Need you to open the email
and click on the link.
You the one that sent me the package?
Listen, please don't do this.
Look, I-I can pay.
Open the email and click
on the link, Freddy.
Okay, look, if... if this
is some sort of a ransomware thing
or you're trying to get
money out of me, listen...
You obviously don't know
me, because if you did,
you'd already know I don't
give a shit about money.
Do what I'm telling you,
or I'm sending the video to the FBI.
Oh, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait.
No.
Fred, I gotta go.
I'm just wrapping up in here.
Then you have to ask Trish
to do the Secret Santa,
because I need to get home.
Okay, okay, fine. Okay, good, yeah.
Freddy, I need you to pay attention.
What are you doing in there?
Are you on the phone?
Merry Christmas, and
I'll... I'll see you in 2016!
Open the email and click on the link.
You know, this isn't
gonna get past our IT guys.
That's what I'm counting on.
Okay, I just clicked it.
Are we done?
Get the USB from the envelope.
I left instructions on
how to archive your inbox.
Copy the .pst file to the thumb drive.
Inbox?
I'm an attorney, pal.
That inbox is full of
sensitive client information.
You hear me?
Hello?
I was just taking a moment
to think about whether
or not I give a fuck.
I don't.
♪ Oh, jingle bells, jingle bells ♪
- ♪ Jingle all the way ♪
- All right, so...
what are you gonna do with
my emails once you do get 'em?
Once you're finished,
leave all your personal
effects in your office:
your phone, your Fitbit, your smartwatch,
anything with an on-off switch,
then bring the USB
drive to Grand Central.
You know, this isn't
just gonna destroy me.
It's gonna destroy the
people that work for me,
my firm, their families, everyone.
Keep this phone on you.
Expect another call when you get there.
Who the fuck is this?
This is Mr. Robot.
I'll load it up for ya.
Taxi!
42nd and Lex, Grand Central.
Increase by 20%
- this holiday season.
- Can you believe that?
Not long ago, we were talking
about an economic collapse
on par with the Great Depression.
Especially hard to believe
given the November jobs report
that was released on Friday.
Over 400,000 jobs were added.
This really shows the
resilience of E Corp
and their CEO, Tyrell Wellick.
If it weren't for their data recovery
and their Ecoin loan program,
we wouldn't be enjoying the turnaround
we're experiencing right now.
A quote from the chair
of the Federal Reserve
seems to echo public opinion:
"Sometimes the good guys
really do come out on top."
All right.
Hey.
Walk to the furthest kiosk.
Get in line.
Okay.
I'm, uh... I'm here.
I'm in line.
Don't get freaked out.
You're being tailed.
What? Why?
They want to know who you're meeting.
I'll take care of them.
- Right now...
- Okay.
I need you to stop looking around
like you're a coked-up Henry Hill.
Well, I-I-I actually did some.
- What?
- Yeah, some blow, you know.
Uh, some of the girls
had some at the party,
and I... you know, the Christmas party.
- A little or a lot?
- What?
How much did you do, a little or a lot?
Shit, man, I don't know.
Right now, it seems
like a fucking lot, okay?
Take a breath, Freddy.
We're gonna get through this.
Wait a second. Where are you, anyway?
As far as you're
concerned, I'm everywhere.
What does that even mean?
It means I own the entire station.
Buy a ticket home.
No, don't want these
guys to know where I live.
Trust me, Freddy, they already know.
All right, uh, I'd like a...
first train to Brewster, please.
Okay, I got it.
All right, now you're
gonna head to the train,
but we're gonna take the long way.
Want you to walk past the clock
and go towards the Hudson News.
Take out all your cash.
Give it to the guy in the Santa hat.
Why?
We gotta buy time.
Fold it into a ball,
make a fist, toss it in the case.
Don't stop. Keep going.
Make a right and head to the tracks.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey, that's my money.
Track 19, last car on the right.
So you have been
following me, haven't you?
No, I've been waiting...
For you on the train.
Who the fuck are you?
Thought I answered that already.
Don't think you need the phone anymore.
Sit down and give me the drive.
Yeah, first you're gonna give me
all the copies of that video you have.
You gonna shoot me in
front of all these people?
Put the gun away, Freddy, and sit down.
I'm serious.
I'm not afraid to use this if I have to.
And then that video will not
only be automatically sent
to the FBI but to your wife and kids.
Is that something you're afraid of?
Sit down. Give me the drive.
So we're square, right?
You gonna erase that video?
I mean, it goes without saying.
I can't have anyone seeing that.
Look, I'll tell you what:
you keep that drive.
That'll show you how
much I trust you, huh?
You understand me, man?
I'm trusting that your word is good?
I'm gonna head on back to the office.
Sit down.
We're not done.
Do you know who those guys were,
the ones who were following me?
Dark Army.
Jesus Christ.
What the fuck were those
guys doing following me?
They want to know who
you're giving these files to.
Why?
Because they're protecting
one of your clients.
What client?
Whiterose.
What the fuck are you
talking about, man?
Who's that?
You know her as Zhi Zhang,
the Chinese minister of state security.
He and his partners have been using
shell corporations to move money around,
and your name keeps popping up
on all their company filings.
Oh, shit.
That's what this is about?
I'm a dead man.
I need to know how you've
been helping them funnel money.
Oh, no, no, no, no, you don't
want to fuck with these guys.
If half the shit that I've seen is real,
then these guys are the
official fucking bogeymen.
And I'm not talking conspiracy
bullshit either, man.
I mean, these guys are pure evil.
I'm kind of ahead of you on that point.
Cyprus National Bank.
That's it.
That's their bank.
Tell me what you know about it.
I don't know shit, man, okay?
The reason they even hire peons like me
is 'cause I'm willing
to look the other way
and push the right papers for 'em,
small stuff, incorporation documents.
Look at me. I'm a dumb shit.
You think they're
gonna tell me anything?
I may have... a contact in the city.
Who?
Stop fucking around, man.
We don't have a lot of time.
Give me the name.
John Garcin.
Where can I find him?
Well, I don't have the address on me.
I-I gotta go back to my office.
I told you to leave
all your electronics.
I did.
I don't... I don't have anything on me.
Look, I have nothing.
Go straight to the 42nd Street exit
and wait for my call.
Don't stop. Don't turn around.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, you're leaving me?
If they see us together,
we're both dead.
Go.
Meet me at the corner
of 42nd and Vanderbilt.
Okay.
Then what?
Still need Garcin's address.
Oh, no, you gotta be fucking crazy.
I'm not going back to my office.
Those guys are gonna be
looking for me there.
Let me worry about that.
Listen, I want your word that
if I give you what you want,
you're gonna destroy that video.
You are in no position
to negotiate right now.
Just fucking move.
Then I want your word!
If we don't get out of here,
I'm not gonna be the one
you need to worry about, you understand?
I am your only way out of this.
And just how the fuck
are you gonna protect me
against the Dark Army, huh?
Those guys just saw me
running away from them.
They know that I'm up to something.
Oh, you can't...
protect me,
can you?
Freddy?
Jesus Christ.
You don't give a shit
what happens to me.
Freddy, we don't have time for this.
You need to snap out of it.
They are still coming for you, man.
You need to make it to this
fucking corner right now.
Right now, Freddy.
Freddy, you need to keep moving.
Hello?
Just don't send that video to my kids.
Freddy!
Freddy?
Excuse me. Excuse me.
We need room here. We need room.
Hey, listen...
Taking pictures right now, lady?
What are you gonna
do with them? Come on.
Put it down. Back up.
Jesus Christ.
Today's gonna be another busy one
because of the cyber
bombings memorial brunch.
The board of directors
would like you to do
some PR interviews today
before you head upstairs.
Our media consultant
is going to debrief you
with some talking points
back in the greenroom
before we put you into hair and makeup.
You have about five
minutes before your meeting
with Mr. Milligan and his team.
Thank you, Elizabeth.
Oh, that's not all.
After that, you have a
meeting with the board.
It's more of a meet and greet,
then straight into a meeting
with the Ecoin engineering
team to discuss the new rollout.
And tonight the board would like...
Can we just...
push any of this until tomorrow?
No, I'm afraid tomorrow's
already full as well.
Can you just give me a minute?
Certainly, sir.
Congratulations.
I've been meaning to tell
you that for a while now,
but I wanted to give you your space.
Most of us here consider
you a hero for what you did.
Mom?
Dom? You up yet, hon?
I'm heading out to go
mall walking with Janice,
you know, that lovely girl I
met at church a few weeks ago?
I want you to meet her.
I think you two would really hit it off.
Seriously, Dom?
It's almost noon.
You're still in your PJs.
What gives?
You all right?
What's he doing here?
I told you last week I was
renovating the master bathroom.
What's the big deal?
What's the matter with you?
I thought we agreed I would
vet everyone you hired.
Oh.
Hon, I thought you were
kidding like you do.
Listen, I'm glad you're up.
I want you to put a load in
so you have something to
wear to the bake sale later.
Janice is coming over after
for some macaroni and gravy.
You're just gonna leave
this guy here alone?
He's not alone. You're here.
This John Garcin practically posts
every shit he takes.
It's gonna take forever
to go through his social media.
I know we have our issues,
but it's these people
that are the real psychos.
I mean, how proud of
your life can you be?
We have his address.
We should just go.
We'll get the info we need there.
It's too early for that.
We don't know enough.
He's their liaison at
Cyprus National Bank.
He's gotta have something.
Be that as it may, we can't just knock
on this guy's door and pretty
please ask him for his access,
so we put our heads
down, do the research,
find a way to break him, same as always.
Took us two weeks with Freddy.
We can't wait that long anymore.
We're running out of time.
By next week, Whiterose
will ship her project.
We'll be dead.
I'm not gonna argue that with you.
Freddy could have saved us a lot of time
if his brains weren't splattered
all over 42nd Street right now.
He had it coming.
They all do.
Don't do this for the wrong reasons.
You're angry, and I get it.
But your anger is
keeping you from seeing
the bigger picture of
why we started this thing.
You told me once
you don't take down a conglomerate
by shooting them in the heart,
'cause they don't have hearts.
You were wrong.
We found their heart.
We rob it...
she finally goes down.
What am I not seeing?
This used to be about saving the world.
You're making it too personal.
You're making this about
what they did to Angela.
You're letting your
feelings cloud your judgment.
My feelings?
See what's going on out there?
People are already
forgetting about Five/Nine,
the cyber bombings.
They're buying their Ecoin
discounted stocking stuffers
and Christmas hams, and
they're gonna forget.
And I don't blame them.
They're exhausted.
I'm exhausted.
But we let this go,
it'll be back to business as usual
for Whiterose and her friends.
The more she gets away with
this, the worse this gets.
So fuck my feelings.
I'm done with the therapy sessions.
This is all I'm focused on.
It's Darlene.
She says it's about Angela.
Oh, my God, thanks for calling me back.
Um, I think I figured it out.
Okay, I am... I am
really onto something.
Just wait until you hear this.
It's kind of a breakthrough.
Where's Flipper?
Uh, the landlord took her for the week.
Why? What are you too busy with?
What's going on, Darlene?
What are you doing here?
I think I saw Angela.
We talked about this already.
Angela's gone.
Are you on something right now?
Don't make this about that, okay?
Just listen to me.
Okay, I need you to hear this.
I'm listening.
Okay, um, I was... I was walking by
one of those shelters,
and I think I saw her.
Okay, I-I-I-I tried to catch up with her,
but it was... it was
crowded and I lost her,
but... okay, but this is proof, right?
This is proof.
Maybe this is why they
never found her body.
Maybe she's still alive.
That's not possible.
No, I am telling you I saw her.
She was on the street, same
red cart, same bathrobe,
exactly the way we saw her
in that security footage
before she got into that van.
- Darlene.
- Maybe she escaped.
I swear I saw her.
Maybe if you would just help me,
we could find her together;
we just need to canvass
- all of the homeless shelters.
- This has to stop.
Elliot, we can't give up on her, okay?
We can't.
You did a little too much coke
and you saw something that wasn't there.
I will show you where I saw her.
Just come with me.
Look at you, man. You are
so fucked up right now.
Fuck you.
This is exactly what you do
when shit like this happens.
You shut down.
Angela's dead.
Do you understand?
She's fucking dead.
And it's not our fault.
We tried to help her, remember?
She did this to herself.
You have to stop feeling guilty.
I'm not the one that feels guilty.
Why didn't you just show her
the photo Whiterose sent to us?
You mean the one with
Angela's brains blown out.
Yeah, no, I don't think so.
At least it would have
put her out of her misery.
It'd break her heart.
We need to get back to work.
John Garcin should be our only focus.
I know we don't usually do this,
but I have to fill you in if he won't.
That's why you're back, isn't it, to help?
You gotta be noticing it, then, too,
that he's not talking to you.
He doesn't talk to me that much either,
not since Angela died.
Darlene's right.
He's shutting down,
compartmentalizing the pain,
living in the distraction,
just like the holidays:
the fake Santas, the plastic trees,
the annoying Christmas carols...
♪ O come, all ye faithful ♪
One big song-and-dance production
to sell ourselves the theater
that everything's jolly,
at least for a moment.
But when it's all over,
Santa's gone back to his shitty day job.
The trees get disassembled
and thrown in a closet.
The music's faded away.
What then?
That's why you can't go anywhere.
I know he's keeping you
away, but I'll let you in.
Don't think I'm doing
it for you, though.
Let's be clear.
I still don't give a shit about you,
but he does.
This does not feel right to me.
E Corp owns the building.
They own half of Manhattan.
We stick to the plan.
And right now, Elliot needs
you more than he lets on,
because when that cold, brutal
reality closes in on us,
we're gonna need a friend,
and that's still what you are, right?
Um, a delivery
for John Garcin in apartment 7C.
Seventh floor to the
right of the elevator.
Thank you.
This goes sideways,
We don't have enough
information to break this guy.
We're just gonna own his Wi-Fi.
That'll grab us whatever
we need without him knowing.
Is it just me, or is this
the quietest building
in all of Manhattan?
Hello!
Anybody home?
Let's check things out
before he comes back.
That wasn't the plan.
We're only supposed to own his Wi-Fi.
Are you kidding?
He's not here. We just got lucky.
Search everything.
Something's not right.
No shit.
Ah, fuck.
Did you lock the door?
No.
Signal's dead in here.
They're jamming it.
Shit.
Phone's dead.
- It's almost as if...
- There is no John Garcin.
Freddy set us up.
It must have been a distress
signal they gave Freddy.
Place is a honeypot.
♪ Here's a little song I wrote ♪
♪ You might want to
sing it note for note ♪
♪ Don't worry ♪
♪ Be happy ♪
♪ In every life, we have some trouble ♪
♪ But when you worry,
you make it double ♪
♪ Don't worry ♪
♪ Be happy ♪
♪ Don't worry, be happy, now ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
No!
Let me go!
Stop! Let me go!
Wait! Wait!
♪ Don't worry, be happy, now ♪
So Father DiMarco spills his
potato salad all over her,
which I actually think he did on purpose
because Sister Merkin has,
you know, those big tatas
underneath all that black and white.
Ma, come on.
Oh, get over it.
She's a hottie.
I've seen you check
her out once or twice.
Janice, right, are you with me?
Sister Merkin is a ten, am I right?
Uh, s-she's quite attractive, yes.
See, Janice agrees.
Oh...
Look at the time.
I gotta get to bed.
I'm seeing Dr. Passante in the morning
for that thing on my neck.
Dom, hon?
Why don't you help Janice
carry out the leftovers?
It's just some macaroni.
Dominique, don't embarrass me.
Go on and help.
Oh.
Uh, my apologies.
I forget how frightened
people can be of them the first time.
I'm a taxidermist.
Uh, I wasn't frightened,
just a little unexpected is all.
Taxidermy, huh?
Guess you were into
stuffed animals as a kid?
Not particularly, no.
Well, um, it was nice
meeting you, Janice.
And, uh, I'm sorry about all this.
All what?
I think my mom was
trying to, you know...
set us up.
Oh, my, I had no...
Oh!
I...
Oh, this is... this is terribly awkward.
Uh, I-I-I-I think she might
have gotten the wrong idea.
It's all good. I'm on a
self-imposed time-out anyway.
Okay.
My ma, she's just trying to cheer me up.
She thought this would help.
Yeah, she said you'd been through
kind of a rough patch.
Bet she did.
Um...
It's not a big deal.
It's just a promotion at work
has been a lot of stress is all.
Yeah, she said you
haven't been sleeping,
and she told me about the drinking, mm.
Oh, I hope I'm not
speaking out of school.
I-I-I just meant to say I've been there
with work, you know.
Long hours can really burn you out,
especially in my field.
But I'm here to talk, if you want.
Sometimes that can help.
Yeah. Anyway, I should get to bed.
Good night, Janice.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
You need your rest.
After all, you have that interview
about the Santiago case in the morning.
Excuse me?
You've put it off for weeks.
It's starting to look suspicious.
What did you say?
I was just explaining that
unless you go to work tomorrow
and finish cleaning up Santiago's mess,
then I'm gonna be forced
to do something very bad to your mother,
like, really bad, you know?
Like, I'm probably gonna have
to slit her from mouth to cunt.
You touch my mom,
I will strangle you to death.
You understand me?
Oh, you can strangle me
till the cows come home.
That's not gonna stop the rest of 'em.
Now, you get that rest we talked about.
You got a big day tomorrow.
Oh, and would you thank your
mom for me for the macaroni?
Real life, yo.
I'm just saying, the
skullduggery of scientists
led us to this point in
believing this bullshit.
What bullshit, exactly?
That the Earth is a sphere
when it so clearly is flat.
See, you ain't even
willing to question it.
That's how they get
you. If the Earth's flat,
then how come no one's
ever fallen off the side?
Easy answer: Antarctica.
Whoever lives here has
to be fucking mental.
Dar.
What's up?
I just got here.
Please tell me you
have something stronger.
Hmm, stronger than what?
Anything I've already taken.
That's what's up. I got you.
Shit, girl, you didn't even
let me tell you what it was.
Why the fuck is someone
in Angela's bedroom?
Who's Angela?
Oh, Prada, YSL, Chloé,
ballet shoes,
and a bunch of fish food
with no fucking fish.
Smells like some "American Psycho" shit's
going on here.
Get the fuck out of here, you
fucking Mary Poppins whore!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
The fuck did you give me?
Babe, you need to chill.
- Fuck you.
- What?
Get out.
Get the fuck out right now!
Everybody, out!
Out! Get the fuck out!
Go!
Get the fuck out!
Is she listening?
Of course she is. She always is.
Was that her in the SUV outside?
You tell her if she
goes through with this,
my shipping hack goes public.
She won't be able to move shit.
Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait. Hold on a second.
Listen to me.
The people you work
for, they're terrorists.
They don't care about you or any of us.
I know you don't want to do this.
You're just getting paid to.
Please, I can't leave like this.
I've hurt so many people.
I have to make this right.
Wait. Wait.
No.
You tell her if I die,
this won't be over.
I know all about Cyprus National Bank.
Her money's as good as gone.
Even if I die...
She's gonna pay for what she's done.
Do you hear me?
You tell that piece of shit
that my anger won't die with me
and she can't hide from
what's coming for her!
You hear me?
Do you hear me?
Say something.
Good-bye, friend.
He got too reckless.
Your job was to control him.
My job was to protect him.
Your job was to protect all of us.
What's gonna happen?
The inevitable.
We're all gonna go away.
I just didn't think it
was gonna be like this.
Hmm.
Welcome back, Mr. Alderson.