You're nothing.
You're worthless.
Mom, a lot's happened
since last I saw your.
I'm not gonna run. You
should probably leave.
This is exactly what you do
when shit like this happens.
You shut down.
- Who are you?
- Just a brave traveler
who's finally come home.
Susan Jacobs, the General
Counsel at E Corp.
When they cleared E Corp, you laughed.
There's security
camera footage of him
kidnapping Miss Alderson.
Unless you finish cleaning
up Santiago's mess,
I'm gonna be forced to
do something very bad
to your mother.
We found their heart.
We rob it, she finally goes down.
I know all about Cyprus National Bank.
Her money's as good
as gone. You hear me?
Was that her in the SUV outside?
Welcome back, Mr. Alderson.
A symbolic breach in the structure
that separated millions and
claimed hundreds of lives.
That was 1989.
The world was up for grabs.
All the money, power,
natural resources,
hell, even borders were negotiable.
The Soviet Union, a
great world super power,
was collapsing.
And where some saw freedom,
a young, imaginative Minister Zhang
saw possibility.
A new world order.
So Zhang formed an
investment group called Deus.
The goal, bring together
the world's wealthiest,
most powerful men to consolidate control
and manipulate global events for profit.
Zhang courted dignitaries, world leaders,
oligarchs, businessmen,
and he was a damn good salesman.
The potential profit outweighed
anyone's moral reservations,
which was proven true
in an early endeavor;
the First Gulf War.
Something is happening outside.
The skies over Baghdad
have been illuminated.
A few backroom deals, a promise here,
a bribe there.
Like that, the Deus
Group was rich on oil
and had a foothold in the
military industrial sector.
With the right players in place,
running the world turned
out to be surprisingly easy.
I have to say, business was booming.
With his network of hackers
and terrorists in place,
Zhang suggested the Deus
Group look in a new direction.
Industrial espionage
was yesterday's work.
What better way to gain
leverage on everyone
than if everyone was connected?
During my service in the Congress,
I took the initiative
in creating the Internet.
The United States was a test case.
Americans seemed the most
ready to give their lives
over to a box.
Without hesitation
everyone jumped online.
Welcome. You've got mail.
Offered everything they had.
Bank accounts, electric bills,
medical records, DNA data,
baby pictures.
We staged the biggest
coup in human civilization
and the whole world
volunteered to take part.
Opted in, checked the box,
and clicked, "I agree."
With the Deus Group behind it,
E Corp became the world's biggest front.
With every new device we rolled out,
there was a new way for the Deus Group
to manipulate the public.
But as the world
embraced the digital age,
we began to see that Zhang
had been perfectly positioning himself
to take total control.
Zhang's billion dollar machine,
he clandestinely built it
under the Washington
Township Nuclear Power Plant.
The Deus Group now understood
we were working for Zhang,
not with him.
His pet project which
we'd belittled for years
had been the singular purpose
of the Deus Group all along.
_
Consider yourself lucky, Mr. Alderson...
That I was the one alerted when
you walked into that apartment.
It's my duty to dispose
of any intruder
and report the attempt.
But you didn't.
Why?
Crazy, right?
Yeah, I never thought we'd
still be here, either.
Thought we were goners.
But here we are still alive.
But that's not the crazy part.
The crazy part is we
were saved by him,
the enemy.
One we've been after this whole time.
Question is, what's the angle?
What's the cost?
Because one thing we know by now,
it ain't free.
It won't work...
Your heist.
But you just said the Deus
Group funds whiterose's project
and the Dark Army.
If I can find a way
to rob the Deus Group,
whiterose loses everything.
But like I said,
the Deus Group is impenetrable.
Whiterose designed it that way.
You can get us in.
Excuse me?
It's like you said.
E Corp is a front for the Deus Group.
Last I checked, you're still the CEO.
We can take them all
down if we work together.
You have to have a contact at the bank
that can get me the Deus
Group account numbers.
A real contact.
Susan Jacobs.
General Counsel at E Corp.
She was my designated associate
for Cyprus National Bank.
She handled everything.
Withdrawals, deposits,
transfers.
I would just receive a text
to authorize the transaction, but she...
Can get around two-factor authentication.
I just need their phone numbers.
Of course.
You think the Crown
Prince of Saudi Arabia
has the same cell phone
number for more than five days?
Or the chairman of Royal Dutch Shell?
Let me worry about that.
Just tell me how I can get a
hold of this contact of yours.
Well, that's where you'll
run into some difficulty.
Susan Jacobs disappeared months ago.
And given how open whiterose
is about my inevitable exit
from the group,
I haven't received another contact.
I'm sorry, Mr. Alderson,
but I really can't help you.
You know what they've done.
You just gonna let them keep doing it?
You're trying to stop a speeding train
by standing in front of it.
All thi... all this,
this is just a blip.
They won't even notice.
Whiterose killed your daughter.
You think I didn't look into you, too?
I don't know how you
justify the shit you do.
Maybe you wanna look back at
what whiterose did to Angela
and see it as a necessary evil.
A cost of doing business.
Or maybe you don't
look back at it at all
because deep down you
know what happened...
what's been happening...
is wrong.
Something inside you is telling you
to stop looking the other way.
That can start here.
Even if I were to agree to help you,
it's like I said.
This heist...
It's not possible.
I'll find Susan Jacobs.
Just get them all in a room together.
You want me to randomly request
that the entire Deus
Group gather in one place
- without even a pretext?
- In the next eight days.
Eight days? Is that all?
That's all I got.
Once whiterose starts shipping
their project, I'm dead.
And how do you expect
me to pull this off?
You've done whiterose's bidding thus far
and paid a horrible cost.
That loyalty won't be lost on her.
You can use that.
And if it's your life
you're worried about...
Doing nothing,
not fighting back...
You may as well be dead.
I became a dead man walking...
The minute I agreed
to work with whiterose.
Just like you.
What are we supposed to do now?
He isn't out.
He just walked out that door.
I'd be dead on the floor of my apartment
if he didn't want in.
He'll be back.
Besides, he just gave us
the name of his bank contact.
A contact that's been
missing for months.
So we find out why she disappeared.
We take anything she left behind.
- Yeah?
- It's Mom.
She's gone, Elliot.
Your mom was the nicest,
most thoughtful woman.
When my dad died,
she gave me a shoulder to cry on.
Always had a kind word for everyone.
You two must feel so blessed
to have had her in your life.
Yeah, we feel totally blessed.
What are we supposed to do?
Um, well, when my dad died,
- I turned towards the Lord.
- I mean with the boxes.
Oh, well, oftentimes,
like, families find sentimental value
in their loved ones possessions.
Donate everything.
Staff are not allowed to pack up
a deceased patient's belongings.
You can put a Post-It note on the boxes
with the items you wish to donate.
About yesterday...
I know I was a little mental.
We're cool.
- Are you just saying that or...
- No, we're good.
Let's just get this done.
Score.
Are you gonna help?
What's the hurry?
She's not gonna get any deader.
You know, for someone who
refused to enter this room
in the last few years,
you seem pretty comfortable
now with her gone.
Don't you feel a little relieved?
I know I sound like a total dick,
but you feel it, too, right?
I guess.
You know what? Fuck it.
Why should I feel like
a dick for being happy?
She was an asshole to us.
Now I don't ever have
to think about her again.
Rad. Your old Walkman.
Why is it even here? Mom hated music.
It doesn't matter.
Hold up.
I'll take it if you don't.
Cassettes are full-on back.
What?
Mom had a safe deposit box?
And how long did you
work under ASAC Santiago?
Three years, since I
started the New York office.
Describe his disposition
as a senior agent for me.
How'd he treat his squad? Any quirks?
- Oddities?
- No.
Santiago was always even-keeled.
He treated everyone
fairly, with respect,
both in the office and out in the field.
Did you ever see Agent
Santiago do anything
suspicious or out of character
before his disappearance
on October 23rd?
What do you mean by suspicious?
It's not every day
an ASAC ups and erases
security cam footage from
the FBI's parking garage
before dropping off
the face of the Earth.
Oh, right.
You okay there, Agent DiPierro?
I'm sorry, just, you
seem a little out of it.
You getting enough rest?
Can I...
just have some water?
Sir, there's something I
know I should tell you, but...
But what?
We're both here for the same reason.
To find Agent Santiago,
make sure he's safe.
Now, if there's anything you
can do to help us do that...
I think Agent Santiago
was a double agent.
A double agent?
Yes.
To be clear, Agent DiPierro,
you're accusing your
former commanding officer...
your FBI mentor... of
working as an operative
against the Bureau?
I'm sorry, Agent Horton.
I'm just having a little
trouble saying this aloud
knowing it's on the record and...
I'm worried.
I'm worried about what might happen,
about the repercussions.
What repercussions?
Santiago was working with
some awfully dangerous people.
No agent wants to see their brother,
their sister on the
wrong side of the law.
I get that.
But you know it's our duty to uphold
the integrity of the Bureau.
Well, take a breath.
Whenever you're set.
Can you tell me who Agent
Santiago was working with?
The Trujillo drug cartel.
You know, sort of the official punishment
of people who break the law,
and back then in that
place, in that time,
what the state did to
people as part of, you know,
lawful justice is worse than
anything Charles Manson did
to the people that he
had killed in his name.
What Charles Manson's
followers did to the
Manson murder victims
is merciful by the standards
of the lawful justice...
- Dugout.
- Bonsai.
Dominique, nice to hear your voice.
- How was the interview?
- Fine.
We're good.
Listen, instead of
Charles Manson doing...
Clarify for me what you mean by good.
Um, I fed them the cover story.
He bought it and praised
me for coming forward.
That's encouraging.
So, you believe it was
a successful meeting?
Your colleagues believe
all is aboveboard?
I mean, I was a little
nervous at the start,
but then I was fine.
Totally fine.
Agent Horton bought it. I'm sure of it.
Clarify sure.
And thought that when you
commit the kind of crimes...
Um, I mean, I don't know.
As sure as I can be,
I guess. 99.9% sure.
Interesting.
Well, it is just a red letter day.
Now, I know the beginnings
are always the hardest
but it's best for
everyone if you stay calm
and keep a level head.
Just one moment.
I'm just finishing a phone call.
Dominique, I want you to
know that we are very pleased
that you are back to
work and on the mend.
Don't be a stranger.
Let us know if there's anything you need,
and we'll do the same.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
You know, holidays.
Busy, busy, busy.
What can I do for you?
I want Beatrice with me forever.
If you are adulterous or
involved in fornication...
which basically means sex
outside of marriage...
you get your head cut off.
There's the cost of living
and the cost of dying.
Seems you're paying the price
whether you're coming or going.
This is taking way too long.
Susan Jacobs?
No, death.
We have to get back to work.
Still running the password cracker
on the Ecoin wallet but nothing yet.
And then there's the real price.
Not cash or Ecoin.
The emotional toll.
How are you doing with all this?
As soon as we get the
death certificate, I'm done.
The toll Elliot isn't willing to pay,
whether he's not ready to
or just doesn't want to.
I'm not talking about paperwork, kiddo.
I'm talking about the fact
that your mom died this morning.
Maybe you should take a minute,
deal with what's happening.
The fuck are you talking about?
I'm kind of an expert at observing you.
All I'm saying is that you need to stop
and take in your mom's death
or it's gonna eat away at you
like everything else you're holding in.
Here's the only thing I'm holding in.
We need to take down whiterose
or we die.
Darlene dies.
Did your expert observation
also pick up on that?
I agree. That could
have gone better.
Fuck you.
Okay, I mean,
how the hell should I know
what she would have wanted?
♪ But now it's cold and
Christmas is coming ♪
♪ La, la, la, la... ♪
Don't look at me like that.
Yeah, she was my mom,
but we weren't close.
There was no, "These are my
last wishes," conversation.
I mean, fuck.
I can't even remember
the last time we spoke.
So give me a goddamn
break here, all right?
Cremation, cardboard
coffin, cheapest urn.
You're not even a little
curious about what's in it?
I mean, she went through
the process of opening
a safe deposit box.
That is not the woman we grew up with.
So, I mean, there's gotta
be something important
in there, right?
Hello?
Bueller? Are you alive?
No, Darlene, I don't
think there's anything
important in there.
Well, you don't know that for sure.
I mean, maybe there's some secrets.
Secrets?
I don't know, like the secret
to why Mom was such a bitch.
Money.
The deed to a chateau in France.
Adoption papers.
Your adoption papers.
Yo, asshole!
Please stop ignoring me!
What the fuck is with you, man?
I'm here, aren't I?
No, you're not.
I thought you said we were cool.
We are cool.
Okay, then prove it.
Come with me to the bank.
What is the point?
It's not gonna change
the fact that mom's dead.
Just fucking come with me!
I need to go, okay?
Remember when we were kids
and you were scared?
You were having one of your episodes.
And I would tell you to squeeze my hand.
And as long as you could feel my hand,
you knew I was there
and it was okay and everything was real.
Well now I need you to help me.
Make me feel like everything is okay.
You're not gonna find any answers
in the old safe deposit box.
Then it'll be a short trip.
Condolences.
He's an Irish mobster
out of Hell's Kitchen
trying to recreate the glory days
but online instead of the streets.
Operates what looks like a
legitimate shipping website.
But shipping people, Mr. Maguire?
More like disappearing people.
We pieced together his
AlphaBay connections
and ID'ed 17 career criminals
he helped walk off the street,
never to be seen again,
living happy lives under new names
all over the world.
Mr. Maguire,
you and I, we could help each other.
You talk to me and maybe
I could put in a good word.
You seem a kind lass
and I'd love to help you help me,
should I need the helping.
But I'm an innocent man, you see?
Agent DiPierro, I'm sorry to interrupt.
You should see this.
Chaos and sadness in Tribeca tonight
following the report of an
apparent suicide jumper.
You met with him today, didn't you?
Did he seem upset or worried or...
What are you talking about?
They haven't publicly released the name,
but it's Agent Horton
from the Santiago case.
A spokesperson for the
New York Fire Department
confirmed that a middle-aged
man died on impact.
He jumped from an eighth
floor apartment window
shortly after 5:00 o'clock this evening.
- _
- At this time that's as much information
- as they're willing to release.
- _
- However, I'm told that the identity
has been confirmed and
that the NYFD has notif...
It's gone.
What?
The safe deposit box. It's gone.
Payment lapsed two years ago.
We tried contacting the account owner...
your mother... but never heard back.
It's policy to dispose of the contents
after a 120 day grace period.
You threw away my mom's shit?
It's policy.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
I'll, uh...
give you a few minutes.
This is ridiculous. Let's go.
We still have to pick
up her fucking ashes.
What's going on?
Didn't even know what was in there.
Don't you get it, Elliot?
It's not about the fucking box.
It's about the fact that
you don't give a shit.
About mom?
Fucking sue me for not
giving a shit about her
- after what she did to us.
- Not mom.
Angela.
You were right.
She's gone.
I mean, how do you do it?
How do you just move on like that?
I haven't.
- What are you doing?
- Open it.
You recognize that tape?
How did mom get this?
No idea.
This wasn't for her.
Maybe she wished it were.
Why would she even listen to it?
She was lonely.
What are you doing?
I'm gonna listen to it.
And you're gonna listen with me.
I can't.
Come on.
♪ It's Christmas ♪
- ♪ All over the world ♪
- ♪ It's Christmas ♪
- Is it recording?
- We're live.
- You ready, Angela?
- Ready.
Okay.
Three, two, one.
Good morning, Washington Township.
We are your hosts Elliot Alderson...
Darlene Alderson...
And Angela Moss.
And we're here to say... ready?
Happy Mother's Day, Mrs. Moss!
Happy Mother's Day. I love you, Mom.
We love you, too.
♪ Come and behold Him... ♪
♪ Born the king of angels... ♪
You're a little unbalanced.
The tree.
Yes.
To the left.
Happy Holidays, Phillip.
I was pleased you reached out,
having been so quiet
these past few months.
Is that why you're here?
- To make an attempt at...
- Look.
It would be a waste of both our times
to speculate on why I'm here.
The truth is simple.
Let's give that a shot.
I'm resigning
as CEO of E Corp by the end of year.
Which means, of course,
I'll be parting ways
with the Deus Group as well.
Well, that is obviously unacceptable.
Your tenure at E Corp
will be over soon enough,
but you will simply have to wait.
Nothing can rock the boat now
as my project has not yet shipped.
Yes, yes, I understand,
but here's the thing.
I don't care.
Do not forget your loyalty.
My loyalty has been unquestionable.
You've taken nearly everything from me.
I'd like to leave with
what little I have left.
You know that in order for
me to replace you as CEO,
the Deus Group members must all agree
on your successor.
In person.
Well, perhaps a New Year's celebration
will befit this fresh start, hmm?
Your request is absurd.
You know we can't organize a
meeting within the next week.
And yet I have faith you'll find a way.
That is not how this
fucking game is played!
Game?
Game, that word.
There's our problem.
There's an end point.
There must be, eventually.
And I've reached mine.
Since the game is what you care about,
you should be happy.
You won.
♪ Oh God let us adore him ♪
♪ Christ the Lord ♪
Hello?
I played my hand.
And?
And now we wait.
Thank you.
Don't thank me.
I'm not doing this for you.
You ready? I've got Mom's ashes.
Who was that?
No one.
I saw your phone earlier
when you were here.
And on the train platform.
Why are you hacking Susan
Jacobs's Ecoin wallet?
Why do you care?
Because I do.
Why?
I knew her.
The last transaction
in her Ecoin wallet.
At the animal shelter?
What about it?
That wasn't her.
It was me.
It was you...
who broke into her house.
You were in jail.
Fsociety needed a new base.
But she caught you.
She was supposed to be out of town.
Darlene...
what did you do?
What, you want me to say it?
Jesus fucking Christ!
I knew you wouldn't get it.
Then why did you tell me?
I guess I had to know.
Know what?
That we'd still be okay.
Even if you knew what I did.
I read what she did.
The Washington Township case.
I need everything you
have on Susan Jacobs.
Why?
Susan Jacobs was also
working for the Dark Army.
And what does that have to do with you?
I'm going after whiterose.
You know that's suicide, right?
Probably.
And you're gonna do it anyway?
Why not give up?
Can't.
She'll find me.
Us.
She'll find us both. That's
why you're doing this.
I'm in.
No.
This is exactly why I didn't
tell you in the first place.
I'm not giving you a choice.
Besides, you need me.
Face it, every hack
you've ever pulled off
is because Fsociety helped you,
and right now we're
all that's left, okay?
If this is the biggest
thing you're ever gonna do,
then we're doing it together.
Give me your phone.
I rigged Signal's API to beam GPS coords
so we can share locations.
That way if you're
ever worried about me,
you'll know where I am.
It's done.
Okay, I'm in whether you like it or not.
I honestly wasn't expecting
you to say whiterose.
I mean, I knew you were up to something,
but you were acting like
such a total sketchball,
I figured it had to do with Vera.
Vera?
What are you talking... what
does he have to do with anything?
Well, that's what I was wondering.
I mean, he freaked me the fuck out
when he showed up at your building
a couple months ago,
but when I told you,
you just blew it off
like it was no big deal.
I don't need to worry about him, do I?
No.
You should get going.
Pull everything you have on Susan.
You coming?
I'll be right there.
Elliot, thanks...
For today.
I don't know what Darlene is talking...
Price made his move.
We might actually have
a shot at whiterose.
But none of that matters 'cause
I can't fucking trust you!
Listen to me.
I don't know anything about Vera.
You heard what she said.
She told one of us, and it wasn't me.
There's no reason for
me to keep that from you.
Fuck it!
You wanna go back to not
talking to each other?
Locking each other out?
Fighting for control?
Look at me! I am telling you the truth.
I am not the one Darlene talked to.
If it wasn't you,
and it wasn't me...
Who was it?
I've been looking all over for you.
You shouldn't be sitting
there. That's not your seat.
Why? I thought...
They're not ready yet.
- We need to wait.
- For what?
For him.
You mean Mr. Robot?
No.
Elliot?
The other one.