‐ Alexa, are we friends?
‐ Yes.
‐ She said you haven't
been sleeping.
You need your rest.
‐ You still having them?
‐ In this day and age,
it's sicker not
having panic attacks.
Fuck!
‐ Wow. I've never touched
something so beautiful.
‐ I feel the same way
each time.
‐ Can't we just be
a normal couple
that looks up
vacation packages to Budapest?
‐ Just so you know‐‐
Full‐time freelance now.
Only loyalty is to
the almighty paper.
‐ I want you to destroy
Whiterose's machine.
Everything you need to know
is on here.
‐ You can't make
your own currency.
That is the federal
government's job.
‐ With Ecoin equal to $1,
we are the authority.
‐ You know that night
we spent together.
‐ So this is why you came here.
You were just using me.
‐ You know it was
more than that.
‐ Well, I am not
leaving you like this.
‐ You wanna help me?
‐ This is all my fault.
‐ Take them down.
‐ The data dump
from fsociety was easily
the largest and most damning
doxxing case in history.
While only a small percentage
of the documents in the breach
have been substantiated
at this time,
those that have
are proving to be accurate.
With regard to their source,
the intelligence community
is cautioning
the overall veracity
of the data dump
and rush to judgment, citing
fears falsified documents‐‐
‐ And then your 1K letter
to the FBI will be issued
by the US Attorney's office
once everything you've told us,
and what you've logged in here,
checks out.
Now, I do need to mention
these are some serious crimes
you committed, Agent DiPierro.
You may come out of this
with a record.
There's not much
we can do about that.
‐ China's Minister of State
Security has been exposed
as the infamous hacker
and leader of the Dark Army
known only as Whiterose.
Intelligence officials
who have long thought
Whiterose's identity...
‐ Those dresses he showed me.
‐ Were the key to confirming
Zhang's double life.
‐ He was trying to tell me
who he was.
‐ Saying it was the missing
link that finally allowed them
to connect Whiterose...
‐ I'm sorry,
who are you referring to?
‐ China has yet to officially
respond to the claims...
‐ Nothing.
‐ In either the Deus Group
or the Dark Army.
‐ As for your job
at the Bureau,
you're on administrative leave
for six months
until OPR does their thing.
‐ What's in the bag?
‐ Oh. This is saline.
We'll be putting
some medicine in there
so you can get some rest.
‐ No.
No drugs.
I don't want any drugs.
I'm gonna leave soon anyway.
‐ Oh, sweetie, you can't
leave here anytime soon.
‐ She's right, Dom.
You need to stay put.
Plus, with everything
going on out there,
we don't think you should
go home anyway.
‐ I'm not going home.
I need to see my family.
‐ They're in one of
our safe houses, Dom.
SO‐4's watching them,
24/7 rotation.
‐ I need to see them
for myself.
‐ Have already issued a joint
statement on the matter.
‐ Um... that can't happen.
‐ The heck is that
supposed to mean?
They're my family.
I should be able to see them.
‐ It's like I said.
Until OPR clears you‐‐
‐ I'm not cleared?
‐ World Bank, WTO,
and the US Federal Reserve
are still trying
to piece together the events.
Reports continue to come in
from around the globe
of the far reaching
cyber heist.
‐ I can't believe this.
‐ The confirmed victims
of the robbery
include prominent businessmen,
CEOs...
‐ You don't trust me to know
where my own family is?
‐ Not now, no.
‐ Officials believe
the compromised Deus Group
accounts were managed by
Cyprus National Bank.
They're thought to be
at the center of the hack.
‐ You gotta be
fucking kidding me.
‐ All you need
to worry about right now
is getting a good
night's sleep.
This hospital's gonna take
great care of you.
Now make sure she gets
whatever she needs.
‐ Deus Group lost trillions of
dollars in cyber‐attacks.
Law enforcement authorities
suspect fsociety
to be the architects
of the heist‐‐
‐ Can I get you anything
before I go?
‐ I wanna go home.
‐ Pardon me?
‐ I have to go home.
‐ Sweetheart,
it's like I said earlier,
the doctor isn't recommend‐‐
‐ The doctor said
the surgery went great.
Right?
And I'm able to walk around
just fine
as long as I don't
tear my stitches.
You can't legally keep me here
if I wanna leave.
‐ Yes, we can discharge you
against medical advice, but‐‐
‐ That's what I want.
I really appreciate this, but
I don't need this wheelchair.
‐ Hospital policy, ma'am.
Did the nurse call
your pickup contact?
‐ What?
‐ Who's picking you up?
‐ Nobody's picking me up.
‐ What's that?
‐ Just gonna grab a cab.
‐ You can't do that, ma'am.
‐ Why not?
‐ Since the hospital
administered anesthesia,
you have to have
somebody with you.
Can't just put you in a cab
with a stranger.
You sure there's
nobody you can call?
A friend, a family member‐‐
‐ No.
I don't have anyone.
‐
What about one of those FBI
guys that was here earlier?
I could give
one of them a call.
‐ Definitely not.
‐ All right.
I'm gonna check the
Social Services volunteer list
and see who we have
available today.
It'll just take a sec.
Hang tight.
I'll be back.
‐ This is ridiculous‐‐I told
you, I'm good, I'm just gonna‐‐
‐ Can I trust you to behave?
Or do we need to bring
security over here?
‐ Open up. We don't have
a lot of time.
What the fuck is
going on here?
Don't worry about that.
We're not staying.
You shouldn't even be here.
When I‐‐
It took me forever to find
what hospital you were at,
and when I found out
you went home‐‐
‐ Want a grilled cheese
sandwich?
‐ Why are you even here?
Shouldn't you still be
at the hospital?
‐ Probably.
Figured not
the safest place to be,
given what you guys did.
Saw the news, guess you really
pulled it off.
‐ Which is why we need to
get the fuck out of here.
Elliot and I have
a getaway plan lined up,
and I think it'd be in your
best interest to come with us.
‐ I'm not going anywhere.
‐ Dom, you cannot stay here.
Best bet is to leave with us
until this whole thing
blows over.
‐ I have to stay here
until the OPR investigation
clears my name.
‐ Who gives a shit about that?
‐ I do.
‐ Why?
‐ Because then I can
see my family again.
Then I can finally
apologize to them
for everything
I put them through.
Alexa, play some Faith Hill.
‐ Shuffling songs
by Faith Hill.
♪ ♪
‐ I can't remember
the last time
I had a good grilled
cheese sandwich.
Every day,
I'd come home from work
and say I was gonna make myself
a grilled cheese sandwich,
but I was always too tired.
‐ ♪ Baby hello, oh no,
Good‐bye ♪
‐ Now I've finally done it.
‐ ♪ Shooting straight
across the sky ♪
♪ It's the way you love me ♪
‐ You want a bite?
‐ So that's it then?
You're just gonna
sit here and wait for
the Dark Army to come kill you?
Or did you actually think
that dresser over there
was gonna do anything more
than throw off your feng shui?
‐ I told you,
I need to stay here.
‐ What you need is
to hit the road with me
and get a good night's sleep
somewhere safe.
‐ You know,
you're the second person
that's told me that today.
Good night's sleep.
Boss said the same thing.
‐ ♪ All I wanted
was a white knight ♪
‐ Five years.
I haven't really slept
in five years,
save for a few nightmares.
‐ Not true. Saw you sleeping
last time I was here.
‐ You mean when I busted you
stealing my badge
out of my safe?
‐ ♪ It's centrifugal motion ♪
‐ Yeah, I wasn't really
asleep then either.
‐ ♪ It's that pivotal moment ♪
♪ It's unthinkable ♪
♪ This kiss, this kiss ♪
[drawers slamming
♪ Unsinkable ♪
‐ What are you doing?
‐ Where do you keep your socks?
‐ Darlene.
‐ Stop!
‐ You're coming with me.
‐ I'm not going
anywhere with you.
‐ Well, I'm not gonna let you
just sit here and wait to die.
‐ As opposed to
what you're doing?
What's your plan, anyway?
Run?
How long?
How far?
Where is this magical place
when you're gonna
feel safe enough
to stop looking
over your shoulder?
‐ I'm not gonna let
the Dark Army
kill another person
I care about.
Not when there's something
I can still do about it.
‐ I'm good, Darlene.
The FBI has my back.
‐ The FBI has you
under investigation.
‐ ♪ Subliminal ♪
♪ This kiss, this kiss ♪
♪ It's criminal ♪
‐ Fine. You want my underwear,
go for it.
‐ Dom, we have a plan.
A good one.
We've got fake passports, plane
tickets, and safe transport.
Just come with me.
‐ ♪ It's the way you love me ♪
‐ You're just gonna
sit there all alone.
‐ I'm not alone.
I have Alexa, remember?
‐ Sorry, I'm having trouble
understanding right now.
‐ Ugh!
‐ The fuck did you just do?
‐ Snap the fuck out of it!
This is not a person!
She is not real.
She is not your friend.
She is just a robot you use
to buy paper towels.
Look around you.
Dom, this is emptiness.
There is nothing here for you,
but there is still
a chance for you out there
if you come with us.
Now go get your toothbrush.
Why don't you
go ahead without me?
I'll be there
in a few minutes.
‐ Looks like
you found her okay.
‐ Yeah, she's‐‐
still a little shell‐shocked,
but she'll be fine.
How about you?
You're not...
gonna come with us, are you?
‐ I need to go back
to Washington Township
and you cannot
come with me this time.
‐ I don't want to.
This was it for me.
I'm done now.
Before I go...
You wanna do the honors?
All the money has been passed
through multiple crypto
tumblers and shell accounts.
Should be completely
untraceable now.
It's ready to go out.
‐ This should be you.
This is your win, not mine.
‐
Are you sure you don't want
to come with us?
‐ I can't.
I'm not done.
♪ ♪
‐ Well, in that case,
any advice for a road trip?
I've never been on one before.
♪ ♪
‐ Neither have I.
Recommend getting a bunch
of Sour Patch Kids.
‐
‐ For you to play with.
‐ I wish we were there now.
‐ Well, it's a long way yet.
Past the great rock that
looks like a Long Neck.
‐ Oh, hey.
‐ Still a long way,
but we'll get there.
‐ Holy shit.
‐ I'm sorry, have we met?
‐ Yes, we fucking met.
The barn?
‐ Doesn't ring a bell.
‐ You shot four people?
‐ Hey Hopper, come back!
‐ Oh, shit!
That's right!
Now I've got you.
‐ You again?
Go away!
‐ What the hell is going on?
You're Dark Army.
‐ No, dude.
I'm actually here to help
my boy Elliot and his sis.
‐ So what, you're just a‐‐
a gun for hire, or‐‐
‐ I mean,
it's like I always say:
Gotta keep a open mind
at every opportunity
that comes your way.
You've seen that one movie,
"Three Days of the Condor,"
right?
Dude, you've never seen
"Three Days of the Condor,"
and you're a fucking FBI agent?
You've gotta check that out.
Normally I don't go for that
'70s paranoia shit,
but I don't know, this one‐‐
this one really spoke to me.
You know, maybe it was what
my boy Joubert says:
"I don't interest myself
in the why.
"I think more often
in terms of the when,
sometimes where,
but always how much."
I fucking felt that.
Got me opening up my eyes
to diversifying my revenue
streams and whatnot.
Yo, last quarter, I nearly
tripled my net profits,
according to this chick
who does my books,
and shorty Japanese,
so you know she know what
the fuck she talking about.
She got me stumped off
this one question, though,
saying that I should
incorporate sooner.
What do you think?
S Corp, or LLC?
‐ Oh, shit.
I forgot to tell you
he's working with us now.
♪ ♪
‐ You should get some rest.
‐ So I've heard.
‐ ♪ Midnight hour ♪
♪ Almost over ♪
‐ It's pretty out here.
I've never driven
to Boston this way.
‐ We're taking
the scenic route.
‐ ♪ One more chance
couldn't be... ♪
‐ Yeah, believe it or not,
Connecticut's swarming
with Dark Army,
given the concentration
of RWAs.
Rich, white assholes.
Yep, that's who they like
doing their business with.
Usually, that's their
number one client, in fact.
Anyways, that's why we're
staying off the main roads.
Besides, I gotta find
a rest stop anyway.
Gotta steal me a mirror
real quick.
‐ ♪ I wonder what you'll do ♪
♪ When your chance
rolls around ♪
‐ What, do you not
know your Vonnegut?
‐ ♪ You gotta know how much
I want to keep you ♪
‐ I gotta take a whiz, okay?
Too many Code Reds
this morning.
‐ ♪ I'm afraid it will
all fall down ♪
‐ Man, nobody fucking reads
anymore.
‐ ♪ Wait for me,
all right ♪
♪ I guess that's
more than I should ask ♪
♪ But won't you wait for me ♪
♪ Please wait for me ♪
♪ Although I know the light
is fading fast ♪
‐ What do you think of Jackie?
♪ ♪
‐ Jackie's whoever
you want her to be.
♪ ♪
‐ Yeah, it's easy
for you to say.
You're not pretending
to be someone you're not.
♪ ♪
‐ You think Leon's
my real name?
‐ ♪ And ours
is doing nothing ♪
♪ But all the time we spent ♪
♪ It must be good
for something ♪
♪ Please forgive all the
disturbance I'm creating ♪
♪ But you got a lot to learn
if you think I'm not... ♪
‐ Where are we?
‐ In the land of RWAs.
‐ ♪ Wait for me,
oh, I ♪
‐ Best you keep your eye out.
‐
Jackie's a diehard
for Hall & Oates.
She's a gym teacher.
No, she's not a gym teacher.
She's a...
pastry chef.
She's got a soft spot
for Nutella.
We ready?
‐ Not yet. Leon said something
about stealing a mirror
and then went on about how
illiterate America is
and then said he had to piss
a bunch of red,
so I took that as my cue
to walk away.
Look at all these people.
‐ It's the day after Christmas.
They're all probably
on their way back home.
Holidays are over.
It's back to the grind
for most of them, I guess.
‐ It sucks.
I wanna show you something.
Come on.
‐ Should we really be out
in the open like this?
‐ I don't know.
Maybe not, but‐‐
For once, I wanna
drop the paranoia
and just take all this in.
Just for this moment.
‐ What is this moment,
exactly?
♪ ♪
‐ Watch this.
‐ What did you just do?
‐
Just give it a few seconds.
♪ ♪
‐ Darlene, you're worrying me.
‐ I'm pretty good at that,
aren't I?
‐ Tell me.
‐ Be patient.
‐ If you did something,
I need to know.
‐ Oh, do you?
‐ Is this something
illegal again?
‐ Dom.
‐ I'm serious, Darlene.
If you don't tell me
what you're up to‐‐
‐ Just wait.
‐ What is it with you
and breaking the law?
It's like a fetish.
‐ Shut the fuck up
and just watch.
♪ ♪
‐ I don't get it.
What's going on?
‐ All of the money Whiterose
and her cronies
have been stealing for decades
just went back to the people.
♪ ♪
‐ How?
‐ We found a way to evenly
disperse it anonymously
into everyone's Ecoin wallets.
♪ ♪
‐ Everyone got this much?
‐ Yep.
And due to E Corp's insistence
that Ecoin remain independent
from the US dollar,
it is completely impossible
for them to reverse
the transactions.
♪ ♪
‐ This is illegal.
This is stealing.
‐ After what the Dark Army
did to you?
Fuck, after what
they did to everyone,
you really wanna
start defending them?
‐ This isn't what justice
is supposed to look like.
We have laws for a reason.
‐ And they were so powerful,
they wrote the laws
to benefit themselves.
They got away with everything
because they banked on us,
all of us, to trust the system.
That was our vulnerability,
and they took advantage of it.
It took this
to finally stop them,
and you were a part of it.
Look around.
This is it.
♪ ♪
Everything we've been through
led up to this one moment‐‐
The greatest redistribution
of wealth in history.
We just Robin Hooded
those evil motherfuckers.
If you ask me, this is exactly
what justice looks like.
♪ ♪
Whoo!
‐ People are staring at you.
‐ I don't care!
Fuck yeah, bitches!
♪ ♪
‐
‐ May I have
your attention, please.
This area is for loading
and unloading only.
Vehicles must be attended
at all times.
For security reasons...
‐ Hey, make sure you check out
that Sydney Pollack joint
when you get a chance.
Thank me later, Jackie.
So...
Did you keep any of it?
‐ Keep what?
‐ Covert.
That's cool.
I'm saying, though,
if you're looking to get into
some shit when you get back,
I got some shit for you.
‐ Like what?
‐ Adventures and whatnot.
You know, a high like this‐‐
it don't come so easy
with the normies.
‐ Thanks, dude, but, uh,
I'm trying to lay low
for a bit.
‐ No doubt.
But with skills like yours,
the pay is good,
and you get to be your own
boss, 'cause you know,
you a boss, girl.
‐ Let me think about it.
‐ Cool.
Till the next episode, then.
‐ Vehicles must be attended
at all times.
For security reasons,
unattended vehicles...
‐ You should not accept offers
of transportation from anyone
without prior arrangement.
‐ Dom?
How the hell are you?
Hey, you coming over here
to pick up a copy?
Hey, they're great
for long flights.
A real page turner,
especially when you
get to the part
where he strangles his mother
to death in Chapter 12.
Spoiler alert!
You know,
today's your lucky day.
I'm gonna sign you a copy.
Here you go.
Aw, come on.
Yeah, the book's flying
off the shelves.
It's a real stocking stuffer.
In fact, that's
what I'm doing here.
I got a little
book tour stop at UMass.
Anyway, how have you been?
Is that Elliot's sister?
You two a thing now, or‐‐
I knew I picked up
on something.
‐ Please don't hurt us.
‐ Hurt you?
Why would I hurt you?
‐ Because I‐‐
I disobeyed orders, I‐‐
I killed my handler.
‐ Oh, she was a pain
in the ass.
Trust me, you were
doing them a favor.
And‐‐and your little
loudmouth friend over there,
yeah, well, what she did
was a bad thing, but‐‐
Well, word around camp is
they don't care about
you two no more.
‐ What do you mean?
‐ They've picked up
and skedaddled off
to something more important.
‐ Where?
‐ That I can't tell you.
‐ But all those things you said
you were gonna do to my family.
‐ No one cares
about your family now.
Look, I'm telling you,
the Dark Army's not something
you need to worry about
anymore.
Look, if they wanted
to get to you two,
I would know about it.
Trust me.
‐ But‐‐But I‐‐
I saw you butcher Santiago with
an axe when he got out of line.
‐ Yeah.
That was fun.
All right, well,
this was nice.
I'm gonna go.
Make sure you pay for that.
She still needs
to pay for that.
Take it easy, Dom.
‐ Just wanted me to buy
one of his books.
‐ And you did?
‐ The cashier made me
because he autographed it.
‐ He actually said
they don't care anymore.
‐ Yep.
‐ I don't get it.
Where did the Dark Army go?
‐ I don't know,
he wouldn't tell me.
All I know is we don't
have to run anymore.
♪ ♪
‐ Yeah, but we're here.
Might as well still go.
I've heard Budapest
is pretty dope.
‐ Why Budapest anyway?
‐ Cisco always talked
about going there,
but once what happened,
happened
I just couldn't go by myself.
‐ ♪ How does the motion
make me last ♪
‐ Globe Airlines flight 4057
to Budapest
will begin boarding
at Gate B31.
‐ That's us.
We should get going.
♪ ♪
‐ Where's your brother?
‐ He's not coming with us.
‐ Why not?
‐ He's running behind.
He's gonna catch
the next flight out.
Let's go.
‐ Wait.
I can't do this.
♪ ♪
‐ Can't do what?
‐ You convinced me to come
because the Dark Army
was a threat.
Now they're not.
‐ Doesn't mean
we still can't go.
‐ Do you even really want to go
to Budapest anyway?
You said it yourself, this was
Cisco's dream, not yours.
‐ Then, we won't go there.
When we land, we'll hitch
a ride to somewhere else.
Just come with me.
‐ Darlene.
I can't go.
‐ ♪ In these lines ♪
♪ I know you're
looking forward to them ♪
‐ But you said you would.
‐ ♪ What is it
that has my mind ♪
‐ You don't need me
to come with you.
Whatever your brother's
actually up to,
you don't need him, either.
♪ ♪
‐ No, I can't handle shit solo,
Dom. You've seen me.
I get panic attacks,
I freak out‐‐
‐ You're gonna be fine.
‐ I'm no good on my own.
I've tried.
‐ ♪ And their colors
create my mood ♪
♪ ♪
‐ I'm sorry.
‐ ♪ Two places
I've never been ♪
‐ I've got responsibilities
here, I can't just...
walk away from my family,
my job, my‐‐
‐ Responsibilities?
That's what this is about?
You know your family is safe.
Your job is on hold.
There is nothing
for you to do here.
♪ ♪
Jesus, Dom, no wonder
you can't sleep.
You hold on to a lot,
and you hold on fucking tight.
Maybe running away
might actually help you.
‐ Running away to Budapest
will help me?
‐ This isn't about
Budapest.
You leave this airport,
you're just gonna go back to
the grind like everyone else.
I'm talking about
giving yourself a break.
Okay?
About finally letting go.
‐ Global Airlines flight 4057
to Budapest
will begin boarding
at Gate B31.
♪ ♪
‐
‐ Send me a postcard, okay?
♪ ♪
‐ One other thing.
I wrote down the number
of a friend of mine.
He works at US Cyber Command.
‐
Your bright idea is
for me to be some pig?
‐ When you're ready to grow up.
♪ ♪
Don't take too long, though.
They need you.
‐
They can't handle me.
♪ ♪
‐ ♪ You're stuck in my head,
stuck in my heart ♪
♪ Stuck in my body, body ♪
♪ I wanna go
get out of here ♪
♪ I'm sick of
the party, party ♪
♪ I'd run away ♪
♪ I'd run away with you ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ This is the part
you gotta say ♪
♪ All that you're feeling,
feeling ♪
♪ Packing a bag,
leaving tonight ♪
♪ While everyone's sleeping,
sleeping ♪
‐ Welcome,
ladies and gentleman,
to Global Airlines
flight 4057 to Budapest.
Boarding will begin shortly.
First we would like to invite
any passengers
that need extra time
or assistance‐‐
you now will come aboard
through gate B31.
‐ ♪ And I'll find your lips
in the streetlights ♪
♪ I wanna be there with you ♪
♪ Baby ♪
♪ Take me to the feeling ♪
♪ I'll be your sinner
in secret ♪
♪ When the lights go out ♪
♪ Run away with me ♪
♪ Baby ♪
♪ Every single minute ♪
♪ I'll be your hero
and win it ♪
‐ We are now boarding
all passengers
in group A and group B.
‐ ♪ Run away with me,
run away with me ♪
♪ Up in the clouds,
high as a kite ♪
♪ Over the city, city ♪
♪ We never sleep,
we never try ♪
♪ When you are with me,
with me ♪
‐ Ladies and gentleman,
group C, you are welcome
to board for flight 4057.
‐ ♪ Ooh ♪
♪ 'Cause you make
me feel like ♪
♪ I could be driving you
all night ♪
♪ And I'll find your lips
in the streetlights ♪
♪ I wanna be there with you ♪
‐
‐ ♪ Oh, baby ♪
♪ Take me to the feeling ♪
♪ I'll be your
sinner in secret ♪
♪ When the lights go out ♪
♪ Run away with me ♪
♪ Hold on to me, I ♪
♪ Never wanna let you go ♪
♪ Run away with me ♪
‐
‐ Excuse me, are you okay?
‐ Everyone,
please take your seats
and fasten your seatbelts.
We will be closing
the cabin doors shortly
in preparation for takeoff.
‐ Ma'am?
Are you okay? Is there
something I can help you with?
Are you missing something?
‐ In the pocket
in front of you,
you'll find a flight
safety information card.
Please take it out and look
over it before we take off.
‐ No, I'm good.
‐
‐ Do you need any help?
No.
No, thanks, I'm okay.
‐ Final call for flight 4057
to Budapest.
Final call for flight
4057 to Budapest.
‐ That your flight
they just called?
‐ Yeah.
Yeah, but I'm not going.
‐ Are you sure?
I can get someone.
‐ No.
No, I've got it.
I can take care of myself.
‐ Please check your seatbelts.
Have your seat backs in an
upright position for takeoff.
Thank you.
‐ Good afternoon,
ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome aboard.
Captain speaking.
We're gonna get you out of
here just as soon as possible.