Mr. Alderson needs to
be kept on a short leash
and trained not to bite his master.
If I can find a way
to rob the Deus Group,
Whiterose loses everything.
You have to have a contact at the bank.
I need everything you
have on Susan Jacobs.
I'm in, whether you like it or not.
You want me to request
that the entire Deus Group
gather without even a pretext?
I'm resigning as CEO of E Corp.
I played my hand.
Now we wait.
Fernando Vera.
DJ, shoot the cocksucker.
When he showed up at your building
a couple months ago...
The CTO position is worthless.
When the time is right,
we'll expose them.
There's something about
this. I can feel it.
I know him.
I actually think he
might have been involved.
- Whiterose.
- Does the guy even exist?
Minister Zhang.
The official fucking bogeymen.
- State security.
- Whiterose.
Who is Whiterose?
IBM will pay to shareholders
a cash dividend of $22
UN per depository share,
and this payment will bring
the total annual cash dividend
to $44 UN per depository share.
And along with our purchase agreement,
we're also willing to offer
your government a discount
on tech licensing fees.
_
Director Zhang is quite
taken by your generous offer.
Excellent.
We look forward to a long
and prosperous partnership.
_
Uh...
the feeling is mutual.
Thank you, Director Zhang,
for paving the way for
IBM's first facility in Asia.
_
♪ Could have been so much more... ♪
♪ We know they got nothing but time ♪
_
John Carpenter's "The Thing,"
now playing in theaters.
the great American network.
_
You'll find high-caliber television...
Hmm?
USA celebrates the arts
with music and performances
that you'll never forget.
Be a part of the great
American network...
_
I will be wearing this the
day my project is shipped.
The day we begin to build a new world.
Please have it pressed and ready.
Minister Zhang, it's
too early to celebrate.
We have a number of issues to discuss.
There's Freddy Lomax...
the cartoon character you call a lawyer
who committed suicide?
The person he met with escaped
after compromising Grand
Central's surveillance system.
And?
Gaining access to Grand
Central is no easy feat.
We've been waiting for
Elliot Alderson's next move,
and this could be it.
And the fact that this is coinciding
with Phillip Price's
abrupt resignation request?
Well, it's like you always say:
There is no such thing as a coincidence.
Very well.
Refuse Price's demands
and keep on digging.
Additionally,
keep constant surveillance
on Elliot Alderson.
We will figure this out, Minister Zhang.
It will just require some patience.
_
No.
Minister Zhang?
Did you say something?
Give Phillip Price what he wants.
I'm sorry?
Let him know that we will
arrange a Deus Group meeting
to confirm a successor.
But sir...
Schedule the meeting for tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
If there's one way to
disrupt a man's plans,
it is to destabilize his timeline.
If they are indeed
planning something together,
we will not wait for
them to make a mistake.
We will force them into one.
Tomorrow's Christmas Day.
There's no way we'll be able
to get the Deus Group
together so quickly.
I have been trying to ship
my project to the Congo
for the last 302 days and counting.
Anything that will disrupt that
will no longer be tolerated.
I have officially run out of patience.
This rash behavior will
only come back to haunt you.
When Phillip Price resigns,
you will have no CEO at E Corp.
Wellick.
I'm sorry?
Call Mr. Wellick and
offer him the CEO position.
Tell him you are speaking for Whiterose.
I have no doubt that he will accept.
You ever play Russian Roulette?
They say once you pull that
trigger, it changes you
and you can't go back to who you were
before you heard that infamous click,
the sound of cheating death.
We've been lucky so far, but
I can't shake the feeling
that there's a barrel pointed at us
and we're running out of chances
to get that empty chamber.
I'm not sure what's taking
Vera so long to come at us
with bullets fully loaded.
Every time I try to
talk to Elliot about it,
he puts up a wall,
like he's flat-out throwing
me a forbidden error,
denying me the chance
to even bring it up.
But Vera's gonna find us sooner or later,
and I just hope we see
him coming when he does.
Oh, shit.
Krista.
Uh, give me a second.
Sure.
I've tried calling you.
Elliot, I thought I made myself clear.
Yeah, I got your letter.
I... I just wanted to talk to you.
You know that can't happen.
I explained that in the
letter as politely as I could.
You don't understand.
I'm... I'm doing better.
I'm finally talking to Mr. Robot
just like you always said I should.
We cannot have contact anymore.
Do you understand that?
I just want you to know
that I'm finally making
some real progress.
I don't feel safe around you!
Leave me alone.
Or I'll be forced to take legal action.
I wasn't asking you to treat me again.
I just wanted to say
thank you for helping me.
You okay?
Yeah.
Olivia Cortez was Susan Jacobs's contact
at Cyprus National Bank.
She's the Deus Group's
only U.S. account manager
since they want to
make their presence here
as minimal as possible.
She's our way in.
I don't see any Cyprus
National Bank accounts.
Yeah, these banks make their
lackeys use on-prem work boxes
that are closed loop and near
impossible to exploit remotely.
We'll have to get physical
access to her laptop.
Kinda makes sense.
What?
That you made this your HQ.
It's where it all started.
No better place to plan how it'll end.
It's just an abandoned office
I knew had a 10-gig fiber link.
Please.
I know you have a soft
spot for this nerd factory.
Where are you going?
Olivia's iCal says
her ex-husband's got her kid
tonight and she's got a date.
Should give me enough time
to check out her place
and get on her machine.
Whoa.
You think I'm your
little research monkey?
We agreed I'd handle the bank contact
and you'd deal with the SS7 license.
That was before I knew
we needed physical access.
Now you're gonna stay here
and get the cell service permissions.
No, thanks.
I'm gonna stick with the plan.
You can spend your Christmas Eve here
watching rats fuck.
I'm gonna go out and do this B&E.
Will you talk some sense into her?
Darlene...
this is not your
run-of-the-mill break-in.
This is a Deus Group contact.
Yeah, I get it, dude. It's dangerous.
Okay, you know this whole
protective older brother act's
gotten beyond lame.
I'm telling you, this is too...
Risky?
Perilous? Treacherous?
Hazardous to my health?
What the fuck do you think you're doing?
You're not going.
You're hurting me.
I know.
Is this you, or...
It's me.
What's happening to you?
You wanted to work with me.
This is the way it is.
If there's a problem, don't
be here when I get back.
And here I thought things
were better after yesterday.
But as per usual,
it's one step forward and
four fucking leaps back.
Nothing's ever gonna
change with you, is it?
No, it's not.
I should've never opened my door
when you came back into town.
There's no word for it, you know?
There's "orphan," "widow," "widower."
So what do you call someone
who's lost everyone?
Mom, dad, sister, girlfriend, friends.
A survivor?
Or a walking time bomb?
Elliot thinks the more he
restricts everyone's access,
the less vulnerable he'll be.
But there's a trade-off
that he's forgetting.
If you block everyone,
then what's the point of being here?
Of doing all this?
Of existing?
I'm that's her personal,
but check it anyway.
There's nothing on Cyprus National Bank,
but I've learned more
than I want to know
about this Evan dude
she's on a date with.
His name is Evan, for fuck's sake.
He's into snowboarding,
social media influencing,
and Reiki.
Classic Evan.
What'd you find?
That.
We got her credentials, but
without her security fob,
we don't have shit.
You check the closet.
I'll take the nightstand.
She'll have it on her.
It's bank protocol.
How do you know she
doesn't get sloppy sometimes
and leave it behind?
You read the same shit on her I did.
She's a single mom who spent
three years in night school
to get this job.
Someone like that isn't going to risk
the best gig they've
ever had by being sloppy.
So we install a listener on her machine,
wait for her to log in.
It's the holidays.
She isn't logging in anytime soon.
And even if she did,
we'd only got 60 seconds
to swipe the code.
Okay. We phish her, get her to log in,
catch the RSA code then.
We're all good.
If she doesn't take the bait?
We don't have time to chance it.
Well, if you have any
ideas, I'm all fucking ears.
Looks like he stood her up.
Okay, she's leaving.
Let's go back and regroup.
I found a bottle of
oxy in her apartment.
So?
She's an addict who's
supposedly gone straight.
Custody agreement says
if she gets caught using
again, she loses her kid.
So what do you want to do
with that information, exactly?
You know how this works.
- Hang on, kiddo.
- What for?
Why don't you try a little small talk?
Keep her here for a while, grab the fob,
and then punch in the code.
No. There's no time for small talk.
Not when we already own her.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me?
You're gonna want to sit back down.
What are you talking about?
'Cause I'm gonna buy you a drink.
I'm sorry, do I know you?
This is a waste of time we don't have.
I'm Elliot.
Now you know me.
I'm gonna take off, actually.
It's been a long day.
Okay. I'll come clean.
I couldn't help but
notice you were stood up.
Now, it's none of my business,
but the guy's clearly a sack of shit
to leave you alone on Christmas Eve,
and if you'd let me,
I'd like to apologize for those
of us who have done you wrong
by buying you a drink.
Another round?
Why not?
It's Christmas.
You're on, kiddo.
There you go, Juanito.
Tell your mama I packed
it special for her.
Merry Xmas.
Tell me you brought tidings
of joy about my dude Elliot.
Come on, bruh.
What was so important about
this motherfucker, anyway?
You know why we came back here, right?
Well, do you?
So you could be king of New York.
And in order for our
kingdom to be built,
I need a brilliant...
Architect. I know.
Yeah, see? You totally get it.
You just be selling yourself short.
Hey, listen here, bruh.
Look, I may not be no architect,
but let me tell you something:
I'm loyal... to the bone.
So let me just get my
gun, put it to his head,
and make him give you
what the fuck you want.
How many times I gotta explain it?
I don't want Elliot to be my prisoner.
A visionary like him
don't work like that.
I want him to be my partner!
Now, reflect...
and give me something I can use.
Come on, bruh.
This kid is aloof.
I may be able to catch him
around his hood sometimes,
but for the most part,
he riding solo and giving up nothing.
What do you mean, "for the most part"?
Well, see?
You gotta be more detailed.
The devil is in that shit.
Well, look. I...
I did see him arguing
with this lady, all right?
And she seemed pretty mad.
- Mad how?
- I don't know. Mad.
Details, bro.
Be specific. Was she crying?
Was... was her nipples hard?
Did a vein pop out of her forehead?
Man, make the connection.
Tell me you at least
took some fucking pics.
Really, man? Of... of course.
I got you. Look. Right there.
You see? She's pissed.
So what?
Look bro, we're wasting
our time with this.
I mean, we took the
risk to get back here.
I mean, shit, we might as
well put it to good use, fam.
Hey, kid.
Tell me what you see.
He feels bad because she's yelling,
like when my mama's mean to me.
It makes me sad,
like him.
How come this fuckin' little
kid sees it and you don't?
This ain't about her.
Her anger legit.
No doubt, the shit you
need to see is on him.
She hurt him.
Not no superficial pain,
neither, we talking...
stab-in-your-heart kind.
She our girl.
She knows something I gotta know.
Sorry, bruh.
I guess I just need someone
a little more detail-oriented.
So, uh,
we already know why I'm
here on Christmas Eve.
What's your sob story?
I don't know. I...
I guess I don't have
anywhere else to be.
No family?
My sister and I got into a big fight.
My mom died yesterday.
Oh, my God.
I'm so sorry.
For what?
For your...
you know, that thing
about your mom dying?
Oh.
No. We weren't that close.
Yeah, I kind of have the
same deal with my dad.
I mean, we used to be pretty tight.
But not as close as my mom and me.
She was amazing.
She died too.
Back in Colombia.
I took it really hard.
I kind of put my dad through
a lot of shit after that,
and...
But we don't have to get into it.
Okay.
I'm addicted...
to m...
morphine.
Well, do you have some on you?
- Uh...
- I'm kidding.
Oh, my God. Your face.
And now I feel bad.
No. No, that's okay. I...
I deserved that.
So how long you been clean?
Almost nine months now.
Well, not if you count...
the heroin I did two days ago.
But I didn't really want it.
Well, did someone hold you
down and force you to do it?
Yeah.
But I'm... I'm clean now.
Are you crazy or something?
I guess so.
I'm not like most people.
I'm starting to pick up on that.
Olivia?
Evan, from, uh, OkCupid.
I'm sorry. I have no idea who you are.
Isn't this you?
Nope.
This is totally you.
Look, it's getting late.
Well, it was nice to meet you, Elliot.
Well, you did better
than I thought you would.
♪ Yeah, I don't see the light ♪
♪ I saw in you before ♪
♪ And no, I don't ♪
♪ And I don't care anymore ♪
♪ Baby, believe me ♪
♪ And you had every chance ♪
♪ You destroy everything that you know ♪
♪ Uncontrollable ♪
♪ If you don't need me ♪
♪ Just let me go ♪
♪ You hate, you bite, you lose ♪
_
Uh, just looking for some aspirin.
Oh, shit.
Here, let me help.
I've got all this crap.
It's not what you think.
Look, earlier when I told you
that I put my dad through
some shit when my mom died...
It was because of this.
I was really fucked up
after my mom got killed.
Murdered, actually.
I never say that to anyone.
It totally wrecked me...
and I couldn't pull myself out of it.
And then, one day, someone
gave me a pill, and...
That was that. It was...
like, my way out of that black hole.
But it led me right into another one.
One that hurt a lot less.
For... for a while, anyway.
A reminder.
If I hate myself enough
to start using again,
I might as well kill myself.
So there it is.
The moment I tell you I'm crazy too.
I get it.
I know what it's like.
What?
Hating yourself.
I almost did it once.
What stopped you?
I promised a kid I'd take
him to go see "The Martian."
Yeah, of course.
You know, you can't scare me.
Well, there's a lot more
crazy where that came from.
But I think that's enough for tonight.
Who knew Olivia would be the one
to override Elliot's
attempts to deny access?
Now he's gotten the message:
letting people in doesn't have to hurt.
Why are you stopped when
we've got to get to Allsafe?
That van's been following us
since we got off the subway.
Dark Army?
It's gotta be.
You think Olivia ratted us out?
No. We got out of there clean.
This is a trap.
We've been off the radar for months.
All of a sudden, Whiterose
takes interest in us again?
What if she's trying to
find out about our plan?
Then let's show her we don't have one.
Just go home and act normal.
Here's our turn again.
Loading a bullet into a chamber...
spinning the cylinder...
and then...
the trigger.
Question is, are we getting
that friendly click?
Or is it the end of the game?
That's it.
We cannot go in there.
Let's make a run for it.
Run where?
They're outside too.
What do we do?
Exactly what we'd do if
we had nothing to hide.
Like I said before,
letting people in doesn't have to hurt...
but it can.
Especially if they're the type
of person that doesn't ask,
that just forces their way in
whether you want them to or not.
Elliot.
I've come with the news
we've been waiting for.
They want to make me CEO of E Corp.
Are you hearing me?
The offer came directly from Whiterose.
What's this... what are you doing?
This is exactly what
we've been waiting for.
We're on the inside. It's
time to take them down!
_