Everything we did was what they wanted.
I'm a prisoner, just like before.
I'm going after Whiterose.
I'm in. Give me your phone.
I rigged Signal's API so
we could share locations.
You fucked me!
I lost everything because of you.
My son's taken to Denmark,
and my wife's dead!
The Dark Army are just hackers.
He turned the gun on himself.
He erased his history.
You work for the Dark Army now.
My whole life is ruined because of you.
Olivia Cortez, she's the Deus Group's
only U.S. account manager.
She's our way in.
You wanted to work with
me, this is the way it is.
If there's a problem, don't
be here when I get back.
I'm resigning as CEO of E Corp.
Call Mr. Wellick and
offer him the CEO position.
That van's been following us
since we got off the subway.
Elliot, we're on the inside.
It's time to take them down.
Elliot, I've come with the
news we've been waiting for.
They want to make me CEO of E Corp.
Are you hearing me?
The offer came directly from Whiterose.
This is... what are you doing?
This is exactly what
we've been waiting for.
We're on the inside. It's
time to take them down.
I'm sorry, I've been
under a lot of stress.
I didn't mean to snap.
No, uh, I get it.
Okay, uh, here, have a seat.
You want... you want water or something?
Let me get you a glass.
There you go.
I'm gonna boot up my computer.
It'll just take a minute.
Fuck.
I forgot the install this morning.
Looks like it failed. I wonder why.
Logs say "out of disk space."
Just give me a second.
I need to adjust the swap partitions.
That should fix it.
"Boot device not found."
Shit, now my terminal's frozen.
Hard drive might be shot.
You know what, I'm gonna...
_
- Oh, fuck.
- Get in, check the logs.
If the recording wasn't
send back to Dark Army,
wipe everything and make
sure they can't track the van.
What about him?
He's dead.
To be clear, I am not calling you
because we are good.
I am calling because I got into
Olivia's Cyprus National Bank Account.
Unfortunately, her
access isn't good enough.
I can see all the Deus account numbers,
but she's not authorized
to transfer anything.
I got lateral access
inside the bank's system
but hit a wall.
All their authentication
goes through a proxy,
and everything else on
their domain is read-only,
which means we are gonna have
to break into Virtual Realty
and get on their servers.
Since the Deus Group
meeting is tomorrow,
I'm scouting the place now.
Security is lax with Christmas,
so we need to do it ASAP.
Also, can't help but
wonder why exactly the fuck
you are not answering my calls.
We were supposed to meet at Allsafe,
or did you forget again?
Dick.
Okay, you know what?
I'm coming to your apartment,
and when I get there,
I expect you to have heard this message
and already be prepping
for Virtual Realty.
Oh, and when you do get this voicemail,
keep this in mind: fuck you!
You are a fucking selfish
dickhead of an asshole
who is the shittiest brother on Earth!
I don't wanna say I
hate you, but I hate you.
I hate you so fucking much.
If I show up at your
apartment and you're hanging
from the goddamn ceiling
by a rope, that's cool.
In fact, that would be my preference.
So in sum, fuck off and die!
To continue your recording, press two.
To delete your recording, press three.
Please re-record your
message at the tone.
Hey, Elliot,
it's me.
_
Elliot?
Okay, it looks like the
logs were never sent.
So all we gotta do
is get rid of the body
and the van, and we're good to go, okay?
I'm gonna go pick us up
a couple of snow shovels.
We're not here for shovels.
What are we here for?
Go inside, pay for the
gas, and grab a lighter.
Oh, Internet's down.
No Ecoin.
$19.86.
Do I know you?
I don't think so.
You look awfully familiar.
Yeah, sorry, we're kind of in a hurry.
You sure we haven't met before?
Yeah, you must have me
mistaken for someone else.
You an actor?
Can you just ring him up?
Wait, were you on "Big Brother"?
Yeah, that must be it.
I knew it. I never forget a face.
Keep the change.
Merry Christmas!
Where'd you move the van to?
I didn't move the van.
Hey, hey, hey, what are you doing?
Hey, hey, thief!
- Thief, I've called the police.
- Shit.
Hey, dude, you're straight
up trying to steal my car.
It's cool, man. It's cool.
You don't need to call the cops, okay?
- I'm walking away.
- No... hold on.
You trying to steal
my car and walk away.
What's up?
Dude, do you really want
to deal with the hassle
of calling the cops?
It's just gonna end in
an all-nighter for you
at the station, followed
by a shit ton of paperwork.
Besides, nothing... nothing happened.
You busted me, I'm walking away.
No harm, no foul.
Yeah, but I got questions
that need answering.
First, have you seen my keys?
No.
That was my only question.
Can I please go now?
Oh, wait, I got another question.
Can you start my car?
Really?
Yeah, I usually use my keys,
and I can't seem to find them.
Okay, you're not really planning
on driving like this, are you?
Well, I gotta get home.
Dude, you are drunk as shit.
Can't you just call a cab or something?
No, cabs don't go where I'm headed.
Where is that, the North Pole?
No.
It's Upstate. Foxrock.
What's your name?
Tobias.
Hi, Tobias.
I'm Darlene. We're friends, right?
Yeah, I'd like that.
Great.
So here's an idea.
I'll drive you home if I can borrow
your car afterwards for a quick errand.
You drive a hard bargain, Dolly.
Darlene.
Exactly. Let's ride!
Oh, guys, I understand,
but like I said, Internet's down.
Phone's hooked to the Internet,
so that means phone is down too.
We're kind of in the
middle of nowhere here.
None of our phones have service.
There's gotta be someplace
nearby with cell reception.
- Sure, back in town.
- What town?
Pike's Hollow.
How do we get there?
It's too far to walk unless
you take the shortcut.
But my husband's coming
to pick me up in a bit,
if you want a ride.
Where's the shortcut?
Got it!
Tyrell Wellick, right?
That's how I know you.
But I never knew you
were on "Big Brother."
Holy smokes!
I cannot believe you are in my store.
Can I get a selfie?
No, I'm not him. You
have me confused, okay?
The shortcut, how do we get there?
Are you sure you're not Tyrell Wellick?
E Corp fella.
You are the spitting image of him.
Yes, I'm sure.
That's too bad.
Sure like to meet him one day.
Seems like a nice guy.
Jesus fucking Christ, woman!
Where is the shortcut? How
the fuck do we get to town?
Whoa, aren't you friggin' rude?
Directly across the street,
you'll see an opening to a trail,
and that will take you through
the woods for a stretch,
but be sure you veer left at the creek.
You'll find yourself in Pike's Hollow
in 30 minutes or so.
Fucking finally.
Wouldn't hurt you to learn
some manners on the walk.
_
This is the right trail, right?
The one across from the gas station.
There was only one.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
So quiet out here.
Have you ever considered leaving?
What do you mean?
Just walking off, disappearing,
leaving the life you're
living behind you,
all the bullshit, the stress, the pain,
everything?
You know, maybe start over
where no one knows you
and reinvent yourself
and forget about all the
mistakes you made in this life.
Find some peace.
Some rest.
I think about that.
Don't you?
No.
Any sign of the creek?
Well, maybe it's still up ahead.
Ah.
We've been walking for a while.
We shoulda come across it by now.
How do you know if we should
have come across it by now?
Because we've been
walking for fucking hours.
- That's how.
- Don't get mad at me.
I don't know where the goddamn creek is.
You were the one who took off this way.
Unbelievable... you're
blaming me that we're lost?
I blame you that we're even here.
- You said he was dead.
- He was.
Well, then how did he drive the van?
I don't fucking know!
All right, all right.
Let's all calm down.
Take it easy.
What was that? A dog?
Who knows?
We're in the middle of the woods.
Could be anything.
Maybe a coyote.
Or a wolf.
That.
You hear it?
Let's just keep going.
Maybe the creek is up ahead.
She knew my face.
What?
The cashier.
She knew my face.
So what?
That means she can ID me.
You search, you find, all is well.
But what if you search
and you don't find?
How long do you look?
Eventually, you've gotta give up, right?
Then what?
That thing you were searching
for, what becomes of it?
How could you ever know?
♪ Joey ♪
♪ Baby ♪
♪ Don't get crazy ♪
Big night tonight?
Uh, no.
I'm not the real Santa.
Yeah.
Sometimes I wish I were.
Sometimes I wish I were...
♪ I know you've heard it all before ♪
♪ So I don't say it anymore ♪
Where'd you go there, Tobias?
Oh, just thinking.
Jimmy.
Good guy.
Fell on some tough times.
You know how sometimes
the world just seems like
it's kicking you down
and you can't get up?
Christ, do I ever.
That's Jimmy.
And you know how it is.
Soon you're out in
the cold winter night,
asking a lot of questions,
looking at the world,
thinking about what it might
be like without you in it.
Do you have to do that?
- It's a Christmas song.
- It's annoying.
I just got it.
Why you wear that hoodie.
I've never seen you in anything else.
Black hoodie, black jeans, black shoes,
always the same.
I've been wondering this whole time,
but now I finally get it.
You don't care.
Sure, why not?
Silk tie,
$6,000 suit.
I mean, it sounds pathetic
to say aloud, but...
I actually care.
And you know what?
That's why I'm a failure.
My entire life, I've been an outsider,
worried what other people think of me,
how I can make them happy,
because I needed their
approval and their acceptance.
But you never cared.
The first day we met,
there we were, Allsafe's
most important clients
roaming through the office,
and you couldn't care less.
We're gonna die out here.
Maybe not tonight, but soon.
The Dark Army soldier,
he's likely reported back by now.
It's only a matter of
time before they find us.
Did you hear that?
If there's traffic, we
gotta be close to town.
- Hey!
Jesus Christ!
So what's with the getup
Mall Santa? Salvation Army?
Sloan Kettering.
It's a cancer center.
I do it for the kids.
Dude, that's dope.
You're definitely a
better person than me.
So what, the kids served spiked nog?
No, me and some of the other volunteers,
we got a little tradition
after visiting the hospital.
What's that?
We get drunk.
Nice tradition, I guess.
Yeah, you know the kids,
they love when we drop by.
So many smiling faces.
This might be the last
time I do it though.
You know, the thing
that really gets you?
Some of 'em are so small.
It's almost as if they
were just born to die.
Jesus.
No wonder you're plastered.
How else do you get through that?
Well, it was easier when
my wife went with me,
but...
since the accident...
What do you got there, Tobias?
Oh, I like to keep a nip or two on me
during the holidays.
I'm not talking about the booze.
Oh, Percocet.
Sometimes the... the
pain's just too much.
Alexa, play "slow jams" playlist.
Playing "slow jams" playlist.
So this is my apartment.
You know, when we were chatting,
I just imagined this super organized.
Well, I... I actually
did clean up earlier.
No, I like it.
♪ Maybe even you ♪
You want a drink?
I have one Tecate.
We can share.
♪ Recline complete ♪
♪ Dream too sweet ♪
♪ I can't do it not with you ♪
♪ Not even with you ♪
♪ Maybe never with you ♪
So my apartment being organized
was part of your fantasy in our chat?
Well, you know, just visualizing.
I guess that's the thing about IRC.
Everyone gets to imagine
exactly what they want.
♪ Total control ♪
Is that why you do it?
I like how I can control everything.
♪ Over you ♪
♪ Total control over you ♪
I have this fantasy that
I'm the only person from IRC
you've ever invited over.
♪ Over you ♪
♪ Total control over you ♪
You are.
♪ Street wet tonight ♪
Just...
let me just...
I'll be right back.
Okay.
♪ Maybe even you ♪
♪ Stay in bed ♪
♪ Stained sheets ♪
♪ My head hurts ♪
♪ I repeat ♪
Stop fighting so hard.
You're gonna lose
control faster that way.
Give into it.
Give up control.
Realize you'll never be free.
_
Um...
Tobias?
What's up?
Hold on now.
Whose car is that?
That was gonna be my question.
Hey.
That's my car.
Oh, I get it now.
Uh, you see, I didn't drive today.
Kenny drove.
- He picked me up at...
- Okay, Tobias.
If that is your car, whose car is this?
I have no clue.
Christmas, huh?
Good-bye, Tobias.
Good-bye is short and final.
Hey. Hey.
Hey.
Look,
I know it might not be my place, but...
I wanna help you.
You wanna help me?
I don't want you to hurt yourself.
Holy crow, what the heck
are you talking about?
What do you mean,
you're all sad and lonely
going on about Jimmy,
your suicidal "friend."
Jimmy Stewart.
"It's a Wonderful Life."
Christmas classic.
Tobias, you just told
me good-bye is final.
That is Steinbeck.
He's a national treasure. Read a book.
Okay, what about the pills?
Okay, you're drunk as shit and
you have a bottle of Percocet.
Explain that.
For my wife.
Your wife's dead.
My wife is dead?
Wait... you said she had an accident.
She threw her back out
when we were putting the
Santa on the roof yesterday.
She's in brutal pain.
She can barely move.
Doc wrote a prescription...
Okay, you fucking scared me.
- Hey, Dolly.
- Darlene.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay. Why wouldn't I be?
You wanna talk about it?
There's nothing to talk about.
You sure?
Yes.
All right.
Have a great night.
Fine.
I have lost absolutely everyone,
my boyfriend, my best
friend, my parents.
The only one I have left is my brother,
who is an asshole that
treats me like absolute shit.
But I'm really worried
about him right now,
and it pisses me off that I'm worried,
because I am always worried about him,
and he flat-out told me to fuck off.
So why do I bother?
I don't know.
I don't know, I'm afraid
this time it's different.
I'm afraid he might be dead.
Okay.
- Reception?
- No.
Time.
Just realizing it's Christmas.
- Can't be much further.
- To what?
Town.
Let's stop lying to ourselves.
We're nowhere near town.
We're completely lost.
- We just gotta keep moving.
- Why?
Even if we magically made it
to this Pike's Hollow place,
the town is gonna be
swarming with Dark Army.
- We've gotta try.
- You aren't listening to me.
Whatever we're walking
towards, it ends with death.
What are you doing?
There's a rock in my shoe.
You honestly don't
care about me, do you?
What are you talking about now?
Like why you wear that
same hoodie every day.
You don't care.
Did you ever care about me?
I mean, be honest, I can take it.
What is the point of this?
Just answer the question, did you?
Tyrell, you didn't make it easy...
- Just answer the question!
- No!
The sound of death.
It's just some stupid animal. Let's go.
- Go without me.
- What?
- You're giving up?
- Yeah.
I think so.
I can't deal with this shit anymore.
Come on.
You stay out here alone,
you can be sure it's game over.
You're better than this.
Yeah, maybe I was, but not anymore.
I'm going.
Yeah, go, Elliot.
- I will.
- Yeah, good.
'Cause you don't need
me. You never needed me.
That's the truth, right?
Yeah, that's the truth, I
never fucking needed you!
You were only in the way!
If it weren't for you...
The world would've been saved?
And you would have been the savior?
Is that what you think?
Is that the fantasy I ruined for you?
Stay here, die!
I don't give a fuck about you!
I'm done!
Good!
Look around you!
All signs lead to the
same hopeless destination,
and the sooner you
realize that, the better,
for you're so much in your own head
that you can't see the truth!
That it's over!
Seems like we're always
thinking of ourselves
when looking for something that's lost,
but we never think much about the lost,
whatever, whoever is unable to be found,
whether it's a set of keys
left somewhere and forgotten,
a couple of guys wandering
aimlessly in the woods,
or someone who's
disappeared inside himself.
What if that's what
they wanted all along?
Not to be found.
You're wrong.
I don't like being an outsider either.
Maybe I'm just good at hiding it.
Why'd you come back?
Why aren't you going?
I don't know.
I guess...
it felt wrong to leave you.
Besides,
I think you're the only person I know
that actually likes me.
You were right about one thing.
I've known that we're gonna die
since we walked out of that gas
station and the van was gone.
I don't think there's a
way out of this for us.
Why do you want to keep going?
My sister.
I have to warn her.
I have to at least try.
I got her into this miss.
Same as last time and
the time before that.
I've been a horrible brother.
I treated her like shit.
Least I can do
is call her and tell her to run.
Maybe she can still escape.
How much longer do you
think until they find us?
I don't know, man.
All right.
Let's keep moving.
Maybe you can still
make that phone call.
- Dolly.
- Dar... what?
I know you're worried
about your brother,
but you gotta worry about you too.
I'm trying.
And I hope he's not dead.
Merry Christmas.
Hi.
Ho, ho, ho.
Santa's home.
Fu...
Tyrell.
You okay?
Oh, Jesus Christ.
I'm okay.
We can't just leave him here.
Gotta get you to a hospital, man.
Fuck.
No... no hospital.
The Dark Army will find
me; they'll find you.
No... no, we gotta keep moving, man.
We'll find someplace that can help you.
No, I'm done.
Burn the van and all the evidence.
Make sure you take care of Whiterose.
Okay?
Tyrell.
I can't let you die.
I'm just gonna go for a walk.