‐ I'm a mercenary.
I don't play fair.
I would rather see you lose
than win myself.
‐ The Deus Group.
‐ We can take them all down.
‐ Just need
their phone numbers.
Get them all
in a room together.
‐ I'm resigning.
‐ We've been waiting for
Elliot Alderson's next move,
and this could be it.
‐ We will not wait for them
to make a mistake.
Arrange a Deus Group meeting
to confirm a successor...
Wellick.
‐ Make sure you take care
of Whiterose.
‐ We got the access we needed
to transfer the money
from the bank's site.
We can rob them blind.
‐ This is all my fault.
‐ You want to help me?
Go find Elliot,
and take them down.
‐ I own everything.
Every bribe,
blackmail, extortion‐‐
everything will go public.
‐ Mr. Alderson,
he's too much of a liability.
‐ If we kill him, his shipping
hack dies with him.
It's time he learns
we're on the same side.
‐ See? They all came back.
Everyone's okay again.
‐ Angela, whatever Whiterose
told you is a lie.
‐ I know it's possible.
I've seen it.
‐ I don't know if I can go
through with the hack anymore.
‐ Look at me.
I am not the one
Darlene talked to.
‐ You shouldn't be
sitting there.
That's not your seat.
‐ Why?
‐ They're not ready yet,
so we need to wait.
‐ How is he?
‐ It's not going
to happen today.
There's no point
in waiting here now.
‐ We aren't going anywhere.
You know where he is.
You need to bring him here.
‐ It's not that simple.
We're gonna have to help him
through this.
‐ Mom.
Maybe we should just
tell him now...
About everything.
Then Elliot will be okay.
Right?
‐
I'm telling you.
He's not ready.
‐ When will he be ready?
You've let this
go on far too long.
‐ It's a little more
complicated than that.
I didn't know
everything that was happening.
‐ That's a lie.
You've been part of these
shenanigans from the beginning.
You encourage it.
‐ Okay, okay.
Just stop.
Yes, I'll admit it.
I did.
I never thought
he'd take things this far.
There's nothing I can do now.
‐ Just talk to him.
‐ We have to finish
his mission.
Once the hack is done,
maybe then
I can get through to him.
‐ And how are you
gonna do that?
‐ I'm gonna show him
what he did.
‐ And if it doesn't work?
‐
We can't go on like this.
And that poor boy.
We may lose him forever.
For God's sake,
he hasn't woken up since‐‐
‐ That's not true.
Darlene.
She said they talked
two months ago.
He woke up for her...
Which means she might be
the one who could help us.
‐ Great. You decided to show.
‐ I know.
You weren't expecting me.
But I'm here for Elliot,
same as you.
What can you expect
after what happened?
Life throws you
an error code like that,
you don't have the luxury of
a fucking pop‐up explanation.
So what are you
supposed to do?
Move on without answers,
or stay down and drive
yourself crazy with questions?
That's where Elliot is‐‐
mired in conflict.
And that's why I'm here.
How we doing?
‐ Got line of sight on the IMSI
catcher to the front door.
Deus members
should be arriving soon.
Where the fuck have you been?
‐ Got held up.
‐ What kind of answer is that?
You had me worried.
I told you the Dark Army
is looking for you.
‐ The day didn't go
exactly as planned.
Cut me some slack, okay?
Things went a little sideways.
‐ Oh. Really?
Is that so?
Things went a little sideways
for you, huh?
You want to hear about
the fucking night I've had?
‐ This isn't a pissing contest,
sweetheart.
Let's just get back to work.
What the fuck are you doing?
‐ Why are you here?
Where is he?
‐
You don't want him
here right now.
‐ Why the fuck not?
‐ He just can't.
Not now.
‐ What happened to him?
‐ He'll be fine.
He just needs some time.
‐ I don't trust you.
‐ I don't need you to trust me.
I just need you
to help me pull this off.
‐ Tell me what's going on,
or I'm walking.
‐ I can't.
He needs to be
the one to tell you...
when he's ready.
What the fuck
are you doing here?
Do you realize
how risky this is?
What if someone saw you?
She's with me.
Out with it.
Why are you here?
You're supposed to be
across the street
with your Deus pals.
‐ There's one last thing
I need from you.
‐ Well, it's a little late in
the game to be making demands.
‐ It's‐‐
it's not a demand.
It's a favor.
‐ Given the danger you've put
us all in just by being here,
I hope it's worth it.
‐ It is.
‐ What's this?
‐ I want you to destroy
Whiterose's machine.
Everything you need to know
about her project,
it's on here.
Promise me.
‐ After tonight,
she'll be ruined.
Why is this important to you?
‐ Because it was
important to Angela.
It's what she wanted.
‐ Okay.
I promise.
Remember,
you gotta keep everyone there
until we grab
their phone numbers.
Don't let anyone leave,
especially Whiterose.
‐ What was that about?
Hey.
What the hell does
Price know about Angela?
What is going on?
‐ I'll fill you in,
but right now,
we gotta get started.
We're already behind.
In order to rob
the Deus Group blind,
we need to get access
to transfer funds
from Cyprus National Bank.
To do that, we need every
Deus asshole's phone number.
Why?
Because Darlene can then match
each of those phone numbers
to its corresponding Cyprus
National Bank account number
and initiate a transfer.
Once she initiates
the transfer,
it'll trigger
a security 2FA code
that'll be texted to every
Deus dickhead's phone.
Then Darlene will run a script
to automatically grab
those 2FA codes,
and transfer all their money
before they have time
to stop it.
So, yeah, I'm worried.
For what, though,
I'm not sure.
But whatever it is...
It's coming.
‐ I can't believe Angela never
told me Price was her father.
‐ Maybe she didn't know.
‐ I miss her.
‐
Darlene, I‐‐
‐ No, I don't want
to talk about it.
I just...
I just wanted to say that.
‐ Okay.
Something's not right.
No one's gone in or out
of that building
other than Price.
‐ Wait,
you think they're onto us?
‐ I don't know.
‐ I see I'm the first
to arrive.
‐ Technically, I was first.
‐ You want to tell me
what's going on?
‐ I thought we'd start
with a drink.
‐ I'm an old man, Zhang.
I gave up on foreplay long ago.
Let's just skip
ahead to the part
where you try to fuck me.
‐ If they are onto us,
if the Deus Group
doesn't show,
everything's we've been
working on
will be a big fucking fail.
If Elliot were here,
what would he do?
He'd look for abnormalities,
incompatibilities,
anything that isn't adding up,
any conflicts.
‐ What are you doing?
‐ Looking.
‐ For?
‐ I don't know yet.
Elliot saved an image
of Tyrell's phone,
swiped all his credentials.
If Whiterose thought
something was up,
she would've told
the other members,
including the guy
she was having the meeting for.
‐ All you had to do
was nothing,
just sit idly by and wait
for the new year to arrive,
but you couldn't leave
well enough alone.
I wanted to let you live
into retirement‐‐
I planned on it‐‐
as a gift of sorts.
I guess you can say
I always get
swept up when it comes
to the holidays.
But then you had to be naughty.
‐ Come on, Zhang.
You know I've never been
the nice type.
‐ Let me drive.
Maybe his calendar.
‐ After your
abrupt resignation
and Mr. Alderson's
curious disappearance,
it wasn't hard to figure out
that you two
were working together.
Tell me Mr. Alderson's plan,
and these gentlemen
will take you home
and inject you with maitotoxin.
You will die in your sleep.
The papers will say
you passed from heart failure.
Sad, but painless.
Or, we could go the other way.
You're well aware
of our methods.
‐ So you canceled
the Deus Group meeting
based on this half‐cocked
conspiracy theory of yours.
This last‐minute change will
not sit well with the others.
‐ Downtown near Wall Street.
Hey, are you hearing this?
Let's move.
We gotta go.
Do‐or‐die time.
They're probably
already inside,
which means
we'll have to find a way in
to get a line of sight.
‐ Price didn't know
about the venue change.
‐ So what?
‐ Why didn't they tell him?
‐ I don't know.
He's persona non grata
on his way out.
Who gives a shit?
‐ Why the heavy
security detail?
Price is one guy.
If they wanted
to get rid of him,
they don't need a team
of Dark Army soldiers to do it.
They're not there
to kill Price.
They're there
to protect someone.
‐ The meeting is taking place
as we speak.
I'm sure Mr. Wellick,
the new CEO of E Corp,
is impressing everyone
with his smile.
Unfortunately,
I'll be uncharacteristically
late for the gathering,
but I'm sure
they'll understand.
‐ Will they?
Hmm.
I'd expect mutiny
when they realize
that Tyrell Wellick,
your guest of honor
and the sole purpose
for the meeting,
will not be in attendance.
‐ I'm gonna stay.
‐ What?
‐ You have the exploit
to verify the phone numbers
ready to go.
‐ No, we can't split up.
What if something else
goes wrong with the plan?
‐ You know,
it just occurred to me.
We've never gotten
drunk together, have we?
I think this might
be a good night to start.
What do you think?
‐ The plan is pointless
if we don't get Whiterose, too.
She's gotta be in there.
I have to stay.
‐ That makes no sense.
We only have one IMSI capture.
We need to do this together.
‐ We don't have a choice.
Now go.
‐ Mr. Wellick
is nowhere to be found.
We're still searching
the tri‐state area‐‐
‐ A waste of time.
Stop.
Tell them all to stop.
Is this part of your plan?
Mr. Wellick's
mysterious disappearance?
What did you do to him?
‐ Truthfully...
I have no idea
where Wellick is.
He may be dead.
Mm.
No, no, no.
Now I think of it,
he did mention
something about
wanting to travel
the great southwest
in a '65 El Camino convertible,
wind in his hair...
‐ He's beaten you!
You lost today.
Doesn't mean
we can't fight back tomorrow,
but right now,
we have to leave
and warn the Deus Group
before this gets worse.
‐ We are not going anywhere.
‐ If you won't
listen to reason,
then I'm done.
‐ Whoa.
It's bad management
when your best employees
either walk off the job,
or blow their brains out.
‐ Fuck am I gonna
get in there?
‐ Perimeter is secure.
Make sure
these doors stay locked
the rest of the evening.
‐ Goddamn. Christmas Day?
This better be good.
‐ Yeah, he's a dickwad,
but a total and complete
shutdown of Muslims
entering the United States...
‐ That runaround for
tonight's location details...
‐ Iraq's a proper mess.
Deus needs to get
its giant dick
out of that sand
sooner than later.
‐ Rousseff is fucked.
He did it to himself.
Or was that us?
‐ How are you, my friend?
‐ Just came off an 11‐hour
flight on Christmas Day.
‐ Ah.
‐ My wife is furious.
And my girlfriend?
She won't return
my phone calls.
Whatever Zhang
has planned better be good.
‐ Couldn't agree more.
‐ Evening, gentlemen.
Hors d'oeuvres?
‐ Speaking of,
where is our host?
‐ Back inside.
This entrance
is off limits tonight.
Go.
‐ There's no fucking way.
‐ Well?
Who is it?
Hello?
‐ That sure as hell
doesn't sound like Price.
‐ Mr. Alderson.
It's good to hear your voice.
I was hoping
we could talk in person.
‐ You once told me that we'd
never see each other again.
What makes you
want to see me now?
‐ Call it a change of mind.
A realization.
‐ Nah.
If I'm hearing your voice
on the other end of this call,
I'm good.
‐ And what does that mean?
‐ You'll know soon enough.
‐ A proposal.
You stop whatever it is
you're planning,
and I give you information
that will prove to be
very valuable to you.
‐ You think
I'm gonna trust you?
‐ Let me earn your trust
by sharing first.
It is about your friend...
Angela.
‐ What about her?
‐ You see, Elliot...
You think Angela's dead,
but she's not.
‐ You sent me a picture
of her dead body,
you sick fucking fuck.
‐ And you believe
what most people believe?
Only what is right
in front of you?
I expected more from you.
‐ You think I'm gonna believe
this bullshit?
You killed her.
Angela's dead.
‐ No, Elliot.
Angela's alive.
And if you allow me,
I can take you to her.
Would you like that, Elliot?
Would you like
to see Angela again?
To hear her voice?
To hold her hand?
Elliot, are you there?
‐ Yes.
‐ I know you have regrets,
Elliot,
and pain.
I know there are things
in your life
you wish were different,
just the same as Angela,
and I can show you a way that
you can make it all go away,
just as I did for her.
You can reset everything
and live in the world
you deserve,
a world without
all the pain you're carrying,
without your past,
without your regrets.
Please, Elliot.
Let me show you the world
that I showed
your closest friend.
‐ I saw what you did to her
before you killed her.
That wasn't Angela.
You used her.
You turned her
into someone else.
‐ Then don't take
my word for it.
Ask her yourself.
Elliot,
we don't have to fight
like this anymore.
Let's finally make peace
with each other,
as we were always meant to do.
Let go of the anger
and the hatred
you've built up towards me.
Understand I've only
wished to help.
‐ Here's the thing.
I don't need help right now.
You do.
‐ Good evening,
people of Earth.
We are fsociety.
We have risen from the ashes
to bring you
a Christmas miracle,
a miracle that will finally
reveal our true nemesis.
The secret club running
the world is the Deus Group,
a clandestine collection
of the world's richest
and most powerful people.
Deus Group, we know you,
and we know what you do.
And tonight, the whole world
will learn about you.
Most of you watching
have never heard
the name Deus Group.
That's because they've worked
hard to keep it that way.
To begin to understand
their reach,
to see the evil crimes
they're responsible for,
click on the link below
to download
all their private files.
And if you'd like to meet
the despicable individuals
who have co‐opted your lives
for profit,
come meet them now in person
while they wine and dine
at Cipriani.
I am sure
they'd appreciate the visit.
Deus Group,
you have been owned.
Fsociety and the world
will cheer
as we watch your black hearts
stop beating.
This is not a warning.
This is the beginning
of the end.
We are fsociety.
‐
‐ Hey.
‐ Did you see the video?
‐ Yeah.
‐ Hopefully,
that'll do the trick
to smoke these fuckers out.
Did you find Whiterose?
‐ Yeah.
I talked to her.
‐ You what?
Jesus Christ.
You were supposed
to hack her phone,
not call it.
‐ It was only for a second.
But it was Price's phone,
so we still need
to get Whiterose's number.
‐ Are you okay?
‐ I don't know.
I don't know anymore.
‐ Hey, Elliot?
I'm glad you're back.
‐ I gotta go.
‐ What happened?
‐ There's a cell tower.
If I can see traffic
on that tower‐‐
‐ No, I mean‐‐
‐ We can't get past her
security and into the hotel.
We need her phone number.
‐ Hey.
Are you gonna be okay?
‐ Only way this works
is if we hit their accounts
at the same time.
If the other members
get the 2FA codes first,
they'll alert Whiterose.
Just keep them
in your line of sight.
I'll let you know
when I've got it.
‐ Sergey,
you have to trust me.
We will get through this.
Everything will be all right.
Oh, don't listen
to that Mason.
The man is an absolute buffoon.
No, no, don't leave.
Don't go outside.
Tell everyone to remain,
Sergey.
Sergey?
Hello?
So that's it.
So that's your big move!
You think that I can't survive
being doxxed?
‐ I have no idea.
I'm as curious as you.
‐ Hello?
‐
‐ Come on!
‐ I can't do anything about it.
Look. It's not working.
Obviously, it's not working.
Shit.
‐ Private event tonight.
You can't be here.
Everyone, back it up.
‐ A short time ago,
fsociety resurfaced
with a new video,
and while the contents
of that video remain
largely unconfirmed,
it focuses entirely
on an international
investment firm,
the Deus Group.
It's a collection of powerful
men whom fsociety claims
to be guilty
of international crimes,
and as you can see behind me,
onlookers have gathered
with hopes
of catching a glimpse
of any Deus Group members.
‐ Just got into
the cell tower.
‐ All this over a little
pipsqueak in a hoodie.
‐ Where are we at, kiddo?
‐ I've got a bunch of numbers.
I just can't tell
if any of them are hers.
‐ Truth be told,
I never liked Mr. Alderson‐‐
his anxious demeanor,
his juvenile anger.
But...
he does bring
something to the table‐‐
well, for me.
‐ Mr. Alderson
is the only person I believe
actually able to hurt you...
Truly hurt you.
And clearly,
you believe it, too.
‐ Come on.
‐ Why do we have to cut these
things so goddamn close?
‐ What are you doing?
‐ Peaceful out here.
Cold winter air.
‐ Are you really going to make
me force you into the car?
‐ You know, I almost
let myself believe you...
When you said Angela
was still alive.
I know what kind of conman
you are,
how you operate.
Even though I saw your men
drag her dead body away,
I still wanted to believe
what you were saying.
When you spoke
to Mr. Alderson,
I felt the power
of your promise.
And all I could think is,
well...
maybe that's what my daughter
thought when you came to her.
The desperation to have
all her pain go away,
to have her past rewritten‐‐
and that's why it works, right?
The one thing
every person has:
regret.
You weaponize that,
and then you use that weapon
against them
to destroy them.
But here's the thing
I've realized as of late.
With Angela‐‐
didn't work.
Angela lives on
in the lives
of the people who love her.
And that love...
that love fuels
their unwavering resolve
to turn the tables
to destroy you.
You just remember, Zhang.
You did all this to yourself.
‐ You should take
your own advice, Phillip.
Accept your truth.
It's over.
‐ Yeah.
Yes.
I suppose it is.
‐ It happened.
It actually happened.
‐ What?
‐ Something wrong, old sport?
‐ What is this?
‐ Well,
if it's what I think it is,
we're all broke.
‐ No.
That's impossible.
‐ Apparently not.
‐ Where is it, Phillip?
Where is my fucking money?
‐ Gone.
‐ No.
‐ I warned you.
I told you long ago.
I'm a mercenary.
I'd rather see you lose
than win myself.
‐ That can't be.
‐ Finally.
I found a way to take
what's most important to you.
‐ No, no.
‐ Your project,
your dream
of another world‐‐
it's as good as dead.
Think of it this way, Zhang.
You didn't lose the game.
You just ran out of time.
‐
‐ And like that...
Rome falls.
No more Deus Group.
No more top 1% of the top 1%.
No more controlling
every piece of our lives.
No more playing God
without permission.
We took them down.
All of them.
‐ FBI.
Open the door.
We have a warrant.
Minister Zhang,
we have a warrant.
FBI.
Open the door.
Minister Zhang,
come out.
We have a warrant
for your arrest.
Minister Zhang.
Minister Zhang,
we're coming in.
Three, two, one,
execute, execute, execute.