- Get in.
- What about him?
He's dead.
- Krista.
- Leave me alone.
She our girl.
She knows something I gotta know.
We are very pleased that
you are back to work.
Let us know if there's
anything you need,
and we'll do the same.
He's an Irish mobster
out of Hell's Kitchen.
If I can find a way
to rob the Deus Group,
Whiterose loses everything.
I got into Olivia's Cyprus
National Bank account.
I can see all the Deus account numbers,
but she's not authorized
to transfer anything,
which means we are gonna have
to break into Virtual Realty
and get on their servers.
Schedule the meeting for tomorrow.
There's no way we'll be
able to get the Deus Group
together so quickly.
I have lost everyone.
The only one I have left is my brother,
who treats me like absolute shit,
but I'm really worried
about him right now.
I'm afraid he might be dead.
Tyrell.
Burn the van and all the evidence.
It's cool, dude.
We don't have to talk.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
♪ Freude, schöner Götterfunken ♪
♪ Tochter aus Elysium ♪
♪ Wir betreten feuertrunken ♪
♪ Was die Mode Schwert geteilt ♪
♪ Alle Menschen werden Brüder ♪
- _
- ♪ Deine Zauber binden wieder ♪
- ♪ Was die Mode Schwert geteilt ♪
♪ Alle Menschen werden Brüder ♪
- _
- ♪ Wo dein sanfter Flügel weilt ♪
_
♪ It's time for mistletoe and holly ♪
♪ Fancy ties and granny's pies ♪
- _
- ♪ And folks stealing a kiss or two ♪
♪ As they whisper, "Merry
Christmas" to you ♪
♪ Then comes that big night ♪
♪ You'll hear voices by starlight ♪
♪ Singing a Yuletide hymn ♪
♪ Oh, by gosh, by golly ♪
♪ It's time for mistletoe and holly ♪
♪ Fancy ties and granny's pies ♪
♪ And folks stealing a kiss or two ♪
- _
- ♪ As they whisper, "Merry Christmas" to ♪
♪ You know I'm all about that bass ♪
♪ 'Bout that bass, no treble ♪
♪ I'm all about that bass ♪
♪ Said the night wind
to the little lamb ♪
♪ Do you hear what I hear? ♪
♪ A song, a song ♪
♪ High above the trees ♪
♪ With a voice as big as the sea ♪
♪ You know I'm all about that bass ♪
♪ 'Bout that bass, no treble ♪
♪ I'm all about that bass ♪
♪ 'Bout that bass ♪
♪ Because you know I'm
all about that bass ♪
♪ 'Bout that bass, no treble ♪
♪ I'm all about that bass ♪
♪ 'Bout that bass ♪
♪ Because you know I'm
all about that bass ♪
♪ 'Bout that... ♪
_
♪ Old Mr. Kringle is soon gonna jingle ♪
♪ The bells that'll tinkle
all your troubles away ♪
♪ Everybody's waiting for
the man with the bag ♪
♪ 'Cause Christmas is coming again ♪
♪ He's got a sleigh full,
it's not gonna stay full ♪
♪ He's got stuff to drop
at every stop of the way ♪
♪ Everybody's waiting for
the man with the bag ♪
♪ 'Cause Christmas is coming again ♪
♪ Silent Night ♪
♪ Holy night ♪
♪ All is calm ♪
♪ All is bright ♪
♪ Round yon Virgin ♪
♪ Mother and Child ♪
♪ Holy infant so tender and mild ♪
♪ Sleep in heavenly peace ♪
_
♪ Silent Night ♪
It's time we talked.