What if I told you we could make it
like none of this ever happened?
What would you be willing
to sacrifice for that?
You wanna know what I believe?
That this isn't the end.
That there's another world
out there for both of us.
And we'll see each other again.
You think Angela's dead, but she's not.
Elliot, I can't wait
to marry you tomorrow.
You can reset everything
and live in the world you deserve,
a world without your past...
Do you recall a time
your father ever hurt you?
- Yes.
- Without all the pain you carry...
Just finishing up a call.
- Be out in a jiff.
- Without your regrets...
"From the Mixed-Up Files
of Basil E. Frankweiler."
Your parents in town yet?
Hello, Emily? You there?
A 5.9-magnitude tremor
struck Washington Township.
I've imagined what it would be like
to be someone with a more exciting life.
Will you believe with me?
[DOOR SLAMS]
- Who are you?
- [HUMMING]
Can you tell me what
happened to that house?
Can you tell me what's your monster?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[GLASS SHATTERS]
It's Mom. She's gone.
She was an asshole to us.
I need to go back to
Washington Township.
- [ALARM BLARING]
- But soon you will see.
We will be reborn as new.
This place is gonna blow!
If we don't stop this,
the meltdown will destroy the whole town.
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
[POWER WHIRS DOWN]
Did it work?
[EXPLOSION]
Hello, friend.
Wait, you can hear me again?
Have you been there this whole time?
I was so focused on the hack
that I guess I thought you were gone.
But after what just
happened at the plant,
I thought for sure I was gone too.
We're dead, right?
There's no way we survived.
But if we're dead...
then how am I talking to you?
And if you're here...
where's Mr. Robot?
[RUMBLING]
[BIRDS CAWING]
What was that?
You felt that too, right?
It was like an earthquake.
Wait.
I'm not dead.
I'm alive.
Which means you are too, right?
Where are we?
[SOMBER MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Yeah, I'm thinking the same thing.
This looks exactly like
where the power plant was,
except...
♪ ♪
It's not.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
I know what you're thinking, but don't.
That's impossible.
Whiterose is out of her fucking mind.
Yeah, yeah, I know. So am I.
But still, there's no way
her machine worked, right?
[STYX'S "MR. ROBOTO"]
♪ ♪
♪ Domo arigato, Mr. Roboto ♪
♪ Domo arigato, Mr.
Roboto, mata au hi made ♪
♪ Domo arigato, Mr. Roboto,
himitsu wo shiri ta ♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
♪ You're wondering who I am ♪
♪ Secret, secret, I've got a secret ♪
♪ Machine or mannequin ♪
♪ With parts made in Japan ♪
♪ Secret, secret, I've got a secret ♪
♪ I am the modern man ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I've got a secret ♪
♪ I've been hiding under my skin ♪
♪ My heart is human ♪
♪ My blood is boiling ♪
♪ My brain IBM ♪
[TIRES SCREECHING, HORN HONKS]
♪ So if you see me acting strangely ♪
♪ Don't be surprised ♪
♪ I'm just a man who needed someone ♪
♪ And somewhere to hide ♪
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
It can't be.
How?
It's been gone for 20 years, ever since...
He died.
♪ ♪
[DOOR BELL JINGLES]
[MUFFLED] Just finishing up a call.
Be out in a jiff.
♪ ♪
Tell me you heard that too.
Can this really be happening?
♪ ♪
Is it...
is it really...
him?
♪ ♪
[MUFFLED] I got a customer.
We still on for lunch?
♪ ♪
Okay.
See ya soon.
♪ ♪
No problem. I'm always here for you.
My monster is still alive.
Sorry for the wait.
- [DOOR BELL JINGLES]
- How can I help you?
Hmm.
Oh, there you are.
[SIGHS]
[LOCK CLICKS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Hey.
Hey!
Hi, honey! How was your day?
[MUFFLED] Dad's home!
This is my old neighborhood.
That's my old house, but who's in there?
Who's he talking to?
- [BELL DINGS]
- Yo, can I ask you a question?
Hey, Elliot.
You know who I am?
Duh, you live right there.
Where have you been?
I haven't seen you in a while.
You look different.
Okay, okay, I'll pick it
up when I get to the city.
Back before dinner!
[CAR DOOR CLICKS SHUT,
ENGINE TURNS OVER]
Your nose is bleeding.
[SNIFFLES]
If she knows who I am, maybe she knows.
I need your help.
I'm looking for Darlene.
Do you know where she is?
Who's Darlene?
My sister.
[CHUCKLES]
What's so funny?
You don't have a sister.
Elliot?
I wasn't expecting to
see you until tomorrow.
Hi, Mrs. Alderson.
Bye, Mrs. Alderson.
[HUMMING]
[EERIE MUSIC]
Well, why are you still standing
across the street there looking at me?
[CHUCKLES]
Stop being funny and come over here.
♪ ♪
You just missed your father.
He went up to the city.
Let me look at you.
♪ ♪
[SIGHS]
Have you lost weight?
You're too skinny.
Come on, let's scrounge
some lunch up for you.
♪ ♪
I can't wait to show
you the new curtains.
I know, I know, you don't care,
but trust me on this,
you'll notice the difference.
♪ ♪
This does look different.
Told you!
Only took me 30 years
to get around to it.
When I saw them, I
knew I had to have them.
Hmm.
Crazy how one small change can
make an entire place feel new.
[HAUNTING MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[DISHES CLINKING]
Okay, so I can make you
one of my special delicious sandwiches.
Do you want turkey or ham?
♪ ♪
No Darlene.
Who's Darlene?
♪ ♪
Anyway, I thought you
had a presentation today,
or was that yesterday?
How'd it go?
I'm not sure.
You've always been your
own harshest critic.
I'm sure you did great.
♪ ♪
This doesn't sound like my mom.
This sounds like someone
who loves their son.
Everything's changed.
Even...
Me.
What was that, honey? You, what?
♪ ♪
If their past has changed...
Has mine?
Does that mean...
The window.
What window?
♪ ♪
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Elliot?
What's gotten into you?
Where's my bedroom?
It was right here.
Are you all right?
My bedroom. Where is it?
Where it's always been.
[PANTING]
No.
This can't be true.
What can't be true?
When I was eight years old,
do you remember me having an accident?
What accident?
When I broke my arm.
Honey, you've never broken your arm.
You've never broken a
bone in your entire life.
Elliot...
I'm worried about you.
Why don't we sit down?
If I didn't jump,
does that mean there was no reason to?
Mom...
Just tell me.
Did you ever hurt me?
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Did...
Dad?
♪ ♪
Elliot...
your father and I
never, ever hurt you.
♪ ♪
We love you...
more than anything.
♪ ♪
Where's all this coming from?
Did something happen
between you and Angela?
Is this about her parents?
I don't mean to overstep,
but I know they've had
their ups and downs,
and if you two think
you're gonna end up like...
Angela?
♪ ♪
She's...
Alive?
It's totally normal to be nervous
before your big day tomorrow.
My big day?
I know the stress of a wedding can be
taxing for a couple...
Wedding?
I'm marrying Angela?
Mom?
Where is Angela right now?
Unless she decided to
become a runaway bride,
she must be back in her
apartment in the city.
[DYNAMIC ELECTRONIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
What do you think?
Do you buy any of this?
We started out wanting
to change the world,
but did it happen?
Is this the world I fought so hard for?
A world free of all the
pain I went through?
Am I actually considering
that this could be real?
♪ ♪
No. I won't let myself.
Not yet.
Not until I see Angela.
♪ ♪
Then I'll know.
If I see her, will this
world make more sense
or less?
♪ ♪
I don't know, but it's worth the risk.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
♪ ♪
Mr. Alderson.
Oh, scared, huh?
Well, you should be.
After all, as far as you're concerned,
I am evil incarnate.
Phillip, stop giving
him such a hard time.
Oh, come on, Em, he knows
I'm only joshing him.
Besides, if I'm to be his father-in-law,
he should be a little frightened of me.
- Sweetie, come on in.
- [CHUCKLES]
Come on.
We came up a few days
early to help Angela out
with a few last-minute adjustments,
but when we got here, as usual,
she's done everything herself,
so we've got nothing to do.
Don't be fooled.
She's bitter about
that, so tread carefully.
She is amazing that way, isn't she?
She always has been, I guess.
Oh, and wait until you
see her in her dress.
Okay.
Well, yes.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Anyway, to... to what
do we owe the honor?
Was Angela expecting you?
No. I, uh...
Just wanted to see her.
Wow, you two really can't go a minute
without missing each other.
So sweet.
I remember that feeling, I think.
And that is usually my cue
to make everyone a drink.
Uh, that won't be necessary.
I'm just trying to find Angela.
Oh, well, she's meeting us for lunch.
- She is?
- Yes.
We're trying that cute
place on the corner.
You should come.
Phillip, I want Elliot to come along.
Only after we've had one
of my whiskey sours, hmm?
Only one. I don't wanna be late.
You know, Elliot,
I am so happy to see the two
of you finally tie the knot.
Watching you grow up,
I always knew there was
something very special
between the two of you,
but, frankly, I was
worried she wouldn't see it.
Between us, she didn't always
have the best taste in men.
Yeah, I know.
[CHUCKLES]
But this is the start of something new.
Are you excited?
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Oh, shoot.
That was meant to be a surprise.
♪ ♪
We borrowed all of
these from your mother.
Angela wanted to give something to you,
something that embodied
your whole story together.
I think she did a wonderful job.
I just love...
These images,
I've seen them before.
I've pictured this fantasy so many times.
This is what normal people
do when they're happy, right?
Get married, start a family,
surround themselves
with people they love,
with people that love them.
Trust me, Em, we got lucky.
He's good, this one.
True love prevails.
Ever since he retired, he
has become quite the softy.
You know, I know I'm not
supposed to say anything,
but when your father came
by and showed us that gift
that you got for her...
she's gonna love it.
Oh, don't worry. It's just between us.
I am a vault, and he
cannot remember anything
past the last five minutes.
Bottoms up!
[GLASSES CLINK]
[CHUCKLES]
Mm!
We should get going.
I don't wanna be late.
- Mmm, it's good.
- [CELL PHONE BUZZING]
Oh, well, this is weird.
Elliot, it says that you're calling me.
No, don't... don't...
don't fall for it, Em.
He's... he's just doing
a gag with the phone.
- Am I right?
- [CHUCKLES]
Oh, he's such a whiz with these gadgets.
What's the trick, huh?
What happens if you pick up?
What?
What happens if you answer?
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC]
[BUZZING CONTINUES]
Uh, here. Let me do it.
N-no. Let me... let me do it.
[BUZZING CONTINUES]
♪ ♪
Hello?
Emily?
You there?
♪ ♪
Are you all right?
What happened, dear?
[HAUNTING MUSIC]
Look at what you did.
He's getting cold feet.
Well, how exactly am
I responsible for that?
Because of your
passive-aggressive jokes.
- [RUMBLING]
- Whoa!
Oh, my God!
Okay, nobody panic.
It's just a little
accident. I've got it.
[WINCES]
Ouch!
Ow.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
That voice, that was mine.
How can that be possible?
I saw myself in those pictures.
That was me, wasn't it?
Or no, was it him?
So are there two of me?
I didn't think about that before,
but that's possible, isn't it?
Everyone's different here:
Price, my dad, my mom...
[KEYS JINGLING]
♪ ♪
Me.
[LOCK CLICKS]
♪ ♪
But if this world isn't mine...
Then whose is it?
♪ ♪
This guy is definitely not me.
And I am definitely not him.
[DYNAMIC ELECTRONIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
I need to find out exactly who he is.
Shit, the boot drive is encrypted.
Maybe he's more like me than I thought.
[KEYS CLACKING]
♪ ♪
[CLACKING INTENSIFIES]
Based on this, he doesn't
have crippling social anxiety
or paranoia.
He looks like he's fun at parties,
makes a good living,
has lots of friends.
♪ ♪
Everything in his life seems perfect.
[KEYS CLACKING]
But nobody is as perfect as they seem.
♪ ♪
Come on, come on, come on.
I know I'll find something.
He can't be this happy.
No one is.
Haven't you been paying attention?
Everyone has a secret.
People are always hiding something:
their vulnerabilities,
their fears, their shame.
I don't care how happy he looks.
Everyone has a monster.
The question is, what's his?
♪ ♪
And there it is,
a hidden partition,
a drive full of files he
doesn't want anyone to see.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
These are images...
Of me...
♪ ♪
My life.
How does he know about me?
Did he somehow hack...
my world?
♪ ♪
Am I... his monster?
[DOOR CLICKS OPEN, SLAMS]
Who are you?
I know this is fucked up.
What are you doing in my apartment?
And why do you look like me?
I think we should talk.
I'm calling the police.
I don't know who you
are or what you want.
No, we can't involve the cops.
Stay where you are!
You're making a mistake.
Let's just take a seat.
I promise you, I can explain.
My name is Elliot Alderson.
I was born in Washington
Township, New Jersey,
September 17, 1986.
Same as you.
You could've looked all that up.
Look at me, man.
You really think I'm making this up?
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Let's sit.
I'm good where I am.
Start talking.
♪ ♪
Why do you have those
sketches on your computer?
♪ ♪
What sketches?
The hidden partition.
♪ ♪
How did you get in there?
Doesn't matter.
I need you to tell me why
you made those sketches.
♪ ♪
Hey, you look exactly like...
Holy shit, how is this happening?
♪ ♪
That's what I'm trying to figure out.
That's why we need to talk.
♪ ♪
The files on your hidden partition...
What are they?
♪ ♪
Sometimes when I get bored,
I create people in my head...
♪ ♪
Like him.
You know, someone with
a more exciting life.
Like a superhero,
except his power would be computers.
He'd a cybersecurity engineer by day,
vigilante hacker by night.
♪ ♪
Is that what you are?
What about the girl with the brown hair?
♪ ♪
She's just sort of like
his partner in crime.
♪ ♪
And fsociety?
That's just a dumb name I came up with
for a hacker group.
♪ ♪
You know...
fuck society?
♪ ♪
I figured that's...
what an anarchist hacker
would come up with.
♪ ♪
This is you, isn't it?
Why did you create this person?
♪ ♪
I guess...
Sometimes I fantasize about being him.
♪ ♪
So you want to be him?
No, not really.
Look at him.
♪ ♪
He's angry.
He has no life.
♪ ♪
He's alone.
He's not normal.
♪ ♪
Oh, shit, man.
I'm sorry.
♪ ♪
He shouldn't be.
He's right.
I'm not normal, and I never will be,
no matter what world I'm in.
What is that?
♪ ♪
Did you hear that?
What?
♪ ♪
It sounded like you
were talking to someone.
Shit, he can hear us.
There it is again.
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
♪ ♪
How are you doing that?
This was a mistake.
I don't belong here.
- I was stupid to think that I did.
- Wait.
[RUMBLING]
[OBJECTS CLATTERING]
[CAR HORN HONKING, ALARM BLARING]
Yo, man.
Are you okay?
Say something.
Shit. [BREATHING SHAKILY]
Fuck.
I-I'm gonna go get some help.
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
[BUZZING STOPS]
Hello?
Oh, my God, Elliot.
What have you done?
- Angela.
- You are out of control.
- The book.
- What?
How were you able to find it?
You're so amazing.
This is the best gift
anyone's ever given me.
Wait. H-hold on a second.
Seriously, Elliot,
I'm so lucky to be
marrying someone like you.
Angela...
I'm not who you think I am.
Oh, you're not?
Then what'd you do with my best friend?
No, you don't understand.
I lost you.
What?
You never lost me. I'm right here.
No, you don't get it.
No, I do get it.
Look, all you have to
do is show up tomorrow,
and then we'll finally be together
for the rest of our lives.
Isn't that what you want too?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Of course, but...
Elliot, you always overthink everything.
You have to finally
let yourself be happy.
That's all it takes.
It's just a choice that you have to make,
a switch that you have to flick on.
♪ ♪
Do you love me, Elliot?
What?
Do you love me?
♪ ♪
Of course I love you.
I've always loved you.
Great, because I love you too.
♪ ♪
So how about it, then?
You wanna start this new
life with me or what?
More than anything.
Okay, then it's settled.
I'll see you tomorrow.
♪ ♪
[GROANS]
Help.
♪ ♪
C-call someone.
Please.
♪ ♪
Call an ambulance.
I can't move.
♪ ♪
I need an ambulance.
But I'll lose her.
♪ ♪
And I can't lose her again.
[SIGHS]
♪ ♪
[SNIFFLES]
I'm sorry.
♪ ♪
[UNSETTLING MUSIC]
[GROANS SOFTLY]
[CHOKING]
I think you should look away too.
♪ ♪
[PANTING]
[SNIFFLES]
[WHIMPERING]
♪ ♪
Please, don't judge me.
This was inevitable.
You saw the earthquakes.
Both of us can't exist
here in this world.
♪ ♪
I had no other choice.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --