If they show up and we're
gone, my family's dead.
My life puts everyone I love in danger.
My instructions were
to find your brother.
Well, in that case, my phone's
not gonna do you any good.
I just wiped it.
Do you think it's possible
Mr. Robot is the reason
why you can't remember?
You didn't exist when
I was a kid, did you?
- Shh.
- Do not do this to him!
He's not supposed to know!
Why were you afraid of your father?
Were you afraid he was going to ask you
to do something you didn't want to do?
Yes.
This was our runaway
hideout. He always came here.
Remember somehow we ended up
at the Queens Museum instead?
When you're eight,
running away can be fun.
20, 19, 18,
17, 16, 15,
14, 13, 12...
What?
Who cares what I'm doing?
It's none of your business.
Don't worry about it.
I gotta do this. It's gonna help us.
Just trust me.
Ready or not, here I come!
Angela's not gonna find us here.
Just give me a sec.
I heard that!
You suck at this game!
I see you, butthead!
I killed him.
Okay, Elliot, we need
to call the police.
His phone's ringing.
Oh, God.
The others are coming
back. Did you hear me?
We're not safe in this place anymore!
Elliot, you gotta listen to me.
Listen to me. You gotta
listen to me, Elliot.
We have to go. Elliot, we have to go!
We have to leave, Elliot.
You have to get up.
Elliot!
Elliot, look at me.
Elliot! Elliot!
Yo, make it plain.
Yo, he's not picking up, bro,
and I gotta fucking piss.
Man, I told you
at the Arby's up around the way, bro.
I'm not sitting on no
dirty-ass toilet seat, bro.
You know they be
getting hep C up they ass
in they pores and shit
sitting on that toilet, bro?
Man, I'm... I'm going inside, bro.
Yo, yo.
Boss told us stay
here till he done, son.
Bro, I'm gonna be quiet.
Yo, you don't wanna know
what's going on up there?
Come on, bro.
That was some cliff-hanger
shit they left us on.
Yeah, man. Come on, bro.
Yo, Arby's be delicious, though.
Got that five for five.
Shit's the fiscally responsible meal.
Man, I don't care about fiscally.
When it come to food,
I'm treating myself, man, period.
- Yo, you ever had Momofuku?
- Nah, see?
Yeah, you probably can't afford that.
I ain't never had Momofukus, bro.
I don't even know what that shit be.
You know what that shit be?
Oh, shit, bro!
What the fuck?
Oh, sh...
What are you doing, dummy?
Grab his wallet. Let's go.
Fuck.
Okay, come on.
We're gonna just get in this taxi.
Let's go. You're just fine.
Thank you. Just hold the taxi.
Come on, let's go. We gotta go.
Gotta go. It's okay.
I got you. There you go.
All right.
Okay, take us to the nearest
police station, please.
The nearest police station.
From everyone here at the E Corp family
to you and yours,
we're wishing you a
happy holiday season...
Slapjack!
Nuh-uh, my hand was there first.
Doesn't matter. I
called it first, doofus.
Don't call me doofus, dingus.
All right, all right. Official ruling.
You each get half the cards.
- But, Aunt Trudie...
- No buts.
I am the referee.
It's not fair.
Well, that's the way it's gotta be.
You're splitting the baby.
You can split my dick hole!
Thomas Alan DiPierro, you
apologize this instant!
- But, Mom...
- Now, young man,
or I'm taking your iPad.
Sorry, Aunt Trudie.
Now you go take a
time-out in the living room
and think about what you said.
♪ There'll be much mistletoeing ♪
Stupid idiot.
Think you can tell me what to do.
- What was that, young man?
- Nothing.
Ugh, I'm so embarrassed.
I don't know where he
got that language from.
His father.
Probably letting him
watch SummerSlam again,
the son of a bitch.
♪ There'll be parties for hosting ♪
♪ And caroling out in the snow ♪
♪ There'll be scary ghost stories ♪
♪ And tales of the glories ♪
- Mama?
- Not now, Tommy.
♪ Of Christmases long, long ago ♪
- Mama!
- I said not now, Tommy!
Mama! Mama!
♪ It's the most wonderful
time of the year ♪
♪ There'll be much mistletoeing ♪
♪ And hearts will be glowing ♪
♪ When loved ones are near ♪
Did you know that cities
were created by lightning?
It's true.
I heard it on a podcast.
Villages used to be made
of organic materials.
Mostly mud, sticks.
Then one night about 12,000 years ago,
a bolt of lightning hit
a chunk of limestone...
Which formed a powder
that we now know is...
Anyone?
Cement?
Very smart, Darlene.
You're absolutely right.
Just think what a
different world it would be
if that lightning had struck a tree
or a puppy instead.
This remarkable city you see before you
would be nothing but
sticks and leaves and...
Puppy shit.
But the lightning hit stone,
and the people of Turkey
awoke to find that they
were in the cradle of
modern civilization,
all from one perfect moment
of violent convergence.
Isn't it wonderful?
Destruction can be so productive.
Her phone is useless.
There's nothing here.
She wiped it clean.
I had hoped for better news.
I told you you were wasting your time.
Looks like you're just
going to have to restore
your phone for us yourself.
Eat shit. Then die.
Oh, nasty mouth on this one.
She doesn't know anything.
And even if she did, she
wouldn't give her brother up.
Trust me.
Well, I wish I could, Dominique,
but you failed me, remember?
Of course, I always held
out hope that you would rise
to the occasion when the time came,
but in the back of my mind,
I always knew you'd never
be able to see it through.
Why? Because I'm not a murderer?
You work for the federal government
of the United States of America.
What are you, trying to be funny?
No, what I meant was
is we all know how much
you care about Darlene.
What?
The hell are you talking about?
Oh, you know.
Miss Alderson's interrogation video?
The one you pleasure yourself to?
In private?
I mean, all that excess
energy may be the reason
you can't get any sleep, Dominique,
but in any case,
it's pretty strong evidence
of your affection for Miss Alderson,
wouldn't you say?
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Did she not know?
Uh, that is...
Embarrassing.
Um, I apologize.
But...
While we're at it...
What did happen between the two of you?
I mean, it just all
seemed quite... dramatic.
We fucked, end of story.
Mm, come on, now.
I have a feeling there's a lot more
to this relationship than just that.
Just sex.
Sorry to disappoint you.
I don't believe you,
so... no worries there.
Disappointment averted.
Look, cunt stick.
I don't know what you're driving at,
but there's no way I'm
giving up my brother,
so whatever you're gonna do to me,
you might as well make it fast.
Okay.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I wouldn't take it out if I were you.
I am not a doctor,
but I am 99% sure I punctured a lung.
Yeah, that wheezing
sound is her chest cavity
filling up with air,
slowly compressing her lung.
You pull it out now,
it'll just supercharge the process.
She's got about 15
minutes before she goes
into full cardiac arrest
or drowns in her own blood.
Maybe longer,
since Dominique's such a fighter.
What was the fucking point?
She has nothing to do with this.
You said you would never
give up your brother.
I simply thought this would
be the most expeditious way
to break our stalemate.
You give us what we want,
we'll get Dominique the
care she so urgently needs.
Or she'll die here.
I'll just have to get it
out of you some other way.
Does that make sense?
Elliot, you have to come in with me.
I can't do this.
I can't do it.
Okay.
What do people do?
People like me,
when then they find out
about something like this...
What can they do?
They just try to keep going.
I should have fought him.
If I... if I would have...
if I would have fought him,
maybe... maybe it would have stopped.
Look at me.
You were just a child.
It wasn't up to you.
I wanna go back to forgetting.
You never did forget.
You may not realize it now,
but you've been struggling
with this for years.
The itch in the back of your mind,
the one you can't scratch?
It's always there.
You just didn't know what it was.
But now you do.
He made me feel special.
You are special,
and what he did is... it's not
gonna take that away from you.
You will survive this, Elliot.
Call you tomorrow, okay?
No, no, I'm sorry...
I'm sorry I got you
involved in any of this.
You don't... you don't have
to take care of me anymore.
I'd like to see you again.
You shouldn't go through this alone.
I know.
Promise me you'll take care of yourself.
Where are we going?
You sick fuck!
She needs help. She is dying over there.
Oh, I'm aware.
I want nothing more than to
get her to our medical team
- and have her stitched up ASAP.
- Bullshit.
Even if I gave you Elliot's location,
you would just let her die.
That couldn't be further from the truth.
I'm not saying it's been all
blue skies with Dominique,
but most of our moles have
some growing pains at first,
and she is honest, loyal,
and she loves her family,
all of which are qualities
that make her easy to control.
No, Dominique has pluck.
Losing her is the last thing I want.
Don't do it.
Don't tell her anything.
See?
I knew you two shared
a special connection.
Even now, I can sense it.
It's like a kind of...
Phantom electricity.
I wonder, did Dominique ever
introduce you to her mother?
Can't say she did.
Oh, that's too bad.
Trudie is my favorite.
You know, at first, I
thought our relationship
would be purely tactical.
Isolate the mark, ingratiate yourself,
find a pain point...
you know, the usual.
But then I got to know her,
and she is just so lovely and kind.
Every other word out of her
mouth is about you, Dominique.
She is so desperate
for you to find someone
that she even looked to
me as a potential match.
Can you imagine that?
I was so flattered.
You really have to admire
a mother who cares so much
about her daughter's
happiness that she's willing
to ignore certain red flags.
Like what, the fact that
you're fucking insane?
Mm.
You know, when I was in high school,
my parents discovered my
profound interest in taxidermy.
They had similar concerns,
so they had me undergo
a series of tests,
but the results were
always underwhelming.
No signs of personality disorder,
no unusual thought processes.
All the doctors arrived
at the same conclusion.
That I'm remarkably normal.
You wouldn't be fucking
doing this if you were normal.
She can't breathe over there.
Because of you.
Let's remember that.
I see this is causing
you a lot of grief.
I didn't want that.
I honestly thought we
would have moved on by now.
Let me continue to help you.
What are you doing?
I'm making a phone call
to our surveillance team
outside your mother's house.
Why?
Because I'm going to start
killing your family members.
Janice, please don't.
- There are 13 of them.
- Janice!
Four children...
eight adults, and Trudie.
Don't! They're innocent, Janice! Please!
I wonder how many of them
have to die before you buckle.
Please, Janice, don't!
Please!
Do not do this.
Please don't!
Stop!
Stop.
Okay, hand me my phone.
I'll give you my brother's location.
I'll do whatever you
want. Just don't hurt them.
Now look who has pluck.
Why did you bring me
here? I don't get it.
What are you trying to say?
That I couldn't stand up to him?
That I ran away here instead?
I'm sorry I let him
do those things to you.
I'm sorry I didn't fight back.
I'm sorry I didn't protect you.
I am so fucking sorry!
I'm sorry, okay?
That isn't why I brought you here.
This sign.
It used to be over there.
Can you help me?
This is the key to my old bedroom.
Why would I hide it here?
It was Dad's key to our room.
We took it from him
so we could lock him out.
We thought that if he
didn't have his key...
He wouldn't be able to
come in and hurt us anymore.
That's right.
We hid the key
so the monster couldn't get to us.
Don't you see?
You're wrong.
This wasn't running away from him.
I was fighting back.
Location checks out.
Alderson's phone was
here, but he's gone.
Well, then where is he?
We're not sure yet.
There's a dead body, but it's not him.
Thank you.
He wasn't there, Darlene.
That doesn't make any sense.
You're right. It doesn't.
I gave you access to his location.
We tracked him on my phone.
You saw it for yourself.
You're gonna have to find another way.
There is no other way.
If he wasn't there, I
don't know what to say.
I mean, look,
my brother doesn't tell me anything.
Okay, if he's not with
his phone, it's because...
either something happened to him
or he doesn't want me
to know where he is.
You're lying.
Are you serious? I'm not lying.
Yes, you are. You are
a filthy lying liar.
Oh, my God.
She doesn't know.
She doesn't know where her brother is.
She's telling the truth.
Trust me.
I know what it looks
like when she's lying.
This isn't it. It's a dead end.
You know, maybe you're right.
Like my mother used to say:
you can't juice the orange
when there's only the rind left.
- Give me my phone.
- What are you doing?
I'm gonna have my men
gut Trudie like a trout.
What? Why?
Only way to confirm
or deny her statement.
No, I gave you my brother's location.
I did what you wanted me to do.
Correction: you gave
me his phone's location,
not his location.
No, no. Think about it, Janice.
My family's all you've
got. If you kill them now...
Then I'll have nothing
left to hang over your head.
- No!
- I know.
Looks like we both have a
lot riding on this, Dominique.
You know, in poker,
they would call this an all-in move.
You fucking moron.
You're doing this for no reason.
- I don't know where he is.
- And I'm calling your bluff.
Please, Janice, please.
We can work something out.
- Please.
- I'm sorry, Dominique.
I held off as long as I could.
No answer.
What?
Your men.
Are they not answering?
And why exactly... would
you be asking me that?
Probably wanna ask him.
Him? Who's him?
Check my phone.
He's probably been trying to call me.
_
Dom, love, I've been
waiting for your call.
Hello?
Sorry for the delay,
but your plan worked.
The license plates you
gave me checked out.
Don't worry. Everything's grand.
I've got your family and we're
on our way to the safe house.
Who's this?
Who the fuck is this?
I asked you first.
This is Deegan. Who's this?
This is Janice.
Oh, yeah. The Dark Army lass.
Listen, tell Dom thanks
for the technicality.
We're square now.
Oh, and I'm really
sorry about your boys.
What do you mean? What boys?
The fellas guarding Dom's mum's house.
I had to give 'em a bit
of a holy show back there.
There weren't no other way.
What? Speak English!
I fucking killed 'em, dear.
Shot 'em in the brains.
With me gun.
Don't worry, though.
They died with dignity.
Well, a few of them might
have shat themselves,
but I believe that's
what the Frenchies call
de rigueur, innit?
Mr. Deegan,
I don't think you
have taken into account
the primal forces you
are meddling with here.
If you proceed down this path,
I will use every means at my disposal
- to make sure that you nev...
- Yeah, yeah.
I heard it all before. Take a number.
Et cetera and so forth.
Now you have yourself a
merry little Christmas.
Ta-ta for now, you flange.
You're okay.
- What do I do?
- Give me the phone.
I have a 10-13.
Officer needs immediate assistance.
202 West 20th street.
Apartment 16B.
Go.
What?
You can't be here when they arrive.
No, I am not leaving you like this.
I don't give a shit if they arrest me.
Don't be stupid.
This is all my fault. I did this to you.
You wanna help me?
Go find Elliot and take them down.
Hey, kiddo.
Uh, sorry for the time-out.
We're almost good to go.
Darlene's got everything we need
to grab the Deus Group phone numbers
and intercept the 2FA codes.
And I'm working on a script
to transfer all the money.
Uh, but we don't have long.
Meeting's in an hour.
That's not why you
let me back in, is it?
Wanna talk about it?
Mind if I talk, then?
The only reason I'm here...
Is to make sure no one ever hurts you.
That was supposed to
be your father's job,
but he failed.
He was too weak.
But you...
You were strong.
You fought back...
The only way you could.
You brought me here to protect you...
from him.
I tried to keep you safe...
Only show you the memories
when the two of you
were friends before...
I thought I could...
store the truth so you'd
never have to see it...
or feel it.
The fact is...
I didn't wanna see it either.
I made a terrible mistake.
I was afraid...
Afraid of what this would do to you...
To us.
This was never my secret to keep.
And you deserved better than
to live in darkness for so long.
I'm so sorry.
I failed you too.
I understand if you
can't forgive me or...
If you decide to shut me out for good...
Just as long as you know...
I am not your father.
I never was.
I know.
You're nothing like him.
That's why I created you.
You're the father I needed...
Not the father I had.
If I could have stopped him...
If I could go back in time,
change everything
that happened to you...
make it all go away...
Then I wouldn't be me.
And I wouldn't have you.
I don't know if I can go
through with the hack anymore.
I don't know if I can do anything.
I can't do it.
I can't do it. I'm sorry.